Chapter 881: Is It Time

The arm attached to the hand was giving off rays of white light, and it was hurtling through the air with such immense power that it was threatening to tear the very space apart.

Upon being struck in the chest, the speed of Han Li's retreat was increased by severalfold, and he crashed heavily into the stone door behind him.

A loud thump rang out as the stone door was smashed to bits, sending shattered rocks flying in all directions, while Han Li crashed into the ground to form a huge crater.

Given how powerful his physical body had become, he didn't sustain any severe injuries from the blow, and he was just about to spring back to his feet, but right at this moment, two black chains shot forth through the air, then wrapped themselves tightly around his arms and legs.

The chains were extremely resilient, and Han Li was instantly completely immobilized.

Before he had a chance to struggle any further, a figure appeared before him in a flash, then closed a hand around his throat.

The hand belonged to none other than Chen Yang, and he chuckled in a cold voice, "Don't bother struggling, you're not getting away."

At this point, two black-robed figures had appeared beside the crater, with each one holding one end of the black chains.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly upon seeing this, but he didn't struggle.

The gladiators of the ninth area were very alarmed by this turn of events, but once then identified that it was Chen Yang, none of them dared to say anything.

"How did you know what I was planning?" Han Li asked.

"Given your personality, there's no way that you would've resigned yourself to your own fate. It's hilarious that Hu Bi and the others were completely complacent to this, so I'm the one who gets the credit for catching you red-handed," Chen Yang chuckled.

Han Li offered no response to this.

One of the black-robed figures placed a set of shackles onto Han Li's body, while Chen Yang declared to the crowd that was gathering nearby, "This man has broken the rules of the arena, so we're taking him to the city lord's manor for his punishment. There's no need for alarm, this has nothing to do with any of you."

Judging from everyone's reactions, no was feeling particularly reassured.

"Take him away!" Chen Yang ordered before departing.

Daoist Xie trailed along behind Chen Yang in silence, not even sparing so much as a single glance at Han Li, much to Han Li's dismay.

Before long, the group had left the ninth area, and in the wake of their departure, the entirety of the ninth area erupted into a frenzy, with everyone discussing the potential reasons for Han Li's capture.

Standing silently among the crowd was Chen Lin, and he lingered in the lobby momentarily before returning to his room.

……

It didn't take long for Chen Yang and the others to leave the arena and enter Green Goat City.

The city lord's manor was situated at the highest point of Green Goat City, so Chen Yang's group attracted a great deal of attention as Han Li was paraded through the city.

Han Li walked along with his head lowered while rapidly considering his options.

Chen Yang seemed to have gleaned Han Li's thoughts, and he warned, "I know you're capable of unleashing spiritual attacks, but now that we're already in Green Goat City, you're not getting away, so don't even try it. Otherwise, you'll only be heaping more punishment upon yourself."

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon hearing this, and his heart sank a little further.

The group quickly arrived at the city lord's manor, which was quite an enormous place, but wasn't very opulent in appearance.

Chen Yang walked straight in with Han Li without declaring his own arrival, and he was walking along at the forefront of the group with a contemplative look on his face.

Daoist Xie was trailing along behind him, while Han Li and the two black-robed guards brought up the rear as they arrived outside the city lord's cave abode.

"City Lord Du, it's me, Chen Yang," Chen Yang declared as he strode over to the tightly shut stone door.

There was no response from inside the cave abode.

Chen Yang's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he was just about to announce his own arrival again when the stone door slowly opened amid a heavy grinding sound.

"Come in."

A voice rang out from inside, and it seemed to be tinged with a hint of irrepressible fury.

Han Li beckoned to the two black-robed figures, who brought Han Li over to him before departing.

A slightly sympathetic look flashed through his eyes as he took a glance at Han Li, then pressed a hand down onto his shoulder before pushing him into the cave abode.

Upon entering the cave abode, it was revealed that there were three other people in the main hall aside from Du Qingyang.

These three were three of the four captains that had been summoned by Du Qingyang for that earlier meeting, and out of the four captains, only Hu Bi was missing.

"Why did you bring him here now?" Du Qingyang asked with a displeased look in his eyes.

"I had just returned from a hunting trip when I caught this man attempting to escape from the arena, so I detained him and brought him to you, City Lord Du," Chen Yang replied as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Du Qingyang's expression darkened even further upon hearing this, and a hint of fear had appeared in the eyes of the three captains.

"Security seems to have been a little lax in the arena of late. I suggest that we dedicate more manpower to tightening security so something like this doesn't happen again. After all, there's no guarantee that we'll be so fortunate next time," Chen Yang continued.

There was a square-faced young man standing next to Du Qingyang, and he took a resentful glance at Chen Yang. He was the one responsible for overseeing security in the arena, so he was going to be held culpable for this close call.

"You did very well," Du Qingyang praised, but his expression remained as stony as ever.

It seemed that he had no intention of assigning blame, and the square-faced young man was very relieved.

"I was only doing my job, City Lord Du. If you have no further instructions for me, then I'll be taking my leave now," Chen Yang said as he extended a respectful bow.

Du Qingyang took a hesitant glance at Chen Yang, then sighed, "Don't go just yet. I just so happen to have something that I need to discuss with you."

"Please go ahead, City Lord Du," Chen Yang immediately replied.

Du Qingyang beckoned for him to come closer, so Chen Yang left Han Li under Daoist Xie's supervision before approaching Du Qingyang.

"This morning, Hu Bi was found dead in his room," Du Qingyang said in a low voice.

An astonished look appeared on Chen Yang's face upon hearing this, and he asked, "How did he die?"

"No one knows. He didn't have external injuries, nor were there any signs of battle in his room. The only thing worthy of note is that there's some residual blood in both of his ear holes," Du Qingyang replied.

"Could it be that he was poisoned then? Surely not! Given his physical constitution, what type of poison could possibly have killed him?" Chen Yang speculated with tightly furrowed brows.

"There aren't any leads to pursue at the moment. The problem is that now that he's dead, the task that I assigned to him has been cast into limbo, so I want you to manage the Sinha Blood Array in his stead. What do you say?" Du Qingyang asked.

Chen Yang was ecstatic to hear this, and he hurriedly cupped his fist in a salute as he replied, "Thank you, City Lord Du! You can count on me!"

"Prior to initiating the ritual, I have to go into seclusion for a while, so I'll leave it to you to complete the array's setup. I'll look into Hu Bi's death, but don't let that distract you from the task at hand. Make sure to prioritize the ritual and the Sinha Blood Array above all else," Du Qingyang said, and Chen Yang and the three captains immediately gave a collective affirmative response.

After that, Chen Yang departed with Daoist Xie and Han Li, but instead of returning to the arena, Han Li was taken to an underground prison.

……

Over a month flew by in a flash.

Right at this moment, the door of Han Li's cell was suddenly opened, and two figures strode in from outside.

The visitors were none other than Chen Yang and Daoist Xie, and the former said, "Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Li. Have you been well?"

Han Li was sitting in a corner of the cell, and he looked up as he asked, "Is it time?"

Chen Yang faltered slightly upon hearing this, then smiled as he replied, "I suppose it is."

Han Li rose to his feet in silence, then dusted himself off before making his way out of his cell.

The armored guards outside immediately converged to surround him, but Chen Yang waved them off, and Han Li began making his way down a corridor.

Chen Yang walked along beside him, while Daoist Xie and the others trailed along behind them.

"Do you have any final wishes, Fellow Daoist Li? Perhaps I can help you fulfill them," Chen Yang jibed with a faint smile.

"My wish is for you to spare me and escort me out of Green Goat City. Will that be doable?" Han Li asked in an indifferent manner.

"That's obviously not a wish that I can grant, but if you teach me your cultivation arts, then I'll ensure that you at least get a proper burial instead of being fed to the scaled beasts," Chen Yang replied with a smile.

Han Li offered no response.

The group followed the corridor downward, and it didn't take long before they arrived in a large underground space.

It was a dome-shaped space that seemed to be a naturally forming underground cave, and even before walking inside, Han Li was struck by a hot and sickly sweet aroma that caused him to involuntarily scrunch up his nose.

After walking inside, Han Li spotted a strange stone platform that had been constructed in the shape of a pentagram.

The stone platform was several hundred feet in size and around three feet tall. At its center were two slots that were both around a foot deep, while connected to each of the five tips of the pentagram was a round platform that was around six feet tall with a fist-sized beast core fitted into a slot on each platform.

All five beast cores were B tier beast cores of an exceptional quality, and at this moment, Du Qingyang and the three captains were all standing beside the stone platform, seemingly awaiting their arrival.

Chapter 882: What Did You Do?

"He's here, City Lord Du," Chen Yang declared as he extended a respectful bow.

For this occasion, Du Qingyang had put on a brand new red robe, and he gave Chen Yang an authoritative nod.

Among the three captains, the bald man strode forward before shoving Han Li onto the stone platform, forcing him into an indentation at the center of the platform.

As soon as Han Li set foot into the indentation, he immediately felt a sticky sensation beneath his feet, and he looked down to discover some type of sticky black substance inside the indentation, looking much like black blood plasma that had accumulated over a long period of time.

Despite how sticky the substance was, it was only giving off a faint odor.

"Enter the array," Du Qingyang ordered with a serious expression.

Chen Yang and the captains instantly flew into the array, while Du Qingyang himself made his way onto the stone platform, then sat down with his legs crossed in another indentation across from Han Li.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but he knew that he was in a very grim situation indeed.

"Begin," Du Qingyang ordered, and Chen Yang and the others also sat down with their legs crossed, then channeled the starpower in their bodies as they each pressed a hand against the B tier beast core in front of them.

A burst of faint buzzing rang out as the entire stone platform began to vibrate slightly, and all of the beast cores lit up in unison, releasing bursts of formidable energy fluctuations.

At the same time, wisps of starpower were surging out of the beast cores before flowing into the indentation that Han Li was situated in along the patterns on the stone platform.

With this injection of starpower, the viscous substance beneath Han Li suddenly began to bubble and churn before slowly climbing up his body until it had enveloped the entirety of his lower body beneath his waist.

Han Li gave a muffled groan as he felt a burst of heat surge through his body, as if his blood had been set alight in his veins, and he could feel his true spirit bloodline beginning to stir.

His heart beat began to accelerate, while his mouth became as parched as a desert, and he wanted to struggle and resist, but his body was impossibly heavy, as if it had been injected with lead.

A series of hazy true spirit projections began to surface over his body in an uncontrollable fashion, and a look of elation and greed appeared in Du Qingyang's eyes upon seeing this.

"I didn't think you would have so many true spirit bloodlines in your body! Looks like I made the right decision to wait for so long," Du Qingyang chuckled in an excited manner.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed, and he offered no response.

Right at this moment, his expression changed slightly, and he felt an empty sensation in his own body. He hurriedly looked down to find that there was a crimson trough on the stone platform that connected him to Du Qingyang.

At this moment, his blood was flowing toward the other side along the trough as if it were being sucked out of his body drop by drop.

As the blood flowed to Du Qingyang, it began to rise up around him, forming a spherical crimson light barrier that encompassed his entire body.

A low roar escaped his lips as he clenched his fists tightly by his sides, and his eyes gradually took on a crimson color.

All the while, the sense of emptiness and depletion in Han Li's body was only becoming more and more pronounced, and he could sense his own true spirit bloodlines being stripped out of his body bit by bit.

If things were to continue in this fashion, not only would he lose his true spirit bloodlines, even his life would be forfeit!

With that in mind, a decisive look appeared in his eyes, and his Heaven Controlling Vial tipped over on its own within his stomach, pouring the crimson liquid inside into his body.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li's skin turned bright red like the shell of a steamed crab, and wisps of pink mist began to rise up out of his body.

Du Qingyang was still immersed in the blissful sensation of absorbing Han Li's true spirit bloodlines, and he paid the discoloration of Han Li's skin no heed, merely chalking it down to a normal reaction that one would have as the victim of this array.

Before long, Han Li's skin began to crack open like a plot of parched land, but no blood was flowing out of the cracks on his skin.

At this moment, all of the other true spirit bloodlines in his body were in a relatively stable state, but his Xuanwu bloodline was surging through his veins.

This was something that had happened to him in the past, so he was able to tolerate this sensation, but even so, the outflow of blood didn't cease. Instead, due to the unrest in his Xuanwu bloodline, his blood was only flowing faster out of his body and into the trough.

However, as this blood began to flow into Du Qingyang's body, his eyes abruptly widened, and a a stunned look appeared on his face.

At the same time, the spherical crimson light barrier around him began to bubble and churn like a pot of boiling water.

Du Qingyang gave a muffled groan, and his blood began to churn in his own body far more violently than Han Li's blood in his. Even with his incredibly formidable physical constitution, he felt as if his body were about to be torn apart.

He let loose a loud roar as he joined his palms in front of his own chest, and all of his joints cracked and popped and over two hundred profound acupoints lit up over his body, while a layer of hazy white light also emerged over his skin.

Shrouded within this layer of white light, his frenzied blood seemed to have been temporarily suppressed.

Unaware of what Han Li had just done, Du Qingyang was merely under the impression that true spirit bloodlines were supposed to be this violent.

As time slowly passed by, the outflow of blood from Han Li's body only sped up further and further, and his complexion gradually began to pale, while a dazed look had appeared in his eyes.

Du Qingyang's teeth were tightly gritted, and a savage grin appeared on his face at the sight of Han Li's condition.

"To think that a mere human can harness so many true spirit bloodlines and make them all coexist in harmony. What a truly remarkable feat. I thought that forcing you to fight in the arena would tame some of the wild nature of your true spirit bloodlines, but they're still incredibly violent," Du Qingyang harrumphed through gritted teeth.

At this moment, Han Li felt as if his entire body had been sucked dry, and he was too feeble to respond.

He could only reflexively channel his Great Universe Origin Arts and Wingform Ascension Arts to try and arrest some of the starpower that was flowing out of his body alongside his blood, but the endeavor was one that was largely futile.

Right at this moment, a Giant Mountain Ape projection emerged over Du Qingyang's body, and it was thumping its own chest in a display of domination. At the same time, an Azure Luan Bird projection appeared before attempting to fly away with all its might. On the other side, a Lightning Bird projection appeared, and it also began to struggle vehemently.

All of the true spirit projections that had previously appeared around Han Li had now appeared outside Du Qingyang's body, but they were all in an extremely unstable and violent state.

Du Qingyang's eyes widened drastically as bursts of incredibly formidable tearing forces began to ravage his entire body, causing him to let loose an involuntary roar.

At the same time, cracks also began to appear over his skin, but these cracks were all bright red, and they were countless tiny gashes that had been torn into his skin.

Blood began to flow out of those gashes, instantly staining his robes.

Chen Yang and the captains were all at a temporary loss for what to do upon seeing this, but then Chen Yang suddenly yelled, "Don't just sit there, channel the array to help City Lord Du absorb the true spirit bloodlines!"

Everyone immediately sprang into action upon hearing this, injecting their starpower into the beast cores before them with all their might.

However, right at this moment, a sinister grin suddenly appeared on Chen Yang's face, and he raised a fist before slamming it into the beast core in front of him.

The beast core instantly exploded, sending white starpower erupting in all directions, while Chen Yang darted back in retreat.

This turn of events had unfolded so abruptly that no one was able to react in time, and in the next instant, the entire Sinha Blood Array was thrown into a state of imbalance, causing a burst of incredibly powerful tearing force to surge throughout it.

Everyone inside the array was rooted to the spot by this tearing force, rendering them unable to escape.

"What did you do, Chen Yang?" Du Qingyang roared in a furious voice.

"All I did was slightly alter your Sinha Blood Array, City Lord Du. As for what the effects of the alterations are, you'll just have to see for yourself," Chen Yang replied with a smile.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the crimson light barrier around Du Qingyang abruptly expanded to form a crimson vortex, which instantly encompassed the entire Sinha Blood Array and everyone within it.

The captains could see that things had gone awry, and they wanted to escape the array, but it was already too late.

Their hands were tightly glued to the beast cores in front of them, and their arms had turned bright red.

At the same time, their profound acupoints were lighting up one after another in an uncontrollable fashion, and their blood and starpower were being involuntarily sucked out of their bodies and into the crimson vortex.

Thanks to his superior cultivation base, Du Qingyang was still able to hold his own within the array, but the captains were all in a truly dire state.

At this moment, Du Qingyang's eyes were bright red, and there was blood flowing down from the corners of his eyes as he glowered at Chen Yang with a look of murderous rage.

Chapter 883: Rapid Absorption

"It should be about time," Chen Yang murmured to himself as he observed the array.

Sure enough, as soon as his voice trailed off, the crimson vortex that encompassed the entire array abruptly ceased in its rotation, then began to revolve in the opposite direction.

The blood that had flowed into Du Qingyang's body instantly began to flow back toward Han Li through the trough between them, and the viscous black substance beneath him immediately began to bubble and churn.

Han Li felt as if his own body were about to be set alight, and his skin instantly turned bright red, and the cracks all over his skin also began to glow red.

The blood that had originally only covered his lower body spread further upward, climbing up to his chest, then his neck, before ultimately encompassing his entire body to form a huge crimson cocoon.

The blood that was surging into his body also contained the starpower of Du Qingyang and the captains, and it was an enormous influx of starpower that was completely beyond what Han Li's body was able to handle without the assistance of immortal spiritual power.

A string of muffled roars rang out incessantly from within the crimson cocoon, and Han Li could feel bursts of power crashing through his body like untamed bulls, making his limbs, his meridians, and even his head feel extremely swollen, to the point that they were about to explode.

This sensation was no less tortuous than what he had experienced back in the Bone Rinsing Lightning Pond.

At this point, all he could do was protect his own consciousness with all his might so that he remained lucid and awake.

Time slowly passed by, and everyone inside the array was persevering with gritted teeth.

Even now, Du Qingyang still wasn't willing to give up.

He was waiting for the influx of starpower to become too much for Han Li, thereby causing his body to explode, at which point he would finally be able to claim Han Li's true spirit bloodlines.

Once that happened, he was going to personally ensure that Chen Yang suffered an even more terrible death than Li Feiyu.

At this point, Chen Yang and Daoist Xie had already retreated to the edge of the cave, and he was sweating profusely as he looked on with a tense expression.

He was also waiting for Han Li to self-detonate as the power from the explosion would undoubtedly kill the captains in the array on the spot.

As for Du Qingyang, perhaps he wouldn't die from the explosion, but he would definitely suffer severe injuries that would place him at Chen Yang's mercy.

However, both Han Li and Du Qingyang were displaying far more perseverance than he had hoped to see, and that was making him feel very uneasy.

He had gone all in on this plan, and he didn't even dare to consider the consequences of failure.

In contrast, Daoist Xie was looking on with a completely calm and placid expression, as if none of this had anything to do with him.

As the crimson cocoon continued to expand, so did Han Li's body, and at this point, he was looking like a bloated humanoid balloon that could explode at any moment.

However, right at this moment, a series of true spirit projections reappeared around him, but instead of attempting to flee the array, they fused into his body one after another.

At the same time, the blood in the bodies of the captains in the array also began to rapidly surge toward Han Li, and in no more than just a few moments, their bodies had become significantly shrunken and withered.

Du Qingyang finally gave up all hope upon seeing this. If he were to wait any longer, then the roles of aggressor and victim would be switched.

With that in mind, he let loose a thunderous roar, and several dozen more profound acupoints emerged over his body, with all of them appearing on his abdomen and arms.

He raised a fist, and starpower converged rapidly toward the end of his fist as he threw an almighty punch into the ground.

The Sinha Blood Array shuddered violently alongside the entire underground cave, but it was able to withstand the force of his punch.

Du Qingyang clearly wasn't surprised to see this. While constructing the array, he had considered the possibility of an attack during the ritual, so he had ensured that the array was extremely resilient, to the point that even he couldn't destroy it in a single blow.

Never did he think that his meticulous plan would work against himself.

The impact of Du Qingyang's punch launched him up into the air, and while in mid-air, he threw another punch to forcibly sever his own connection to the array.

Blood came spewing out of his mouth as his chest sank in significantly, but he was finally able to escape the array's control.

In the wake of his escape, the captains were forced to bear the array's full fury on their own, and they instantly exploded one after another amid a string of bloodcurdling howls.

Du Qingyang took a moment to steady himself, then turned to Chen Yang with a furious expression and charged straight at him, paying no heed to his own injuries.

"Chen Yang, it's time for you to pay with your life!"

A cold sneer appeared on Chen Yang's face as he scoffed, "You're nothing more than a spent force at this point."

Despite the mockery on his face, he didn't dare to take Du Qingyang lightly at all, even in his terrible condition, and his profound acupoints lit up as he lashed out with both fists.

All of a sudden, a long screech rang out from within the crimson cocoon, and all of the power contained within the entire Sinha Blood Array began to gush rapidly into Han Li's body.

At the same time, his body began to swell rapidly, giving him the appearance of a bulging ball of blood, and even more cracks had appeared over his skin.

However, aside from Daoist Xie, no one noticed the speck of faint green light that had appeared in Han Li's abdomen.

As the bursts of starpower surged into his body, the Heaven Controlling Vial instantly sprang into action, sucking in the starpower. As a result, only the bloodline power from Du Qingyang and the captains were still rampaging in his body.

Han Li was already on the verge of losing consciousness, but the strain on his body was significantly alleviated by the Heaven Controlling Vial, allowing him to cling onto consciousness.

He immediately channeled his Wingform Ascension Arts with his might, rapidly absorbing the rampant bloodline power and starpower within his body.

After being passed through the Heaven Controlling Vial, the starpower had become quite tame and easy to absorb. As for the bloodline power, most of it was actually Han Li's own true spirit bloodlines, so even though it was much more difficult to absorb than the starpower, it was still manageable.

As these two bursts of power began to integrate themselves into his body, his swollen body slowly began to contract.

At the same time, bursts of starpower began to surge toward his lower body, and all of a sudden, a profound acupoint was opened on his left leg with a dull thump.

This was immediately followed by another profound acupoint on his right leg, followed by two more profound acupoints on his legs.

All of a sudden, he had reached full mastery over the Wingform Ascension Arts, having opened all eighteen of the cultivation art's profound acupoints.

A hint of incredulity flashed through Daoist Xie's eyes upon seeing this.

Opening consecutive profound acupoints should've been fantastic news for Han Li, but in this particular situation, it was a very troublesome turn of events.

Now that he had reached full mastery of both the Wingform Ascension Arts and the Great Universe Origin Arts, there were no more profound acupoints left for him to open.

The remaining starpower and bloodline power was still running rampant in his body, and to further compound his woes, the two types of power in the Sinha Blood Array still hadn't completely run out, so there was still more and more surging into his body, and he didn't know if he could withstand such an enormous influx of energy.

On the other side of the hall, over a hundred and thirty profound acupoints had lit up over Chen Yang's body, but he was still well and truly on the back foot against Du Qingyang, and a series of large cracks had appeared on his suit of bone armor.

However, Du Qingyang certainly wasn't enjoying himself, either. His injuries were very severe, and he was having to forcibly suppress them. If he couldn't keep those injuries in check, then his condition could take a sharp and rapid turn for the worse, resulting in catastrophic consequences.

All of the profound acupoints on Du Qingyang's arm lit up, and he slammed a fist into Chen Yang's crossed arms, upon which a loud crack rang out.

Both of Chen Yang's arms were instantly snapped, and he was sent flying back through the air, tumbling over the ground like a ragdoll before slamming violently into the wall of the cave.

Upon falling to the ground, he couldn't help but throw up a large mouthful of blood.

Instead of charging in to press his advantage, Du Qingyang remained standing on the spot, internally suppressing his own injuries as he said in a cold voice, "I always felt like you had a rebellious bone in you, but I didn't think you would actually dare to betray me. You may have hid your true power this entire time, but that's not going to save you from your inevitable death."

"Whether I live or die isn't up to you anymore," Chen Yang sneered as he wiped the blood from his lips.

Chapter 884: Revenge

"Quit bluffing!" Du Qingyang roared as he stomped his feet into the ground, and all of the profound acupoints on his legs lit up in unison, following which he abruptly vanished from the spot, as if by instantaneous teleportation.

In the next instant, Chen Yang felt a gust of fierce wind blow past his ear, and Du Qingyang's joined middle and index fingers came plunging directly toward his temple like a sharp dagger.

There was no time for Chen Yang to do anything aside from instinctively dodge to the side, but Du Qingyang certainly wasn't going to let him off the hook so easily, and he changed directions to continue pursuing Chen Yang, while a profound acupoint appeared on each segment of his two fingers, further enhancing their power.

Right as it seemed like Chen Yang's fate was sealed, a resounding boom suddenly rang out, and the stone door of the underground cave exploded violently, following which a yellow figure flew into the room before crashing into Du Qingyang from the side.

A dull thump rang out as Du Qingyang was sent flying back over a thousand feet, crashing into the mountain face on the other side of the hall before tumbling to the ground.

He struggled to his feet with some difficulty, and he was finally unable to suppress his own injuries any longer as blood came spewing out of his mouth and onto the ground.

He clasped a hand over his own wounded chest as he stumbled back a few steps, and he was only able to steady himself after leaning back against the stone wall behind him. However, his legs were still trembling uncontrollably, and it looked as if he were going to fall at any moment.

A perplexed look flashed through his eyes at the sight of the yellow figure that had just flown into the room, and he exclaimed, "Gu Qianxun? Why are you doing this?"

Indeed, the yellow figure was none other than Gu Qianxun, and there was a frosty look in her eyes as she glowered at Du Qingyang and said in a cold voice, "Why am I doing this? I've been waiting for this day for thirty thousand years!"

"Thirty thousand years? Who are you?" Du Qingyang asked in a cold voice.

"It looks like your memory isn't that great, so let me give you a reminder. Do you still remember that woman that you secretly abducted from Profound End City all those years ago?" Gu Qianxun asked.

A hint of realization appeared on Du Qingyang's face as he murmured, "Profound End City? Could it be..."

"All those years ago, you used this same Sinha Blood Array in this exact same place to suck out her true spirit bloodline. In the end, her body detonated, and she wasn't even able to die with an intact body!" Gu Qianxun said as her lips quivered with rage.

"Yan Hongyu... How are you related to her?" Du Qingyang asked.

"Shut your mouth! A deplorable scoundrel like you has no right to speak my mother's name!" Gu Qianxun yelled in a furious voice.

"I see, so she was your mother. No wonder you came to my Green Goat City over six thousand years ago and requested to join the arena, this is what you've been plotting all along, isn't it? Your patience is truly exemplary," Du Qingyang sneered.

"Even if I had to wait another thirty thousand years, it would still be worth it! Your subordinate has already turned on you, and it's finally time for you to receive the retribution that you deserve!" Gu Qianxun declared in a righteous manner.

Du Qingyang took a glance at Chen Yang, then turned his gaze back to Gu Qianxun as he asked, "You must've played a role in Hu Bi's death as well, right?"

Gu Qianxun offered no response, merely continuing to glower at Du Qingyang with a cold sneer on her face.

Du Qingyang spat out a mouthful of viscous blood, then harrumphed coldly, "Seeing as you're so attached to your mother, I'll send you to the afterlife to reunite with her using the power of her bloodline!"

Du Qingyang closed his eyes as he spoke, and his hands balled up into tight fists as he let loose a thunderous roar.

Immediately thereafter, a layer of tiny iridescent scales that were extremely tightly packed together surfaced over his body, giving off a dreamy glow under the light of the flames in the surrounding braziers.

Daoist Xie raised an eyebrow at the sight of Du Qingyang's transformation, and he murmured to himself, "That's the bloodline of the Illusory Scale Rainbow Serpent... What a rare sight..."

Gu Qianxun's expression darkened even further upon seeing this, and her fury was only further exacerbated.

"You bastard!" she roared in a furious voice as a series of profound acupoints lit up over her legs, and she leaned forward slightly before pouncing directly at Du Qingyang like a hunting panther.

As the two passed each other by, Gu Qianxun extended a hand with her fingers joined together, then plunged it at Du Qingyang's throat like a sharp dagger.

It was unclear whether Du Qingyang was too severely injured to dodge the attack, or he never intended to dodge it in the first place, but he took the attack head-on with his vulnerable throat.

A loud thump rang out, but right as the collision took place, a layer of faint rainbow light surfaced over Du Qingyang's throat.

Immediately thereafter, his throat contracted slightly before bulging outward like a spring, transmitting the power of Gu Qianxun's blow toward his own chest.

In that instant, it was as if his body had become that of a boneless serpent, and every single muscle of his began vibrating at the same frequency, transmitting the force of the attack into the ground, while his own body remained completely unscathed.

In the blink of an eye, he had shrugged off what had appeared to be a killing blow.

At the same time, Du Qingyang swung an arm through the air, throwing a palm strike at Gu Qianxun's face.

Gu Qianxun took a step to the side upon seeing this, then lashed out with her fist in retaliation.

A string of profound acupoints lit up over her arm, releasing a burst of tremendous force that instantly tore her sleeve apart, revealing a section of her fair and slender arm.

Despite how delicate the arm appeared, the muscles on it were very clearly defined, giving the arm the appearance of an appendage that harbored immense explosive power.

Her fist struck Du Qingyang's palm with a resounding boom, sending powerful shockwaves erupting in all directions.

Du Qingyang's serpentine body was able to transmit the force of the clash into the ground once again, but he was still forced back in retreat, only drawing to a halt after stomping a foot down onto the stone wall behind him.

As for Gu Qianxun, she was sent flying back through the air before crashing heavily into the mountain face on the other side.

A large section of the mountain face instantly collapsed, burying her under a pile of shattered rocks.

Chen Yang's expression darkened significantly upon seeing this. He had thought that Du Qingyang would be in terrible condition after suffering backlash from the Sinha Blood Array, but it appeared that he was still far from a spent force.

"Chen Yang, I've always treated you well, yet you've thrown my kindness back in my face. Now, it's your turn," Du Qingyang said as he turned to Chen Yang with a cold sneer.

A series of dark red lines began to appear around his eyes as he spoke, giving his already hideous face an even more sinister appearance.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he sprang forward with explosive force while reaching out a hand to grab at Chen Yang's chest.

Chen Yang dodged to the side to just barely evade the blow, but several deep marks were still left behind on the bone armor in front of his chest from Du Qingyang's fingers.

Before Chen Yang even had a chance to catch his breath, Du Qingyang's body suddenly began to elongate, following which a serpentine tail wrapped itself around his midsection before exerting tremendous compressive force.

Chen Yang clenched his fists tightly as he let loose a thunderous roar, and all of his profound acupoints lit up as a burst of formidable energy fluctuations erupted out of his body in an attempt to shake off Du Qingyang.

However, Du Qingyang's body only loosened slightly before constricting tightly around him once again.

At the same time, he opened his mouth to a seemingly impossible degree, unhinging his jaw like a true serpent as he chomped down upon Chen Yang's head.

Chen Yang was struggling with all his might, but to no avail, and he could only raise an arm and lash out with all his might at Du Qingyang's head.

Right as Du Qingyang's mouth was about to close itself around Chen Yang, a burst of bright white light suddenly emerged beneath the pile of shattered rocks at the foot of the opposing mountain face, and Gu Qianxun flew out from within, sending loose rocks flying in all directions.

At the same time, she removed a white bone belt from her own waist, then lashed out at Du Qingyang with it.

Attached to the end of the bone belt was a piece of triangular bone that struck Du Qingyang on the face, raising a trail of dark red sparks.

However, the blow failed to inflict any injuries upon Du Qingyang. All it did was force his head slightly to the side, so he chomped down onto Chen Yang's shoulder instead of his head.

Gu Qianxun's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, but she continued to persist, charging at Du Qingyang while the bones that formed her belt rapidly compressed, transforming it into a bone longsword that was around four feet in length.

All of the profound acupoints on her body lit up, and the muscles on her arms bulged as she spun around several times in mid-air to build up tremendous momentum, then slashed her sword into Du Qingyang's head with all her might.

The sword struck the side of Du Qingyang's face, and blood immediately splattered through the air.

The sword had managed to slice through his skin and part of his skull, but it was unable to chop his head off. Instead, it was lodged into his cheekbone.

A sense of powerlessness welled up in Gu Qianxun's heart upon seeing this.

She had given that attack everything that she had, yet Du Qingyang was still standing.

Chapter 885: Different Objectives

"Do you see how powerful your mother's bloodline is now, little girl? It's a pity that you weren't able to inherit it. Otherwise, I wouldn't mind keeping you alive a little longer so I can suck the bloodline out of your body as well," Du Qingyang chortled as he raised his head from Chen Yang's shoulder.

Right at this moment, a fierce look flashed through Chen Yang's eyes, and he suddenly raised his right arm before plunging his hand toward Du Qingyang's body like a sharp dagger.

All of the two dozen or so profound acupoints on his arms were glowing as radiantly as the sun, and they were also giving off bursts of scorching heat.

A meaty thud rang out as the skin on Du Qingyang's abdomen was breached, but just like Gu Qianxun's bone sword, Chen Yang's right hand was only able to embed itself slightly into Du Qingyang's body before being stopped cold in its tracks.

Du Qingyang took a glance down at the wound on his midsection, then harrumphed coldly, "You really don't know when to give up, do you?"

However, right at this moment, a resounding explosion rang out as Chen Yang detonated his own right arm, blowing a large hole into Du Qingyang's body.

Du Qingyang let loose an agonized roar as a torrent of blood came gushing out of his mouth, yet he still chomped down at Chen Yang once again with a furious look on his face.

It seemed that he was no longer able to suppress his own internal injuries, and the rainbow scales on his body were flickering in an unsteady fashion, as if they could fade away at any moment.

A panicked look appeared on Chen Yang's face, and all he could do was raise his remaining left arm in a futile effort to defend himself.

All of a sudden, a blurry figure shot forth from afar, and close to twenty profound acupoints lit up over their arms as they slammed their fists down onto Gu Qianxun's bone sword, which was still lodged into the side of Du Qingyang's face.

Gu Qianxun's arms immediately went numb from the force of the blow, and the bone sword slipped out of her grasp, while she was sent flying back through the air.

This additional injection of force was sufficient for the bone sword to slice the rest of the way through Du Qingyang's skull, and his head came tumbling down from his shoulders before falling onto the ground with a dull thump.

Immediately thereafter, the bone sword was plunged into his dantian to destroy the nascent soul inside.

Chen Yang was completely rooted to the spot with a shocked look on his face, and his entire upper body was drenched in blood as he continued to stand in a daze with his left arm raised above him.

All of this had unfolded far too abruptly, and Gu Qianxun was also stunned by what she had just witnessed.

After a brief moment of stunned inactivity, she turned to the figure to discover that it was none other than Li Feiyu, the man that all of them had already forgotten about and had left for dead!

What was even more astonishing to her was that there were currently seventy-two profound acupoints on his body.

Aside from the fifty-four profound acupoints that he had cultivated using his Great Universe Origin Arts and his Wingform Ascension Arts, eighteen new profound acupoints had appeared on his arms.

After taking a closer look at the positions of the profound acupoints on Han Li's arms, an incredulous look appeared on Gu Qianxun's face as he exclaimed, "Those are the profound acupoints of the Titan Vajra Arts! How is that possible?"

They had only exchanged cultivation arts recently, so how was it possible that he had already mastered the Titan Vajra Arts? Could it have been thanks to the Sinha Blood Array?

A hesitant look appeared on Gu Qianxun's face, and she wasn't sure of how to proceed.

Meanwhile, Chen Yang had finally snapped back to his senses as well.

Du Qingyang was already dead, so he was naturally no longer able to bind Chen Yang any longer. As soon as Chen Yang rose to his feet, Du Qingyang's headless body immediately fell to the ground.

The three of them took a glance at one another, and a tense silence ensued, with none of them making a move.

Somehow, under some very unlikely circumstances, they had worked together to kill Du Qingyang.

Moments later, Han Li made the first move, taking a step back to distance himself from the other two slightly as he said, "If it's possible, I'd like to avoid having to battle the two of you."

Chen Yang and Gu Qianxun also each took a step back with apprehensive looks on their faces, and the latter said, "My thoughts exactly, Fellow Daoist Li."

"Whether we intended it or not, we only survived because we worked together, so let's end the bloodshed here," Chen Yang said as he forced a smile onto his own face.

After that, he pulled out a black stone box, then tipped out a crimson pill that he devoured.

A burst of white light immediately emerged from his right shoulder, and countless muscle fibers began to regenerate rapidly within the white light. In the blink of an eye, a brand new arm had taken shape, except it was still looking quite weak and tender.

Chen Yang then pulled out a piece of beast hide to wrap up his new arm, while Han Li wiped the blood from his face before asking, "Would anyone care to explain to me what happened here?"

"Is it not obvious enough, Fellow Daoist Li? Captain Chen Yang... No, City Lord Chen Yang and I worked together to hatch this plot against Du Qingyang, but in the end, we couldn't have done it without you, Fellow Daoist Li," Gu Qianxun replied with a smile.

"Does that mean that vial of red liquid was left for me by the two of you as well?" Han Li asked.

Up to this point, the situation had become quite clear to Han Li. Gu Qianxun was seeking vengeance, while Chen Yang desired the position of city lord, so the two of them had worked together to eliminate Du Qingyang.

In a massive stroke of fortune, Han Li had been swept up into their plot and absorbed the starpower and bloodline power of Du Qingyang and the captains, thereby significantly enhancing his physical prowess.

"That was indeed me, but rest assured, that was just a vial of blood from a Wild Blood Scaled Rat, and its only effect is to make one's bloodline more violent. Aside from that, it has no negative effects," Gu Qianxun said in an apologetic manner.

"No negative effects? Is that right?" Han Li asked, clearly unconvinced.

"If you insist on blaming me for this, then I have no defense for my actions. Indeed, my objective for getting you to drink this blood was so that it would inflict backlash upon Du Qingyang, and I never considered what would become of you," Gu Qianxun admitted in a candid fashion.

"I owe you an apology, Fellow Daoist Li," Chen Yang said as he extended a respectful salute. "If I hadn't invited you to come to Green Goat City, then you would've never been targeted by Du Qingyang for your true spirit bloodlines, and you wouldn't have been swept up in this mess."

"It's fine. At this point, there's no point in discussing such matters," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

Of course, he didn't believe Chen Yang and Gu Qianxun at all. However, at the time, the two of them would've only considered him to be a pawn, so there was no reason for them to be concerned for his wellbeing.

As for why their attitude toward him had suddenly changed, that was only because they were unable to glean his true power, so they were feeling wary of him.

"Your magnanimity is truly admirable, Brother Li," Gu Qianxun said with a smile.

"Now that your plot has been successfully carried out, there's no need for me to stay here any longer, so I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

At the moment, the threat of the Black Tribulation Centipede was still hanging over his head, so he had to find the Black Tribulation Stone as soon as possible.

"Hold on a second, Brother Li. Even though Du Qingyang and his most trusted captains are dead, he still has many remaining subordinates, and if we can't completely control them, then we could still find ourselves in some peril. My right arm is essentially disabled for the immediate future, so I have a request for you," Chen Yang hurriedly said.

"You want me to help you solidify your position as city lord?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. Only now have I come to realize just how powerful you are, Fellow Daoist Li. Hence, I would like to invite you to join my alliance with Fellow Daoist Gu. Once we claim Green Goat City together, not only will we no longer have to fear for our safety, we'll also have a stable source of beast cores to support our future cultivation," Chen Yang replied with a nod.

Han Li contemplated the proposal momentarily, then said, "I can help you, but I have two conditions that you must accept. Otherwise, our discussion can end here."

Chen Yang's brows furrowed ever so slightly upon hearing this, but he still prompted, "Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Li."

"The Black Tribulation Centipede in my body has to be removed, and on top of that, you also have to release Shi Kong and Daoist Xie," Han Li said.

"I want to help you, Fellow Daoist Li, but the problem is that these Black Tribulation Centipedes were personally refined by Du Qingyang, so I don't know how to get rid of them. Having said that, Du Qingyang has always had a very tightly guarded secret vault. Perhaps there's something in there that can help you get rid of the Black Tribulation Centipede in your body," Chen Yang said.

"Alright, then let's go and take a look in the vault now," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Regarding Fellow Daoist Shi Kong, for some reason, he was sent to Profound City by Du Qingyang not long after the three of you arrived here, and I haven't heard anything about him since.

“As for Daoist Xie, I've only been using him as a servant this entire time, and I'd say we've coexisted alongside each other quite harmoniously. If he's willing to return to your side, then I naturally won't refuse," Chen Yang said as he turned his gaze to Daoist Xie.

Han Li also turned to Daoist Xie, but the latter remained standing on the spot in a completely still fashion, as if he hadn't even heard the conversation unfolding right beside him.

Han Li's heart sank slightly upon seeing this, but he didn't say anything further, and the rather tense and awkward silence descended upon everyone.

In the end, it was Gu Qianxun who broke the silence.

"Let's discuss these matters some other time. How about we go to this secret vault first to find a way to remove the threat of the Black Tribulation Centipede?"

"I can take us there, but prior to that, let's clean up this place and ourselves first," Chen Yang said as he took a glance at the surrounding area.

Chapter 886: Joining Forces

Han Li, Chen Yang, and Gu Qianxun quickly cleaned up the cave, erasing all signs of the battle that had just taken place before piling the bodies of Du Qingyang and the others together.

After rummaging through Du Qingyang's body briefly, Chen Yang pulled out a black badge that was triangular in shape with two curved bulges on its surface, resembling a strange goat's head.

On one side of the badge was inscribed the words "Green Goat", while the other side read "Profound City". It was unclear what material the badge was crafted from, but there was black light constantly flashing over its surface.

Chen Yang was ecstatic to see the badge, and Han Li knew that it most likely represented the status of the city lord of Green Goat City.

"Take it back and look at it some other time, we don't have any time to waste here," Gu Qianxun said in a cold voice.

"My apologies, fellow daoists," Chen Yang chuckled as he stowed the black badge away, then pulled out a round white rock, which he rubbed briefly with his fingers before throwing it onto the pile of bodies.

The white rock was instantly set alight, erupting into a ball of white flames that enveloped the pile of bodies, causing them to quickly melt away.

Even before the bodies had fully melted away, Chen Yang changed into a set of new clothes, then pulled out two more suits of black armor for Han Li and Gu Qianxun.

Han Li accepted the suit of armor offered to him, but a perplexed look appeared on his face, and he didn't put it on right away.

"The vault is being guarded by a powerful subordinate of Du Qingyang's, and we have to get rid of him. If you're wearing these suits of armor, you'll appear less conspicuous."

Han Li nodded in response, and he was just about to take off his clothes when he stopped what he was doing and took a glance at Gu Qianxun.

His gladiator attire only consisted of a cape and a pair of shorts, so if he were to take that off, then he would be completely nude.

Right at this moment, the sound of rustling clothes rang out nearby as Gu Qianxun stripped off her yellow dress to reveal a set of tight-fitting white underwear.

The underwear was a little small, only just barely containing her breasts, which were slightly compressed out of shape and on the verge of popping out. Her voluptuous breasts were further complemented by her delicate and slender waist, as well as her long, supple, and perfectly proportioned legs.

However, there was almost no physical appeal to her body at all as her chest, lower abdomen, and legs were all riddled with scars. In particular, there was a huge scar on her chest that resembled a giant centipede, extending diagonally down from her collarbone, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this. At their cultivation bases, normal injuries wouldn't be able to leave any scars on their bodies. Only certain special weapons or extremely grievous injuries would be able to leave behind scars like these.

Regardless of which of the two was true for Gu Qianxun, it was clear that she had some stories to tell.

Gu Qianxun's expression remained calm and placid, as if she were completely alone, and she quickly put on the suit of black armor.

"Time is of the essence, so hurry up and get changed. Don't get hung up on useless things like gender sensitivities, I'd like to hope that my allies aren't so naive," Gu Qianxun said, then began to make her way out of the cave.

"She really is something, isn't she?" Chen Yang chuckled, and Han Li responded with a wry smile before quickly changing into his suit of armor.

The suit of armor included a visor that concealed most of his face, granting him an extra layer of protection.

After that, the trio left the cave, making their way up along the passageway that led to the cave, while Daoist Xie trailed along behind them.

Right at this moment, a faint voice rang out in Han Li's mind.

"How about we join forces, Fellow Daoist Li?"

The voice belonged to Gu Qianxun, and it was a different method of communication than voice transmission through spiritual sense.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he took a subtle glance at Gu Qianxun.

"I know you always like to act alone, that much was apparent to me after you refused to join my Myriad Bone Alliance. However, things are different now. Du Qingyang is dead, and my collaboration with Chen Yang has come to an end. Once he establishes himself as the city lord, we won't be of any further use to him, and on top of that, both of us have Black Tribulation Centipedes in our bodies," Gu Qianxun continued.

Han Li remained silent as he took a glance at Chen Yang's wrapped right arm.

Gu Qianxun could see what Han Li was implying, and he said, "Chen Yang possesses far more power than what he displayed just now. He may have detonated the profound acupoints on his right arm, but he's still not to be taken lightly. On top of that, he's a very deceitful and cunning man, so he can't be trusted. The only way we can ensure our safety is to join forces."

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes, following which he gave an almost imperceptible nod.

A hint of elation flashed through Gu Qianxun's eyes upon seeing this, but it then immediately vanished.

The party of four quickly made its way out of the passageway into a side hall of the city lord's manor, where many people were currently gathered, most of which were guards, administrators, and servants of the city lord's manor.

The members of Chen Yang's hunting party were also present, and they immediately approached him as one of them asked in a low voice, "How did it go, Captain?"

"It's done," Chen Yang replied with a wide grin, instantly eliciting a chorus of cheers.

Chen Yang raised a hand to make a quieting gesture, then said, "It's time to carry out the next phase of the plan. Everyone, split up from here."

"Yes!" everyone collectively replied before departing to play their roles.

"Let's go as well," Chen Yang said to Han Li and Gu Qianxun, then also made his way out of the side hall toward a secluded little path.

Shortly thereafter, the four of them arrived in front of a spacious stone hall, at the end of which was a stone gate that was several dozen feet tall. The gate was riddled with silver patterns that were glowing with radiant silver light, and on the stone wall above it was engraved the words "Green Goat Vault" in large golden characters.

At the center of the stone hall stood a black stone platform that was several dozen feet tall, atop which sat a gray-robed elderly man with his legs crossed and his eyes closed.

The elderly man was quite ordinary in appearance with the exception of the silver coloration of his cheeks, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

Close to a hundred rays of silver light were radiating from his body in all directions, giving him the appearance of a silver hedgehog.

Upon hearing the footsteps of Chen Yang and the others, the elderly man opened his eyes, and the silver light radiating from his body faded away.

"What brings you here, Captain Chen Yang?" the elderly man asked as a hint of wariness flashed through his eyes.

Chen Yang feigned an urgent expression as he hurriedly replied, "City Lord Du is currently using the Sinha Blood Array, but something's gone wrong, and we're in urgent need of Blood Soul Crystals, so he asked me to fetch some."

"The vault can only be opened by the city lord himself or someone holding a token from the city lord. Do you have a token, Captain Chen Yang?" the elderly man asked.

"I do, here's the city lord's badge," Chen Yang hurriedly replied as he pulled out the black badge that he had taken from Du Qingyang's body.

The wariness on the elderly man's face eased slightly at the sight of the badge, and he pulled out a silver key that was around a foot in length before turning to the stone gate.

Right at this moment, Chen Yang's eyes suddenly widened as if he had seen something incredible, and he pointed at the gate as he exclaimed, "What's that?"

The elderly man hurriedly swung around to inspect the gate upon hearing this, only to find that there was nothing amiss about it.

Right at this moment, three fierce gusts of wind swept toward him from behind.

Eighteen specks of starlight emerged over Han Li's arms, which thickened to around twice their original size while also taking on a golden coloration, resembling a pair of golden pillars that were thrust at the elderly man.

Around twenty to thirty profound acupoints had appeared on Chen Yang's left arm and left hand as well, and he plunged it viciously toward the elderly man's back like a peerlessly sharp white sword.

As for Gu Qianxun, she had pulled out her white bone sword and was slashing it through the air at the elderly man's neck.

"What the hell are you doing?!"

The elderly man could sense the formidable attacks coming at him from behind, and he knew that he didn't have time to turn around, so he began racing forward as a streak of silver light.

Even though he was a split-second slow to react, he was extraordinarily fast, and the attacks from Chen Yang's trio weren't able to catch up to him.

At the same time, bursts of silver light appeared over his body before rapidly connecting together, forming a suit of silver armor that was riddled with sharp spikes.

An urgent look appeared in Chen Yang's eyes, and he was just about to do something when Han Li's speed abruptly doubled, allowing him to catch up to the elderly in the blink of an eye before ramming his fists forcefully into his shoulder.

Radiant golden light erupted out of Han Li's fists as all of the surrounding space within a radius of several dozen feet collapsed violently.

The sound of shattering bone rang out as the elderly man was sent flying forward like a ragdoll before crashing heavily to the ground, and the suit of silver armor that was taking shape on his body faded away as well.

Before he had a chance to get up, a grotesque thud rang out, followed by a loud squelch as Chen Yang plunged his left hand through the elderly man's chest, emerging on the side with a beating heart before crushing it into pulp.

At the same time, Gu Qianxun's bone sword had also pierced through the elderly man's dantian to destroy the nascent soul inside.

The elderly man's body spasmed a few times before the light in his eyes quickly faded away, and the life was drained out of his body.

"Thank heavens Fellow Daoist Li was able to get to him before he fully donned his Star Spike Profound Armor. Otherwise, things could've gone very badly for us," Chen Yang said as he pulled out his arm and turned to Han Li with a smile.

A hint of wariness flashed through Han Li's eyes as he glanced at Chen Yang's left arm, which previously hadn't displayed any profound acupoints, and he offered no response.

Meanwhile, Gu Qianxun withdrew her bone sword, then shook it out into a bone belt before wrapping it around her own waist.

Chen Yang pried the silver key out of the elderly man's hand, then strode over to the gate of the vault.

Near the bottom of the gate was a white keyhole, and Chen Yang put the key inside before turning it a few times.

A string of mechanical clicks rang out, and the silver light on the stone gate faded away before it slowly swung open.

Chapter 887: Fruitless Trip

Chen Yang took a glance at Han Li and Gu Qianxun, then made his way into the vault.

Han Li and Gu Qianxun exchanged a glance with each other before following along.

The interior of the vault was just as large as a palace, and inside it were seven or eight large cabinets that were crafted from some type of black wooden material.

The material appeared to be quite extraordinary, and it was giving off a fragrant aroma that permeated throughout the entire space.

Each cabinet was split up into three levels, with each level bearing various containers that held things like precious materials, cultivation arts, and beast cores.

Han Li paid no heed to the cabinets as he cast his gaze directly toward the center of the vault.

A tall black stone pillar was standing there, and it was riddled with squiggly worm-like patterns.

At the top of the stone pillar was a black crystal roughly the size of a human head.

The crystal was as smooth as a mirror and giving off rays of bright black light that rippled through the air in all directions, carrying with a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations.

As soon as Han Li stepped into the vault, he could immediately sense that the Black Tribulation Centipede in his body had fallen into an even deeper state of slumber.

"That's the Black Tribulation Stone!"

Han Li took a glance at Chen Yang and didn't immediately make a move for the Black Tribulation Stone, while Gu Qianxun was also looking at the stone with a hint of elation in her eyes.

"You also know of the Black Tribulation Stone, Fellow Daoist Li? The problem is that this thing can suppress Black Tribulation Centipedes, but not entirely remove them, so let's see if there's something here that can do the job. My apologies, but given the current situation, we can only stay here for an hour at most," Chen Yang said.

Gu Qianxun nodded in response, then began rummaging through one of the nearby cabinets, while Han Li quickly followed suit.

With devilish qi and immortal spiritual power completely inaccessible in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, there were no restrictions in the vault, so the three of them were quickly able to complete an exhaustive search.

Around fifteen minutes later, Han Li set down a book with a grim look on his face, then turned his gaze to Gu Qianxun.

She also turned to look at him, and both of them could see their own disappointment and concern mirrored on each other's faces.

Neither of them trusted Chen Yang, so they had volunteered to look through all of the books in the vault, while Chen Yang was assigned with the task of searching through everything else.

However, there wasn't even any mention of Black Tribulation Centipedes in any of the books.

Right at this moment, Chen Yang's voice rang out.

"I've found some useful information here, come and take a look, fellow daoists."

Han Li and Gu Qianxun hurriedly made their way over to him upon hearing this.

At this moment, Chen Yang was standing in front of a cabinet in a corner of the vault, looking at a black crystalline box that was around a foot in size. Through the semi-transparent walls of the box, one could see a series of Black Tribulation Centipedes sitting inside.

He was holding a black jade slab that was crafted from the same material as the crystalline box, upon which was inscribed a passage of small text.

Chen Yang handed the jade slab to Han Li and Gu Qianxun, who quickly read through its contents, and as they did so, their expressions darkened even further.

Written on the jade slab was the breeding method for Black Tribulation Centipedes. It covered the processes of raising Black Tribulation Centipede and implanting them into host bodies in great detail, but there was no mention of how to remove the creature from a host's body once implanted.

However, the jade slab did mention that Black Tribulation Centipedes were social creatures, and that each colony of Black Tribulation Centipedes had a king that ruled over them all.

This Black Tribulation Stone was a special material refined from the body of a Black Tribulation Centipede King, and that was why it was able to suppress Black Tribulation Centipedes.

In order to suppress a Black Tribulation Centipede, it was sufficient for one to carry a piece of Black Tribulation Stone the size of a fingernail.

While Han Li and Gu Qianxun were reading through the contents of the jade slab, Chen Yang strode over to the Black Tribulation Stone, then lopped off two egg-sized pieces before handing them to Han Li's duo as he said, "Carry these with you to suppress your Black Tribulation Centipedes."

"According to what's written here, I don't think we'll need pieces this large," Han Li said.

"That may be so, but it's better to be safe than sorry," Chen Yang replied.

"That's true. You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Chen Yang," Han Li said as he stowed the Black Tribulation Stone away, and Gu Qianxun also did the same, but her gaze was still fixed on the black jade box.

"Are you considering taking some Black Tribulation Centipedes with you? Go ahead, but make sure to use a special container to hold them," Chen Yang said.

Gu Qianxun shook her head as she pointed at one face of the box and said, "Take a look here."

That side of the box just so happened to be in Han Li's blind spot, so he was only able to see what she was referring to once he strode over to her side.

An intricate six-petaled flower design had been engraved onto the box there, and it seemed to be some type of symbol.

The engravings were very shallow, making them difficult to see unless one were to pay close attention.

"Do you recognize this symbol, Fellow Daoist Gu?" Han Li asked.

The design didn't appear to have been engraved onto the box simply for decorative purposes.

"I've seen this design in Profound City prior to coming to Green Goat City, it's the emblem of the master swordsmith, Mistress Liu Hua," Gu Qianxun replied.

"Mistress Liu Hua? Female swordsmiths are quite uncommon," Han Li mused.

"I've heard of Mistress Liu Hua as well, and he's actually a man. There's a tribe by the name of the Hundred City Tribe in the Holy Realm, and the tribe excels in forging swords. The most skilled swordsmith of each generation in the tribe receives the title of "mistress", and Senior Liu Hua is the current mistress of the Hundred City Tribe.

“However, for some reason, he was cast into the Scalptia Spatial Domain by the Night Sun Empire around a million years ago, and he's been residing in the main city of Profound City all this time. All of the weapons refined by him are exceptional, priceless pieces. Even Du Qingyang had once requested a weapon from him, but was turned down," Chen Yang said.

"I see. Any idea why his emblem has appeared on this box?" Han Li asked.

"Perhaps this box was made by Mistress Liu Hua, or perhaps he has something to do with the Black Tribulation Centipedes," Gu Qianxun speculated.

"There's still a bit left of the vault that we have to search, so let's go through that first," Chen Yang interjected.

Han Li raised his head to discover that there was still one more cabinet that hadn't yet been searched, and this one was laden with miscellaneous items.

Even though the chances of finding what they wanted on this cabinet were quite slim, they still conducted a thorough search.

Han Li picked up a glowing dark purple crystal, then carefully inspected it with his spiritual sense, but didn't discover anything special about it, so he set it down before picking up another item beside it.

This item was a palm-sized black statue depicting a devilish deity with three heads and six arms in a strange seated posture, and a hint of intrigue flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

He had seen a black statue in Daoist Master Bone Shine's storage tool that was almost identical to this one in size and material, except the two differed in posture.

Could it be that the two statues are somehow connected? Han Li thought to himself, then took a glance at Chen Yang and Gu Qianxun to discover that they were busy looking through other things, so they hadn't noticed what he was doing.

A beam of translucent light shot out of his glabella before vanishing into the statue, which shuddered slightly before immediately going through a series of poses, of which there were a total of twelve, and with each pose that it adopted, a passage of strange text would appear on its back.

However, these twelve poses were completely different from the ones displayed by Daoist Master Bone Shine's stone, and even though Han Li couldn't read this text, it was quite apparent to him that the text displayed by the two statues was also different.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this. It seemed that this statue and the one that had once belonged to Daoist Master Bone Shine belonged to the same set.

After inspecting the black statue for a moment longer, he placed it down onto its original spot in a seemingly nonchalant manner.

It didn't take long before the three of them completed the search of the cabinet, and sure enough, they discovered nothing of value.

The only useful thing that they had found was that black jade slab, so the three of them gathered around the black jade box again.

"In any case, this is technically a lead," Han Li mused with a contemplative expression.

Gu Qianxun offered no response as she turned her gaze to Chen Yang.

"My apologies for my inability to find a way to remove the Black Tribulation Centipedes from your bodies. However, once I've eliminated all of Du Qingyang's loyal followers, I'll be sure to send out people to investigate the matter and give the two of you a satisfactory answer," Chen Yang said with an apologetic expression.

"A satisfactory answer? When is that going to come?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Du Qingyang was the only one who knew how to remove Black Tribulation Centipedes from their host bodies, but he's dead now. I'll continue searching for leads in the city lord's manor, and at the same time, I'll try and find out more information from Profound City as well. That should be enough to unearth a solution," Chen Yang hurriedly replied.

"Should be enough? I suggest you don't try to placate us with such insubstantial promises, Fellow Daoist Chen. Please give us a conclusive answer on the matter regarding our Black Tribulation Centipedes," Gu Qianxun said in a cold voice.

Chen Yang bristled slightly upon hearing this, and he also said in a cold voice, "Looks like the two of you have already joined forces. Are you planning to conclude your collaboration with me?"

At the same time, a layer of white light emerged over his left arm, and a tremendous aura erupted out of his body.

The aura that he was displaying here wasn't inferior to that of Du Qingyang's by much, and it was extremely sharp, making Han Li and Gu Qianxun feel as if there were countless tiny blades slicing through the space around them.

The two of them immediately released their auras as well, and their combined auras were able to hold their own against Chen Yang's.

The surrounding space was beginning to twist and warp violently, while the entire vault was also trembling slightly.

Chapter 888: Mysterious Statue

"Are you two really going to turn on me at a time like this?" Chen Yang asked with a stunned expression.

"That'll be up to you. If you want to fight it out here, we'll be happy to oblige!" Han Li harrumphed coldly as a layer of golden light surfaced over his arms, while Gu Qianxun also grabbed onto the bone belt around her waist.

"Right now, we have a common enemy in the form of Du Qingyang's residual forces, and infighting among ourselves will only benefit our enemies. If we escalate things too far and Profound City gets involved, then none of us will be spared," Chen Yang said as he slowly began to rein in his own aura.

Han Li and Gu Qianxun also withdrew their auras upon seeing this.

"I'll admit that I wasn't able to follow through on my promise of finding a solution to the Black Tribulation Centipedes in your bodies, so how about this? Once I've gotten rid of all of Du Qingyang's residual forces, I'll be sure to address this matter within a month, and if I still haven't found a solution by then, then each of you can state a different request for me. Is that alright?" Chen Yang asked.

Han Li and Gu Qianxun communicated briefly with one another through voice transmission upon hearing this, following which the former's expression eased slightly as he said, "Alright, we'll do as you say."

Having just killed Du Qingyang and the gray-robed elderly man, they now had an irresolvable vendetta against all of Du Qingyang's forces, so their only two options were to leave Green Goat City right away or continue working with Chen Yang.

Even though they hadn't found a way to remove the Black Tribulation Centipedes in their bodies, obtaining the Black Tribulation Stone ensured their safety for at least the near future, so this was already quite a good outcome.

"Thank you for your understanding, fellow daoists. As compensation for my failure to fulfill my promise to you, I can allow each of you to select two treasures from this vault to take with you," Chen Yang said with a warm smile, and it was as if the earlier confrontation hadn't happened at all.

Han Li was rather apprehensive of Chen Yang's drastic shift in demeanor, but at the same time, he was also quite tempted by the offer.

While searching through the vault, he had spotted many precious items, and in particular, there were many bodily refinement cultivation arts here that were very appealing to him.

"Alright, in that case, don't mind if we do," Gu Qianxun said with a smile.

"Go ahead and take whatever catches your fancy, but we don't have much time left, so do hurry," Chen Yang said with a smile of his own.

With that, Han Li and Gu Qianxun departed to search for the items that they wanted to claim.

Han Li strode over to one of the cabinets that was laden with cultivation arts, and after briefly hesitating between several of them, he quickly made his decision, picking out one.

He had briefly read through these cultivation arts earlier, but not in any fine detail due to the time constraints.

Right at this moment, Daoist Xie's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Don't choose any of those cultivation arts, take that black statue instead. It contains a bodily refinement cultivation art."

Han Li swung around with a startled expression upon hearing this, only to discover Daoist Xie standing by the entrance of the vault with his eyes cast downward like a loyal servant, paying no heed to the trio inside.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he waited in silence for further elaboration from Daoist Xie.

However, Daoist Xie didn't provide any further information.

On the other side, Gu Qianxun had already completed her selection, claiming a book and a length of golden beast bone that seemed to be the spine of a certain scaled beast.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he gave Daoist Xie a subtle glare before putting down the book in his hand to pick up the black statue instead.

A pleased look flashed through Daoist Xie's downcast eyes upon seeing this.

After claiming the statue, Han Li turned his gaze elsewhere.

At the moment, he didn't require anything urgently aside from cultivation arts. No ores or materials were appealing to him, and things like weapons and armor weren't very useful to him, either.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he strode over to another cabinet that was laden with beast cores, all which were glowing radiantly with starlight.

Seeing as he didn't need anything else anyway, he may as well select a high-grade beast core. Even though Chen Yang had promised him a steady supply of beast cores to support his cultivation, he certainly knew much better than to place his trust in Chen Yang.

Furthermore, the more advanced the caliber of a beast core, the more precious it was, not just because high-grade beast cores harbored more starpower, but also because they were particularly helpful when it came to opening profound acupoints. Even now, Han Li still clearly recalled the pivotal role that the B tier beast core had played in opening his profound acupoint in the star pond.

Du Qingyang had arranged the beast cores in order of descending quality from left to right, seemingly for ease of access.

Hence, Han Li made his way straight to the left side of the cabinet, where there was a white jade box with a series of patterns engraved upon it.

Han Li gently opened the jade box to reveal a fist-sized white beast core that was glowing as radiantly as the sun.

It was so bright that it was almost impossible to look at, and it was giving off astonishing starpower fluctuations.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up at the sight of the white beast core.

At this point, he had already become very familiar with beast cores, and he could tell that this beast core couldn't even be compared with the one that Gu Qianxun had given him, meaning that it went beyond the realm of B tier beast cores.

A faint smile appeared on his face as he closed the jade box again, then made his way back to Chen Yang's side.

"I would like these two things, Fellow Daoist Chen. Is that alright?" he asked as he raised the jade box and the black statue.

Chen Yang took a glance at the two items that he had selected, and he didn't pay much heed to the black statue, but a slightly pained look flashed through his eyes at the sight of the white jade box, and he replied, "Of course. However, you seem to have selected an A tier beast core.

“The higher the grade of a beast core, the more difficult it is to refine, and due to the immense amount of starpower contained within an A tier beast core, you could easily suffer backlash from it if you're not careful, so do proceed with caution."

"I'll be sure to keep that in mind, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li said with a faint smile.

Chen Yang took another reluctant glance at the white jade box, then said, "Let's go."

Chen Yang picked up the black jade box full of Black Tribulation Centipedes as he spoke, then made his way out of the vault, followed closely by Daoist Xie.

Han Li and Gu Qianxun exchanged a surprised glance at the sight of Chen Yang picking up the black jade box, following which the two of them left the vault as well.

With Chen Yang leading the way, the group quickly arrived in a side hall in the city lord's manor, and upon entering the hall, a slightly solemn look appeared on Chen Yang's face as he said, "Please wait here for me for a moment, fellow daoists. Right next to this room is the main hall where Du Qingyang used to hold all of his meetings.

“I'll find a way to assemble all of his residual forces there, and if things go smoothly, then I won't require your assistance. However, if things go not so smoothly, then I must ask you to lend me your help."

"Right now, we're all in the same boat, and if the boat sinks, all of us go down with it, so of course we're willing to lend you our full support," Gu Qianxun said with a smile.

"Fellow Daoist Gu is right, so just rest assured and do what you need to do, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li agreed.

Chen Yang gave a slight nod upon hearing this, then departed with Daoist Xie, leaving only Han Li and Gu Qianxun behind.

"Come and have a seat, Fellow Daoist Li. Given Fellow Daoist Chen's powers and cunning, I don't think our services will be required at all," Gu Qianxun said as she beckoned to Han Li after taking a seat next to a stone table in the hall.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he also sat down at the table, then asked, "How much do you know about Chen Yang?"

"There's far more to him than meets the eye, and if anyone dares to take him lightly, they'll only suffer an even worse fate than Du Qingyang," Gu Qianxun replied.

Han Li fell into deep thought upon hearing this.

A hesitant look appeared on Gu Qianxun's face, following which she said, "Fellow Daoist Li, there's something that I feel like I need to tell you."

"You want to talk about what happened with the Heart Pitting Insects, right? I'm assuming you were the one who instructed Scarface to do it?" Han Li asked.

"You already knew?" Gu Qianxun exclaimed with a surprised expression.

"I only guessed that to be the case after some recent events. After all, there's no incentive for Du Qingyang and Chen Yang to kill me, and it appears that you have no incentive, either, but in reality, there's a hidden incentive for you beneath the surface," Han Li said.

"Looks like you're even smarter than I thought. What is this hidden incentive of mine?" Gu Qianxun asked with a faint smile.

"Du Qingyang is a sworn enemy of yours, and he's already far more powerful than you to begin with. You must've been worried that he would become even more powerful after absorbing my true spirit bloodlines, thereby making revenge an even more unattainable goal, and that's why you wanted to kill me in advance, right?" Han Li said.

"That's right. At the time, Chen Yang and I had already hatched a plan, but it wasn't to use your true spirit bloodlines to inflict backlash upon Du Qingyang. Instead, we were plotting an assassination.

“However, after you survived the Heart Pitting Insects, I was forced to see you through new eyes, and Chen Yang and I later adjusted our plan to tamper with the Sinha Blood Array instead after hearing about Du Qingyang's plans for you," Gu Qianxun replied with a nod.

"Why have you suddenly decided to come clean to me about this?" Han Li asked.

"Seeing as we're working together, I thought it was best that we be as open and candid with each other as possible. After all, Chen Yang is no easier than Du Qingyang to deal with, and if we don't have full trust in each other, then we'll eventually die by his hands as well," Gu Qianxun sighed.

Chapter 889: Plotting a Rebellion

Around two hours later, the conference hall had become quite rowdy and chaotic.

Around a dozen men that were dressed in all types of attire were seated around a huge stone table, and each of them was holding a black stone goblet full of scaled beast blood while conversing spiritedly with one another.

Chen Yang was seated near the main chair at the head of the table, gently stroking his goblet with one hand, while his other hand was concealed up his sleeve. Even though everyone else was drinking, he refrained from doing so, and even when an acquaintance proposed a toast to him, he would only bring the goblet to his lips before setting it down again.

Placed on the stone table beside him was a covered black box, making it impossible for anyone to glean its contents.

Right at this moment, a tall and imposing man with tusks jutting out of his mouth approached Chen Yang with a smile as he asked, "Why has City Lord Du suddenly ordered you to gather all of us here? Is there something important to be announced? How about you tip me off in advance?"

"I would love to tell you, Captain Mou Lin, but honestly, I have no clue myself. Rest assured, once everyone's here, all will be revealed by City Lord Du himself," Chen Yang replied with a smile.

Right at this moment, the doors of the hall were opened, and three people made their way inside.

One of them was none other than the horned man who was responsible for overseeing the ninth area's arena battles, and he was accompanied by the two crimson-robed scribes.

As these people entered the room, a young man standing beside Chen Yang informed him through voice transmission, "Brother Chen, everyone's here now aside from the few who are out on hunting trips."

Chen Yang nodded in response, and the young man departed from the conference hall, closing the stone doors behind him.

Even after the newly arrived trio took their seats, Chen Yang was still in no hurry to speak, merely observing everyone in the hall in silence.

After a long silence, a red-faced devilish man with a pair of horns on his head finally ran out of patience, and he asked, "What's the meaning of this, Chen Yang? You summoned all of us here, saying that City Lord Du has something important to announce, so why is he still not here?"

The commotion in the hall quickly died down, and everyone turned to Chen Yang to hear his response.

"Why so impatient, Captain Xiong Pei? Just let City Lord Du take his time, and have some more beast blood while you wait. It's not every day that City Lord Du is in such a generous mood to allow us to drink this stuff," Chen Yang said with a smile.

The man by the name of Xiong Pei duly obliged, raising his stone goblet for another sip of beast blood.

Only after everyone had finished their drinks or were close to doing so did Chen Yang rise to his feet, then strode over to the main chair that was designated solely for Du Qingyang before sitting down on it.

Initially, no one noticed, but it didn't take long before everyone caught sight of what he was doing, and a tense silence instantly descended upon the entire hall.

The man by the name of Mou Lin instantly sprang to his feet as he yelled in a furious voice, "How dare you sit there, Chen Yang? Do you have a death wish?!"

Immediately thereafter, two more captains rose to their feet with enraged expressions as well.

"Stand up right now, you bastard!"

Chen Yang remained completely unfazed, stretching lazily before getting into a more comfortable position on the chair.

"Hold on a second, everyone. Like I said, City Lord Du has something important to announce today," Chen Yang said as he slowly swept his gaze over everyone present.

Everyone else in the hall was perplexed by Chen Yang's strange actions, and they all waited in silence for him to continue.

"Du Qingyang feels like he's unworthy of the status of city lord, so he's passed it onto me."

The entire hall instantly erupted into a raucous frenzy upon hearing this.

"What the hell did you just say?" Xiong Pei yelled as he sprang to his feet once again.

"What right do you have to covet the position of city lord?" someone else yelled.

"Are you trying to rebel, Chen Yang?" Mou Lin interrogated in a furious voice as he kicked his stone chair aside.

"He must be insane!"

A loud thump rang out as Chen Yang slammed a hand down onto the stone table and rose to his feet.

A series of cracks instantly appeared on the table, and everyone immediately sprang to their feet in alarm.

"You can ask City Lord Du himself to see if I've gone insane or not," Chen Yang said in a cold voice.

"Where is City Lord Du right now? I want to see him!" Mou Lin yelled.

"As you wish," Chen Yang said as he pushed the black box beside him onto the ground, and its lid immediately fell off upon impact to reveal its contents, namely Du Qingyang's severed head.

Everyone was astonished to see this, and Mou Lin rushed over to the head with his eyes wide with incredulity, then brushed aside the head's disheveled hair to reveal the face of none other than Du Qingyang.

"City Lord Du!" Xiong Pei yelled in an alarmed voice, while everyone else was still reeling, unsure of what to do.

Mou Lin, Xiong Pei, and several others were glowing intently at Chen Yang with furious expressions, while the rest of the people in the room were looking on with shocked and dazed expressions.

The two scribes exchanged a glance with each other, and their hands were trembling as they pondered what to write as part of their conference records.

In contrast, the horned man appeared to be quite calm and collected.

"How dare you kill City Lord Du! You deserve to die for this crime!" Mou Lin spat through gritted teeth.

"Everyone, let's exact vengeance for City Lord Du by striking down Chen Yang where he stands!" Xiong Pei yelled.

Everyone exchanged a few glances with one another upon hearing this, but no one dared to make the first move.

As the lord of the city, Du Qingyang was a ruler who presided over others by force, so while there were some who were loyal to him, that was certainly not the case for everyone.

"I'm willing to support whoever can kill Chen Yang as the new city lord!" Mou Lin yelled.

In the wake of this declaration, the atmosphere in the hall changed slightly, and many people began to step forward to surround Chen Yang.

"You want to kill me? Is that something that you're capable of right now?" Chen Yang asked in a cold voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the doors of the hall were flung wide open, and the members of his hunting party charged into surround everyone.

"What do you plan to do with your pathetic little band of minions?" Xiong Pei sneered, and a series of profound acupoints began to light up over his body one after another.

However, all of a sudden, the light emanating from his profound acupoints began to flicker slightly, and all of a sudden, he collapsed to the ground.

Immediately thereafter, more and more people in the hall began to fall to the ground, and all that were left standing were Chen Yang and the members of his hunting party.

"There was White Profound Beast bone powder in that beast blood, wasn't there?" Xiong Pei said in a furious yet feeble voice.

Chen Yang picked up his goblet of beast blood, then strode over to Xiong Pei's side before pouring it over his face as he sneered, "Isn't it a little late for you to be making that realization?"

Xiong Pei heaved a long sigh before closing his eyes and succumbing to his own fate.

Chen Yang paid no heed to him, slowly passing him by as he asked, "So what'll it be, everyone? Will you remain loyal to a dead man and follow him to the afterlife, or live and enjoy this prosperous city with me?"

The entire hall had fallen deathly silent.

In the neighboring side hall, Han Li smiled as he said, "Looks like you were right, Fellow Daoist Gu. Chen Yang clearly already had a plan for today. It appears that he's asked us to stay in this side hall not because he truly needs our help, but instead because he wants to show off to us."

"I chose to collaborate with him precisely because I could tell that he had very lofty ambitions, to rise to the top. Working with someone like him can be very effective, but at the same time, it can also be a double-edged sword," Gu Qianxun said in an indifferent manner.

Following a brief silence in the main hall, Chen Yang's voice rang out once again.

"Rest assured, everyone. For those who are willing to follow me, I'll only give you more than Du Qingyang ever has. However, anyone who dares to oppose me will be struck down right here and now!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he abruptly appeared beside a short and thin elderly man in a wraith-like manner, then stomped down heavily with his foot, reducing the elderly man's wrist to a mangled mass of blood, flesh and bone.

The man gave a muffled groan as his hand slowly unfurled to reveal a palm-sized white bone inside.

"The star bone of an Explosive Scaled Beast, eh? I never noticed that you were so loyal to Du Qingyang in the past, Fellow Daoist Wu Heng, certainly not to the point that you would detonate this beast bone just to wound me at the cost of your own life," Chen Yang mused as he picked up the white bone.

The elderly man gritted his teeth tightly as he replied in a feeble voice, "City Lord Du once saved my life. If I can't live to serve him, then I'll follow him to the afterlife."

"Chen Yang, do you really think that you can replace City Lord Du just by killing him? The envoys from the main city aren't going to acknowledge a traitorous piece of scum like you!" Xiong Pei sneered.

"When has the main city ever cared about any changes that have taken place in the subsidiary cities? As long as the offerings made to the main city are never delayed, they couldn't care less whether the lord of Green Goat City is Du Qingyang or me," Chen Yang chuckled.

Wu Heng knew that he was right, and a despairing smile appeared on his face as he sighed, "Just kill me."

Chen Yang duly obliged, slamming a fist down onto his lower abdomen, instantly causing his body to explode into countless pieces.

Chapter 890: Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts

"As you wish," Chen Yang said as he slowly withdrew his fist, then wiped it clean on Xiong Pei's clothes.

Xiong Pei's eyes widened, his body trembled uncontrollably as fear began to well up in his heart.

Not far away from him, the two scribes were also trembling uncontrollably. Chen Yang had always been so easygoing and amicable to them, and never did they think that there would be such a cruel and vicious side to him.

"I... I'm willing to follow Captain Chen Yang... No, City Lord Chen Yang!" the round-faced scribe yelled, breaking the tense silence.

"I'm also willing to follow City Lord Chen Yang," the square-faced scribe echoed, and everyone else immediately began pledging their loyalty to him as well.

A pleased smile appeared on Chen Yang's face, and he strode over to Mou Lin, then crouched down slightly as he smiled and asked, "What do you say, Fellow Daoist Mou?"

"I'm willing to submit to you," Mou Lin sighed.

"You may be willing, but I'm not willing to accept you!" Chen Yang said as a hint of killing intent flashed through his eyes, and he slammed his fist down onto Mou Lin's head without any warning.

A dull thump rang out as Mou Lin's head exploded like a ripe watermelon, and the entire hall descended into silence once again as everyone's fear was elevated to new heights.

It seemed that even surrendering to Chen Yang wasn't a sure ticket to survival.

"If you're going to kill us, then just do it. Why fool around with us like this?" the horned man suddenly scoffed.

"Oh? Looks like we have someone else with a death wish here," Chen Yang remarked with a faint smile.

"I certainly don't have a death wish, but if I'm going to die anyway, then I want to at least die with some semblance of dignity," the horned man replied in a calm manner.

"If I recall correctly, your name was Xuanyuan Xing, right?" Chen Yang asked.

"I didn't think you would know my name, Fellow Daoist Chen," the horned man replied in an indifferent manner.

"You have some guts. I like that. I'll get you to take over Mou Lin's position as leader of the city's patrol squads," Chen Yang declared.

The horned man faltered slightly upon hearing this, while everyone else also looked on in befuddlement.

"Mou Lin is a very sinister man, and he just tried to rally everyone to kill me, so I naturally couldn't keep someone like him around. As for everyone else, as long as you're willing to pledge your loyalty to me, all of you can survive," Chen Yang declared.

"I'm willing to pledge my loyalty to City Lord Chen Yang!" the round-faced scribe declared once again, and everyone else quickly followed suit.

……

In the neighboring side hall.

"Chen Yang really has executed his plan quite well. Even if there are still people who don't wish to accept him as the city lord, they have no choice at this point," Han Li mused.

"There's still more to come," Gu Qianxun said with a smile.

……

Inside the hall, the declarations of loyalty gradually began to die down as Chen Yang raised his hands for silence.

He strode over to Xiong Pei, then looked down at him with a smile as he asked, "What would you like to say after your near-death ordeal?"

At this point, Xiong Pei was already terrified, and his lips were quivering as he replied, "You know me, Fellow Daoist Chen... No, City Lord Chen. I'm not like Mou Lin, I don't have any ambitions. I'm genuinely willing to submit to you."

"Those sound like genuine words," Chen Yang remarked with a nod.

Xiong Pei was feeling a little more reassured upon hearing this, and he was just about to say something further when Chen Yang continued, "However, as a safety precaution, it's best to put in place some measures that are more reliable than empty words."

He pulled out a black stone vial from his sleeve as he spoke, then placed it onto Xiong Pei's chest before removing the stopper.

A black centipede that was around three inches in length slowly crawled out from within, then easily burrowed its way into Xiong Pei's body.

A despairing look appeared on Xiong Pei's face upon seeing this, but he didn't dare to raise any complaints and closed his eyes to accept his fate.

Everyone else was also completely at Chen Yang's mercy, so they naturally didn't dare to put up any resistance, either.

Chen Yang made a hand signal, and the members of his hunting party instantly sprang into action, pulling out black stone vials of their own to plant Black Tribulation Centipedes into the bodies of everyone laying on the floor.

"I'm sure all of you are familiar with Black Tribulation Centipedes, so I won't waste any time telling you about them. Now that Du Qingyang is dead, I'm the only one who can remove them, and if anyone makes a sufficiently significant contribution in the future, they can have their Black Tribulation Centipede removed," Chen Yang declared.

Everyone was still completely powerless to resist, so they could only allow the Black Tribulation Centipedes to burrow into their bodies.

With that, the final resistance had fallen, and Chen Yang had successfully taken over as the city lord.

However, due to the fact that there were still several hunting parties outside the city, Chen Yang didn't hold a celebratory ceremony right away. Instead, he continued to keep a low profile, planning to hold his inauguration ceremony only after everyone had been taken care of.

After that, all he had to do was send a lavish gift to Profound City from Du Qingyang's vault, and he would officially become the lord of Green Goat City.

Han Li wasn't interested in any of this, and he returned to his room in the arena that same night.

Even though he had been at the very center of the storm this entire time, he and Gu Qianxun had always been hiding behind Chen Yang, so no one aside from Chen Yang and Daoist Xie were aware of the roles that he had played in this power struggle.

Chen Yang had offered to take them out of the arena so that they could stay in Green Goat City as secret guest elders, but both of them had refused.

Just like Han Li, Gu Qianxun had chosen to remain in the arena for now.

After receiving confirmation from Chen Yang that Violet Spirit truly hadn't ever appeared in Green Goat City, Han Li's plan was to stay for a while longer before departing the city altogether.

However, prior to his departure, he had to find out what was happening with Daoist Xie.

That night, Han Li's room was brightly lit, and he was seated on a corner of his stone bed, inspecting a statue of a devilish deity in his hand.

A beam of translucent light shot out of his glabella and into the statue, and as usual, it cycled through those twelve different poses, with corresponding passages of text appearing on its back with each pose.

He was still no closer to understanding the texts, and his brows furrowed slightly at this thought.

Right at this moment, the sound of door-knocking rang out, and Han Li raised an eyebrow as he strode over to the door of his room, then opened it to reveal a familiar figure.

"What on earth are you plotting, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked as he allowed the figure into the room before closing the door.

"I don't have much time, so let's discuss the important stuff first," Daoist Xie said as he turned to Han Li with a serious expression.

For some reason, Han Li suddenly felt like Daoist Xie was looking a little unfamiliar, as if this wasn't the same Daoist Xie as the one that he had always known.

"You've inspected the statue with your spiritual sense already, right?" Daoist Xie asked as his gaze fell upon the statue in Han Li's hand.

Han Li nodded in response.

"Your spiritual sense is far more powerful than Du Qingyang's. He was only just barely able to make out the statue's different poses, yet you should be able to see the text that it displays, right?" Daoist Xie asked.

"The statue has a total of twelve poses, corresponding to twelve passages of text, but I don't understand any of it," Han Li replied.

"This statue is called a Heavenly Baleful Deity Statue. It's an ancient deity that was worshiped in the Devil Realm in ancient times, but the religion has since died off. The text recorded in the statue is also a type of ancient lost text called profound text.

“The statue contains an advanced bodily refinement cultivation art by the name of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, which consists of a total of twelve levels, the first three of which are in this statue," Daoist Xie explained.

"You must've asked me to choose this statue over the other cultivation arts in the vault for a reason, right?" Han Li asked.

"Those other cultivation arts may look flashy, but at the very most, they'll only allow you to open fewer than four hundred profound acupoints, whereas the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts contains four hundred and fifty profound acupoints," Daoist Xie replied.

A hint of elation appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

"And that's only the first three levels of the cultivation," Daoist Xie continued. "If you can find the other three statues and master all twelve levels of the cultivation art, you'll be able to open a thousand eight hundred profound acupoints."

Han Li was stunned into silence upon hearing this.

"Another benefit that comes with selecting this cultivation art is that during the cultivation process, one type of true spirit bloodline must be refined for each level in order to help the user open profound acupoints.

“If someone else were to use this cultivation art, they would have to take on an enormous amount of risk by incorporating so many different true spirit bloodlines into their body, but you have the advantage of the Twelve Awakening Transformations, which has allowed you to complete initial refinement of many true spirit bloodlines.

“Hence, it'll be far less dangerous for you to use this cultivation art," Daoist Xie continued.

"What do you mean by initial refinement?" Han Li asked.

"The refinement method that you used for your true spirit bloodlines is only a rudimentary one from your time in the Spirit Realm. This Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts contains a more advanced refinement method that'll allow you to completely refine your existing true spirit bloodlines, which will enhance your bloodline power while also assisting you in opening profound acupoints," Daoist Xie explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

"I'm going to begin teaching you how to read profound text now. I don't have much time, so let's begin right away," Daoist Xie said.

Chapter 891: Rapid Progress

A few minutes later, Daoist Xie withdrew his spiritual sense, then said, "I still have some time left, so you can ask me any questions that you want."

"What is going on? Han Li asked, raising a question that encompassed all of his questions."

"After arriving in Green Goat City, I began to remember many things, some of which are very important. All you need to know right now is that I'll be staying with Chen Yang for now to prepare for something important. After that, I'll travel to Profound City, and you'll be coming with me," Daoist Xie replied.

"I was also planning to leave Green Goat City to travel to Profound City while continuing my search for Violet Spirit. According to Chen Yang, Shi Chuankong is in Profound City, so I have to go and find him as well. However, prior to that, you have to tell me exactly what you're planning," Han Li demanded with tightly furrowed brows.

"Now's not the time to be revealing my plans to you. Just focus on cultivating the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and becoming stronger. Only then will you be able to assist me in my plans," Daoist Xie replied with a shake of his head.

"When will you be traveling to Profound City?" Han Li asked.

"You'll know when the time comes, but I should be staying in Green Goat City for at least the next three to four years, so make sure to make full use of this time," Daoist Xie replied.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed, and he was just about to raise another question when Daoist Xie declared, "Time's up."

After that, he departed without another word, leaving Han Li with even more questions that he had begun with.

He sat down with his legs crossed on his bed, then began studying the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with his newly learned profound text.

At first glance, the cultivation art was extremely difficult to grasp, far more so than the Great Universe Origin Arts, the Wingform Ascension Arts, and the Titan Vajra Arts, and the method of using the power of true spirit bloodlines to open profound acupoints included in the cultivation art was also extremely profound.

Even though he was now able to read the cultivation art, that was only the first step, and he still had much more studying to do.

Only after three days and three nights was Han Li just barely able to understand the first level of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and he immediately commenced his cultivation.

He pulled out a beast core and devoured it, then channeled the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and the thirty-six baleful acupoints on his chest and abdomen slowly lit up.

The first level of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts contained a hundred and fifty profound acupoints, all of which were also concentrated in the chest and abdomen.

The first level of the cultivation art placed heavy emphasis on building a solid foundation. Hence, all of its profound acupoints were gathered in the chest and abdomen to enhance the one's fundamental physical constitution. As a result, the practical improvement to be gained from it wasn't as immediately apparent as that of the Wingform Ascension Arts or the Titan Vajra Arts.

Such improvements would have to wait until he reached the second level.

However, Han Li didn't find this to be surprising at all.

Given all of his extensive experience in bodily refinement, he knew that the foundation establishment stage was the most important stage of a bodily refinement cultivation art, and the more profound acupoints opened during this stage, the more solid the foundation would be, therefore allowing for greater potential.

The reason why he was able to contend against other people who had opened more profound acupoints than him even back when he had only opened thirty-six profound acupoints was precisely because the thirty-six profound acupoints of the Great Universe Origin Arts were all foundational profound acupoints, thereby granting him a far more solid physical foundation than others.

Thankfully, the statue that he had obtained from Du Qingyang's vault just so happened to contain the first three levels of the cultivation art. With that in mind, he couldn't help but wonder which three levels the statue from Daoist Master Bone Shine's storage tool contained.

Right as Han Li was refining the beast core that he had just devoured, the Heaven Controlling Vial in his stomach suddenly shuddered slightly, following which a burst of starpower surged forth from within.

The burst of starpower was immense and extremely pure, far more potent than the starpower he was deriving from refining the beast core.

He initially faltered slightly upon sensing this, following which an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

Back when the influx of energy from the Sinha Blood Array was becoming too much for him to handle, the Heaven Controlling Vial had sprung into action, absorbing the starpower from Du Qingyang and the captains.

He had thought that the starpower had already been devoured by the Heaven Controlling Vial, but it was now being released to assist him in his cultivation.

He immediately took advantage of this, channeling the immense starpower toward the profound acupoints of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts while also drawing upon his true spirit bloodlines.

A series of true spirit projections instantly appeared around him, and his eyelids fluttered slightly as a surprised look appeared on his face.

Back in the arena, he had tried to draw upon his true spirit bloodlines on multiple occasions, but to no avail. It had felt as if his true spirit bloodlines had been somehow suppressed, but now, he was able to draw upon them without any effort, and he couldn't help but wonder if this was due to the effects of the Sinha Blood Array, or perhaps some other reason.

However, he then shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought. In any case, this was definitely good news, and he would be able to further refine his true spirit bloodlines from here.

In the past, Han Li had only been able to summon nine true spirit projections, but on this occasion, that number had increased to ten, with the new addition being a giant white snake with a body that was as pristine white as jade.

It had a pair of bright red eyes that resembled two vibrant rubies, but not only did they not give it a look of bloodlust, they only made the creature more majestic to behold.

This true spirit was called the Tengshe, and it was a true spirit bloodline that had flowed into Han Li's body from Du Qingyang through the Sinha Blood Array.

Coincidentally, the Tengshe was also one of the true spirits of the Twelve Awakening Transformations.

All of the true spirit projections aside from the Tengshe projection vanished at Han Li's behest, and it coiled itself around his body.

Wisps of the Tengshe's bloodline power were flowing through his body, converging toward a closed profound acupoint on his chest.

This profound acupoint would've been extremely difficult to open using starpower alone, but the true spirit power of the Tengshe was able to infiltrate it with ease.

The profound acupoint immediately began to open, and starpower gushed in through the opening to make further inroads.

A hint of elation appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Sure enough, the assistance from his true spirit bloodline was making it far easier for him to open profound acupoints.

However, his elation quickly turned to concern as he discovered that the outflow of starpower from the Heaven Controlling Vial was becoming faster and faster, to the point that it was almost overwhelming him.

At the same time, the Heaven Controlling Vial ensured that the starpower began accumulating in his meridians instead of seeping out of his body.

Han Li's entire body was gradually filled by starpower, and he began to glow more and more radiantly while his body began to take on a crystalline quality.

Excruciating pain began to surge through his body from the excessive buildup of starpower, and it was even more agonizing than the influx of starpower and bloodline power that he had experienced in the Sinha Blood Array.

A hint of panic began to rise up in his heart.

He was unable to use any immortal spiritual power in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so if his entire body were to crystallize, then that would be the end of him.

He had thought that this outpouring of starpower from the Heaven Controlling Vial was a massive blessing, but it was quickly turning into a catastrophic nightmare.

Han Li gritted his teeth tightly, and he knew that he had to do something drastic in order to save himself. Hence, he completely went against the cultivation method laid out in the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, directing the starpower in his body toward five profound acupoints at once.

Opening profound acupoints required extreme concentration, and even the slightest lapse in concentration could result in catastrophic consequences, but given the dire nature of his situation, Han Li had no choice but to resort to such desperate measures.

Opening several profound acupoints at once instantly significantly increased starpower expenditure, and as a result, the rate of crystallization of Han Li's body began to slow, but it didn't fade.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, both to cultivate and to save his own life.

Over a month flew by in a flash.

Perhaps this was arranged by Chen Yang, but during this time, no one came to instruct Han Li to take part in any battles in the arena.

His body was still in a half-crystallized state, while five specks of starlight were flickering on his chest.

A faint thud rang out as one of the profound acupoints was abruptly opened, while the other four weren't far away.

However, this didn't bring Han Li any elation as the starpower surging out of the Heaven Controlling Vial was only growing more and more abundant.

Just how much starpower is in this damn thing?! he cursed internally, then immediately refocused his efforts on funneling the starpower from the Heaven Controlling Vial toward a new profound acupoint.

On top of that, he began opening six profound acupoints at once instead of five.

Opening five at a time was already quite a strain on him, and he didn't know if increasing that number to six would cause any problems, but at this point, he had no choice.

If the rate of outflow of starpower from the Heaven Controlling Vial continued to increase, then perhaps this number would also have to rise further.

He took a deep breath as all of the profound acupoints on his body began to glow brightly, basking his entire body in a bright cloud of starlight.

Five years flew by in the blink of an eye.

Han Li's entire body was encompassed within a cloud of incandescent starlight, making it impossible to see what was happening inside.

Right at this moment, all of the starlight around him suddenly began flashing erratically before abruptly dissipating, and a string of loud booms rang out within the stone chamber, while the entire room trembled and quivered.

Han Li slowly stood up amid the dissipating starlight, and at this point, his body had already returned to normal.

However, at this moment, there were as many as two hundred and thirty-seven profound acupoints shimmering all over his body.

It had taken him five years to finally use up all of the starpower in the Heaven Controlling Vial, and he had opened a hundred and sixty-five new profound acupoints, mastering the first level of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

An elated look appeared on his face as he examined all of the profound acupoints on his own body. Even though the process had been extremely perilous, the reward was tremendous, and it was worth the years of arduous cultivation up to this point.

He heaved a long sigh as the starlight radiating from his body faded away, and a wave of exhaustion instantly washed over him.

Over the past five years, he had cultivated the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts without rest in a state of high focus and concentration, and he had accumulated far too much fatigue, both mentally and physically.

With that in mind, he fell onto his bed and instantly fell into a deep sleep.

Chapter 892: Five City Martial Gathering

Han Li slept for what felt like an eternity, and by the time he woke up, all of his exhaustion had faded away.

He felt as if his own body were brimming with limitless power, and his mind was also filled with ferocious battle intent that made him want to plow through a mountain with his bare hands.

He was naturally able to suppress these irrational urges, but the battle intent in his heart was so fierce that it proved rather difficult for him to suppress.

"Looks like having too much energy is not a good thing," Han Li mused in a self-deprecating fashion, then began carefully examining his own internal condition.

All of his two hundred and thirty-seven profound acupoints were glowing radiantly, while bursts of immense power were surging through his entire body, and his battle intent was beginning to rise up once again.

I never used to be this aggressive. Could this be a result of cultivating the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts?

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he raised a hand before slashing it through the air like a blade, and a loud screeching sound instantly rang out as the space began to shimmer and warp.

His eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this. Prior to cultivating the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, he wouldn't have been able to achieve the same effect even with an all out attack, yet he was now able to do it with just an errant swipe of his hand.

A gust of ferocious wind swept through the air from his hand before striking the wall, instantly slicing a long and deep gash into it as if it were made of tofu.

A stunned smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he realized that the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts were even more formidable than he anticipated.

Right as he was about to conduct some more tests of his own newfound power, the sound of door-knocking suddenly rang out.

He rose to his feet before opening the door to discover Chen Yang standing outside.

"I was informed that there had been some commotion in your room a few days ago, so I thought that you may have come out of seclusion. Looks like I was right. You were certainly in seclusion for a very long time, Fellow Daoist Li," Chen Yang said with a hint of complaint in his voice.

"Please come in, City Lord Chen," Han Li said as he invited Chen Yang into his room.

"Just call me Chen Yang, Fellow Daoist Li. Looks like you've made significant strides in your cultivation over the past five years," Chen Yang remarked.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Chen. My paltry powers can't even begin to compare with yours," Han Li replied in a modest fashion.

Chen Yang smiled in response, but his smile was a little stiff.

At this moment, he felt as if Han Li were enshrouded in a layer of figurative mist, making it impossible to glean the full depths of his power.

But how was that possible? No more than five years ago, he was nothing more than a piece of small fry who had only opened seventy-two profound acupoints. Could it be that he had been hiding his true power this entire time?

"What brings you here today, Fellow Daoist Chen? Could it be that you've found a way to remove the Black Tribulation Centipede in my body?" Han Li asked.

"My sincerest apologies, but even after searching through all of the potential places where Du Qingyang could've kept things hidden over the past few years, I still wasn't able to find anything. I'm afraid I'll have to ask you to raise a different request to me," Chen Yang replied with a wry smile.

Even though Han Li had already anticipated this answer, his expression still darkened slightly as he said, "Alright, we can discuss this matter another time then. If you're not here to discuss the matter of the Black Tribulation Centipedes, then why have you come to see me?"

"The Five City Martial Gathering is coming up, and that's what I wanted to discuss with you," Chen Yang replied with a smile.

"What's that?" Han Li asked.

Aside from its main city, Profound City also had four subsidiary cities, namely Green Goat City, Excess Passage City, Profound End City, and White Rock City.

However, he had never heard of this Five City Martial Gathering before.

"The five cities of our Profound City are situated quite far away from one another, thereby making exchange of information extremely difficult. In order to strengthen the connection between the five cities, City Lord E Kuai holds a martial gathering once every one thousand years in the main city, where the five cities will send out their most powerful warriors to engage in a series of sparring matches," Chen Yang explained with a smile.

"I see. Why have you brought this up to me, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Han Li asked as he thought back to his last conversation with Daoist Xie.

Could the important event that Daoist Xie had been referring to be this Five City Martial Gathering?

"The Five City Martial Gathering is a grand event for Profound City. Would you be interested in going to take a look?" Chen Yang asked.

"Are you really just inviting me to go and spectate the event? Please get to the point, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li harrumphed.

Chen Yang remained unbothered by Han Li's rather frosty demeanor, and a serious look appeared on his face as he said, "In that case, I won't waste any more time. I came here today to invite you to participate in this martial gathering as a representative of our Green Goat City."

Han Li wasn't surprised to hear this, and he asked, "What are the rules of this Five City Martial Gathering?"

The fact that Han Li didn't turn down this proposal right away was a very encouraging sign for Chen Yang, and he hurriedly explained, "The rules have always been slightly different from one edition to another, but in general, it's always a one on one battle, where the winner advances, and those who manage to clinch the top spots in the event will receive handsome rewards from City Lord E Kuai himself."

"Will participating in the event pose any risk to my life?" Han Li asked.

"There will be some risk, but there have been very few casualties in past editions. They're meant to be sparring matches, so you can surrender if you're defeated. There aren't any vendettas between the cities, so very few people will intentionally try to kill their opponents. After all, the true enemy of Profound City is Puppet City," Chen Yang replied.

Having spent so much time in the arena, Han Li had almost forgotten about the existence of Puppet City.

"I'm sure such a grand event isn't held purely to strengthen the relations between the cities, right?" Han Li asked.

Chen Yang's smile stiffened slightly upon hearing this, following which he replied, "That's only the secondary objective. The most important objective of the event is to decide the cultivation resource allocation among the cities based on the outcome of the martial gathering."

Han Li merely smiled as he looked at Chen Yang in silence.

A sense of unease welled up in Chen Yang's heart at the sight of Han Li's expression, and he said, "I'll be open and honest with you, Fellow Daoist Li. I've only just taken over as the lord of Green Goat City, so our city must do well in this martial gathering in order for me to establish myself. If you're willing to help me in this cause, I won't take any of the reward that you receive from the event, and I'll even give you additional compensation on top of that."

"Oh? What do you plan to give me as compensation?" Han Li asked.

Chen Yang was rather taken aback by Han Li's direct and straightforward line of questioning, and he pulled out a white jade box before offering it to him.

Han Li accepted the box, then opened it up a sliver to inspect its contents, upon which a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes.

He then immediately closed the box again as he smiled and said, "Seeing as you're displaying so much sincerity, it would be downright rude of me to refuse."

Internally, Chen Yang was feeling quite disgruntled, but on the surface, he displayed a grateful smile as he said, "The Five City Martial Gathering isn't far away, and Green Goat City is quite far from Profound City, so I'm planning for us to set off in half a year. If you need to make any preparations, please do so as soon as possible, and I'm happy to provide you with any assistance that you may require."

Han Li nodded in response, and Chen Yang promptly departed.

Following Chen Yang's departure, Han Li sat back down with his legs crossed on his bed, then opened the jade box in his hands to reveal an A tier beast core.

This one was quite lackluster compared with the one that he had chosen from Du Qingyang's vault, but it was undoubtedly also an A tier beast core.

A faint smile appeared on his face as he closed the jade box, then closed his eyes as well.

With only a half a year left to prepare, there was no point in cultivating, so he was planning to make some other preparations.

Opening so many profound acupoints in such a short time was simply unheard of, so he had to take some measures to conceal his newly opened profound acupoints.

……

Six months flew by in a flash.

On this day, Han Li changed into his normal attire before leaving the arena.

He was able to leave the arena without any trouble, presumably because Chen Yang had already informed everyone in the arena to grant him free passage, and he quickly arrived in the main hall of the city lord's manor.

There were already quite a few people gathered in the hall, almost all of which he was familiar with.

All of the arena's area leaders were present, and in addition to them, there were also the likes of Xiong Pei and Xuanyuan Xing, amounting to a total of close to twenty people.

Everyone was looking quite excited, particularly the area leaders, who were spiritedly discussing the upcoming Five City Martial Gathering.

Everyone in the hall took a casual glance at Han Li upon his arrival, then returned to their conversations.

Han Li had earned quite a reputation for himself in the arena, but in the eyes of the area leaders, he was still not worthy of their attention.

His and Gu Qianxun's involvement in the death of Du Qingyang had been kept a secret this entire time, so no one was aware of the role that he had played.

Han Li didn't mind this at all, and he sat down in a peaceful corner of the hall.

At this moment, Gu Qianxun was seated together with Toxic Dragon, Tu Gang, and a golden-haired young man, as well as the purple-robed woman by the name of Yao Li.

Gu Qianxun's eyes lit up slightly at the sight of Han Li, and she excused herself before making her way toward him.

Yao Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but she still followed along.

"Who's that?" the golden-haired young man asked as a cold gleam flashed through his eyes.

He was quite a handsome man, and his aura was even more formidable than that of Toxic Dragon and Tu Gang.

Chapter 893: Traveling to Profound City

"You've been in seclusion all this time, so you won't have heard of him, Brother Yi. His name is Li Feiyu, and he only recently joined the arena a few years ago. Even though he's only opened fewer than fifty profound acupoints, he's quite a strong fighter and has even defeated Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon in the past.

“On top of that, he's a human, so he's earned quite a reputation for himself. However, it seems like he was granted some special privileges starting from five years ago, allowing him to remain in seclusion the entire time, and it appears that he's only just come out," Tu Gang said.

"Do you have to bring that up again? I only lost to him that one time because I was too complacent!" Toxic Dragon harrumphed coldly.

"A human? That's certainly not something that you see every day. Is he planning to take part in the martial gathering as well?" the golden-haired young man asked with a derisive sneer.

"Perhaps. Otherwise, why would he have gone into seclusion for all these years? Tu Gang mused."

As soon as Han Li sat down, he was immediately offered a cup of tea by a maidservant, and accepted the teacup before taking a sip.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Li," Gu Qianxun greeted as she approached Han Li with a smile on her face.

Yao Li was walking along beside her, displaying her usual disdainful expression to Han Li.

"Indeed, long time no see, Fellow Daoist Gu," Han Li replied, paying no heed to Yao Li.

"I knew that with your powers, Fellow Daoist Chen would definitely invite you. I've heard that you've been cultivating in seclusion these past five years, and I can see that you've made some significant strides in your cultivation," Gu Qianxun remarked.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Gu. I can see that you've also made an important breakthrough. Congratulations," Han Li said with a smile, and Gu Qianxun's smile stiffened slightly upon hearing this.

She had indeed broken through a bottleneck using the two treasures that she had taken from Du Qingyang's vault, but she had never mentioned this to anyone and had tried to keep this a secret this entire time, yet Han Li was able to see through her right away!

Unbeknownst to her, Han Li's senses had become far sharper thanks to the rapid progress that he had made in his own bodily cultivation, and that, coupled with his tremendous spiritual sense, was what had allowed him to see right through Gu Qianxun at a single glance.

Gu Qianxun regained her composure as she sat down beside Han Li and remarked, "What a pair of sharp eyes you possess, Fellow Daoist Li."

The golden-haired young man's expression darkened significantly upon seeing this.

"Let's stop exchanging pointless praise, Fellow Daoist Gu. You've been in Green Goat City far longer than I have, so I'm sure you know more about the Five City Martial Gathering than I do. Would you be able to tell me about it?" Han Li asked with a smile.

Gu Qianxun was just about to reply when Chen Yang entered the hall in his city lord attire, then sat down onto the main chair as he said, "Sorry to keep you all waiting, everyone."

As usual, Daoist Xie was trailing along silently behind him.

Han Li cast his gaze toward Daoist Xie, but the latter paid no heed to him, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"We pay our respects to City Lord Chen!" everyone collectively greeted as they rose to their feet before extending respectful salutes.

"No need for such formalities. All of you are pillars of our Green Goat City, so I'll be counting on you for the upcoming martial gathering. Take a seat, everyone," Chen Yang said with a smile.

Everyone sat back down, and the entire hall descended into complete silence.

"I'm sure all of you are aware of why I have gathered you here today. The Five City Martial Gathering is coming up soon, and it'll take us quite some time to get to Profound City, so we'll be setting off shortly. However, before that, there are some things that I must discuss with all of you," Chen Yang declared.

"Has there been some change to the martial gathering, City Lord Chen?" the golden-haired young man asked.

"Who's that?" Han Li asked as he took a glance at the golden-haired young man.

"He's Yi Liya. He's been in seclusion for quite a few years, so you won't have seen him before," Gu Qianxun replied.

Yi Liya was a name that Han Li was quite familiar with. He was the leader of the arena's second area, and he was widely recognized as the second-most powerful arena gladiator behind only Gu Qianxun.

"There's been no change, but I've been informed that City Lord E Kuai is taking this martial gathering very seriously and is offering unprecedentedly handsome rewards, so this will perhaps be the most hotly contested martial gathering we've ever had," Chen Yang declared with a smile.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this. Was there a reason why City Lord E Kuai was taking this particular martial gathering so seriously?

"Our Green Goat City must present itself in a good light to the other four cities, so please give it your all and make our city proud!" Chen Yang implored in a serious voice.

"Rest assured, City Lord Chen, we'll be sure to do our Green Goat City proud!"

"We're going to show the other cities exactly what we're made of!"

A wide smile appeared on Chen Yang's face upon hearing this, and he declared, "Thank you, everyone. Now, let's prepare for departure."

With that, everyone made their way out of the hall and quickly arrived outside Green Goat City.

It was a bright and sunny day, but very windy, as usual. Yellow sand was sweeping through the air as far as the eyes could see, and at this moment, there were close to twenty enormous scaled beasts waiting outside with saddles on their backs.

Chen Yang made his way onto the back of the Black Scaled Elephant at the forefront of the group, and Daoist Xie got on with him.

There were quite a few scaled beasts to choose from, and some people were choosing to travel together on the same beast, so there was a surplus.

Han Li was just about to make his way onto the back of a vacant horse-like scaled beast when Chen Yang suddenly turned to him and offered, "If you don't mind, you can ride with me, Fellow Daoist Li."

Han Li took a glance at Daoist Xie, then smiled as he replied, "That would be my honor."

After that, he sprang up into the air and drifted down onto the Black Scaled Elephant's back.

"Why don't you join us as well, Fellow Daoist Gu? It's going to be a long trip, wouldn't it be nice to have some company?" Chen Yang invited.

"I suppose it couldn't hurt," Gu Qianxun replied with a smile, then leaped onto the elephant's back as well.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the Black Scaled Elephant set off, while Yi Liya was looking on with a displeased expression from the ground below.

He gave a cold harrumphed before leaping onto the back of a deer-like scaled beast, and it didn't take long before the entire line of scaled beasts had vanished into the distance.

……

Over two years flew by in a flash.

An enormous mountain range that resembled a resting giant had appeared on the horizon at the end of a dusty plain.

Close to a hundred kilometers away from the mountain range was a procession of around a dozen scaled beasts, and on the back of the Black Scaled Elephant at the forefront of the procession sat none other than Han Li, Chen Yang, and Gu Qianxun.

At this moment, Han Li was peering at his surroundings through narrowed eyes, and as he cast his gaze toward the mountain range up ahead, he spotted a large city concealed within the mountain range's shadow.

"That city up ahead is Profound City, right, City Lord Chen?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. This mountain range is called the Myriad Profound Mountain Range, and Profound City was built into one side of the mountain range, shielding it from the elements while also making it easier to defend. Our Green Goat City was constructed on the same principles, but the scales of the two cities are downright incomparable," Chen Yang confirmed with a smile.

"I'm sure Green Goat City will soar to greater heights under your leadership, City Lord Chen. I wouldn't dare to proclaim that it could outstrip Profound City someday, but I certainly look forward to the day that it rises to the top among the four subsidiary cities," Gu Qianxun said with a smile of her own.

"I certainly hope such a day will come," Chen Yang replied with a pleased expression.

Before long, the procession of scaled beasts arrived at the foot of the city.

Up close, the city was even more grand and majestic in appearance.

The city walls were constructed from a black stone material with large white scaled beast star bones embedded into them, giving off a faint white glow.

Han Li knew that these star bones weren't just there for decorative purposes. Instead, the starpower that they contained could enhance the city's defenses, and this feat of construction alone was already something that was out of reach for Green Goat City.

The city had a total of three gates, the central one of which was several hundred feet tall, while the other two gates on either side of it were slightly shorter.

Even though all three gates were open, no one was passing through the central one, and only some people were occasionally making their way in and out of the two side gates.

Chen Yang led Han Li and the others to the main gate, then displayed his token to verify his identity as the lord of Green Goat City, upon which he was immediately approached by a black-robed young man.

"Welcome, City Lord Chen. Please forgive me for not coming out to greet you sooner. My name is Tong Song, and I'll be guiding you and your entourage to the city lord's manor," the young man said.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Tong. May I ask if the people from the other three cities have already arrived?" Chen Yang asked.

"The guests from the other three cities have already arrived, so once I've taken you to the city lord's manor, City Lord E Kuai will meet with all of you," Tong Song replied.

"Sorry to keep everyone waiting," Chen Yang said.

"You've arrived in a timely fashion, so there's no need to apologize, City Lord Chen," Tong Song hurriedly replied with a wave of his hands.

"Alright, please take us to the city lord's manor, Fellow Daoist Tong," Chen Yang said with a nod.

Tong Song gave an affirmative response, then sent one of his subordinates to go ahead and report Chen Yang's arrival to the city lord's manor before leading everyone from Green Goat City into Profound City through the main gate.

Chapter 894: Pretty Boy

Yi Liya's brows were tightly furrowed as he watched Han Li, Gu Qianxun, and Chen Yang walking along at the forefront, seemingly on very good terms with one another.

He had nothing to say about Chen Yang taking Du Qingyang's place as the city lord. Even though he was in seclusion during Chen Yang's rise to the top, it was clear to him what had to have happened, and the fact that Chen Yang was able to eliminate Du Qingyang clearly indicated that he was not to be messed with.

When it came to Gu Qianxun, he also had a great deal of respect for her. After all, it was undeniable that her powers were superior to his, and he had been defeated in all of the battles that had taken place between them up to this point.

However, Li Feiyu was someone that he had never heard of before, and he appeared to be quite weak, yet it was clear that he was on very good terms with the other two.

He had asked Tu Gang and Sun Binghe about this, but they weren't able to answer his questions about Han Li, either.

Han Li was completely oblivious to Yi Liya's scrutiny, and he began inspecting his surroundings as soon as he entered the city.

The layout of the city was very orderly and well-organized. All of the buildings were constructed from the same black stone material as the city walls, and even though they were all quite simplistic and monotonous in style, it was still quite a rare sight in a barren secret area like the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

The streets in the city were very wide, allowing even large scaled beasts to pass through with no problems, and they were also lined with shops.

Perhaps it was because it was close to nighttime, but there weren't many pedestrians on the streets in the city, so it was quite serene, with the peace only occasionally punctuated by a beastly roar or two.

As they were about to reach the center of the city, Han Li's eyes suddenly narrowed slightly as he spotted a rather interesting building.

It was an enormous round building with many black stone pillars standing around it, and its walls were packed with scaled beast star bones to an even higher degree of density than the city walls.

Outside the building was a spacious plaza, atop which stood a humanoid stone statue with blurry facial features that was hundreds of feet tall.

Han Li had seen a statue that was virtually identical to this one in Green Goat City, albeit quite a bit smaller, and he had asked Chen Yang about its origins, to which Chen Yang had replied that he didn't know.

After passing by this giant round building, it didn't take long before the group arrived at the city lord's manor.

The city lord's manors of Profound City and Green Goat City could hardly even be compared with one another.

Even though there was no vegetation around the city lord's manor of Profound City, it had been constructed like a beautiful garden.

All of the paths in the manor were paved with giant bluestone slabs, and these paths were lined with black statues depicting different humanoid and beastly figures, as well as some half-human, half-beast deities.

Littered around the paths were some stone palaces with all types of ornate designs engraved upon them, and they were already very similar in style to the palaces that Han Li had seen in the Devil Realm.

Han Li's group was led by Tong Song to a massive stone hall, where Tong Song smiled and said, "Please take a rest in here, City Lord Chen. City Lord E Kuai has already been informed of your arrival, and he'll be seeing you shortly."

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Tong," Chen Yang said.

Tong Song responded with a polite smile, then made an inviting hand gesture, and Chen Yang entered the hall with his entourage.

Inside the hall was a massive rectangular stone table that extended all the way from the wall at the very back of the hall.

The main seat in the hall, a wide and sturdy chair, remained unoccupied, while around a dozen other seats at the table were already occupied, and all of their occupants were currently chatting boisterously with one another.

Han Li swept his gaze over the people already present to discover that their leader seemed to be a short and stocky middle-aged man with a muscular physique. He was dressed in a thick beast hide cape, and he was currently resting with his eyes closed.

Right next to him was another brawny man with most of his body covered in a layer of pristine white bandages, leaving only half of his dark-skinned face exposed, and there was a hint of cold bloodlust in his only visible eye.

What was rather strange was that his bandaged arm was extraordinarily long and muscular, almost trailing all the way down onto the ground, while his unbandaged arm appeared much more normal in comparison.

As Han Li was observing these people, they also noticed the arrival of Chen Yang and his entourage, and the chatter instantly died down as they turned their attention to Han Li and the others.

"Long time no see, City Lord Fu, Fellow Daoist Duan," Chen Yang greeted with a smile.

The bandaged man merely took a glance at Chen Yang before giving a cold harrumph, while the muscular middle-aged man didn't even open his eyes, choosing to ignore Chen Yang altogether.

Chen Yang was completely unbothered by this, and he was just about to sit down across from the muscular middle-aged man and the others when the sound of a violent coughing fit suddenly rang out from outside the hall, following which a tall and thin middle-aged man with a sickle pale complexion made his way into the room.

Han Li noticed that he had a layer of gray scales growing near his throat, which would rustle slightly every time he coughed.

While Han Li was observing the man's throat, a figure suddenly shot out from behind him, abruptly appearing in front of Han Li as if by instantaneous teleportation before piercing a sword that was as thin as a willow leaf straight at Han Li's right eye.

Han Li reacted extremely quickly, raising his two fingers in which his Flower Branch domain had been refined to catch the tip of the sword.

The sword shuddered slightly before being withdrawn, and it was revealed that its wielder was an extremely handsome white-robed young man with a set of gentle and effeminate features, giving him a rather gender-neutral appearance.

"Keep staring at my father like that and I'll gouge your eyes out!" the young man threatened, and his voice was quite tender, further adding to his gender ambiguity.

"Come back, Wuchen. Why get so worked up over a lowly slave?" the pale-faced man said in an indifferent manner.

The white-robed young man immediately retreated respectfully to the pale-faced man's side, but he was still glowering at Han Li with a hostile look in his eyes.

"You've made yourself quite a troublesome enemy right off the bat, Fellow Daoist Li. You're going to have to be careful if you encounter him in the arena," Gu Qianxun remarked through voice transmission.

"Why do you say that?" Han Li asked.

"This man's name is Feng Wuchen, and he's the most powerful subordinate under Qin Yuan, the lord of Profound End City. His cultivation arts are focused primarily on the profound acupoints of his legs, granting him incredible speed and agility, and his willow leaf sword is also a perfect weapon for an assassin," Gu Qianxun introduced.

Han Li remained unfazed as he asked, "Who's the guy in the bandages?"

"His name is Duan Tong, and his cultivation arts place a heavy emphasis on the cultivation of his right arm. That's why his right arm is so disproportionately huge. The last time I saw him, his skin wasn't this dark, and he wasn't wearing these bandages, either," Gu Qianxun replied.

"In that case, he must've cultivated some other powerful abilities since you last met him," Han Li replied.

"He was once the number one subordinate under Fu Jian, the lord of Excess Passage City, but he seemed to have been stripped of that title after being defeated by me during the last martial gathering. It appears that he's back for revenge this time," Gu Qianxun mused.

While the two were conversing with each other, Qin Yuan had already led his entourage to sit down across from Fu Jian and the others, so Chen Yang could take a seat further down the table next to them.

Right at this moment, Fu Jian slowly opened his eyes as he scoffed, "To think that a traitorous scoundrel like yourself would dare to come here and take part in the Five City Martial Gathering. Are you aware of how the word 'shame' is spelt?"

All of his subordinates immediately burst into raucous laughter upon hearing this.

Chen Yang remained completely unbothered as he countered, "Oh? It sounds like you're very knowledgeable on this subject. Why don't you write down the word for me on a piece of rock or beast bone, and I'll make it a prized piece of my calligraphy collection."

Qin Yuan leaned back in his chair, resting his feet on the table in front of him as he mused, "During the last martial gathering, I warned Du Qingyang to be careful of you. I could see that you had a rebellious bone in you, but it seems like he didn't heed my advice."

"Maybe you should worry more about your own Profound End City rather than concerning yourself with the affairs of our Green Goat City. Your advice was taken onboard by Du Qingyang, but his tyrannical ways had already sparked much dissatisfaction among his subordinates, so my ascension to the top was as welcome as it was necessary," Chen Yang replied with a smile.

This was a blatant lie, yet Chen Yang was telling it without even skipping a beat, much to Han Li's amusement and dismay.

"What's the point in all of this bickering? The group that Du Qingyang brought with him last time at least looked half decent, what's this assortment of trash that you've brought with you last time? Ah, forgive me, I didn't mean to lump in Fellow Daoist Gu with the rest, of course," Fu Jian sneered.

The expressions of Toxic Dragon and the others darkened significantly upon hearing this, but in the face of an almighty city lord, they could only suffer in silence.

"If I'm not mistaken, that little pretty boy among you seems to be a human, right?" Qin Yuan asked as his gaze settled onto Han Li.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he turned to Qin Yuan as he replied, "I am indeed a human, but as for the term 'pretty boy', I think that would be much more appropriately used on your son... No, daughter? That doesn't seem right, either..."

Everyone present faltered slightly upon hearing this, and it seemed that many people were very surprised by his decision to provoke Qin Yuan and Feng Wuchen.

Due to some special reasons, Qin Yuan always had a very sickly appearance, but no one ever dared to mock him for it as his powers and status both commanded a great deal of respect.

Gu Qianxun's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, while a cold sneer appeared on Yi Liya's face.

Before Qin Yuan had a chance to say anything, a furious look appeared on Feng Wuchen's face as he yelled, "How dare you! A worthless piece of scum like yourself should know to keep his mouth shut when the city lords are talking!"

Chapter 895: Unrest

"City Lord Qin just directed a question at this subordinate of mine, did he not? Is he wrong for answering? You're the one who should learn to keep your mouth shut unless you're spoken to!" Chen Yang countered as he gave Feng Wuchen a cold glare.

Feng Wuchen was even more infuriated upon hearing this, yet before he had a chance to say anything else, Qin Yuan raised a hand to silence him as he chuckled, "Stand down, Wuchen. Don't be rude. This subordinate of yours appears to have just as sharp a tongue as yours, City Lord Chen."

"Likewise," Chen Yang replied with a faint smile.

This entire time, Han Li's expression remained completely unchanged, but Feng Wuchen was glowering at him with intense killing intent in his eyes.

"It's disgusting that an honorless scoundrel like you dares to sit at the same table with us! Do you really think we wouldn't dare to kill you right here, right now?" Fu Jian suddenly roared in a furious voice.

"It seems like you don't like me very much, City Lord Fu. If you want to kill me, then come and give it a try," Chen Yang replied, completely unfazed by Fu Jian's threats.

All of the people from Green Goat City immediately rose to their feet to support him, while Fu Jian's subordinates stood up as well.

Qin Yuan didn't say anything, but he erupted into another violent coughing fit, while Feng Wuchen and the others all turned to the Green Goat City representatives with hostile looks of their own.

The atmosphere in the hall had suddenly become extremely tense, and a spark was all that was required for a full-blown scuffle to ensue.

Right at this moment, a rather peculiar voice rang out from outside the hall.

"Sorry to keep you all waiting, everyone. Let's all settle down now."

A rotund gray-robed elderly man with a coarse beard made his way into the hall, then smiled as he continued, "All of us belong to Profound City, so we should be assisting one another rather than fighting among ourselves. Leave the fighting for when the martial gathering commences."

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Sun," Chen Yang greeted with a smile.

"Congratulations, City Lord Chen Yang," the gray-robed elderly man said as he extended a congratulatory salute, following which he and his entourage sat down across from Han Li and the others.

Up to this point, he was the only one of the three other city lords that was displaying any semblance of friendliness toward Chen Yang.

"This must be City Lord Sun Tu of White Rock City, right?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"That's right," Gu Qianxun replied. "He may look like a very benevolent and easygoing man, but his city is actually the most powerful one out of the four subsidiary cities. You see that man with the pig face behind him?"

Han Li looked past Sun Tu to discover a short and ugly young man standing behind him. Instead of sitting down, the young man was standing directly behind Sun Tu.

It was a bit of an exaggeration to say that he had the face of a pig, but he did have a pair of slightly upturned nostrils, and he had quite a round face, both of which made him slightly resemble a pig.

There was quite a large gap between his eyes, giving him a rather dazed appearance, and he was holding a greasy roasted scaled beast leg that he was gnawing on while also scrutinizing with his undivided attention.

"I see him. Is there something special about him?" Han Li asked.

"His name is Fang Chan. He may look harmless and perhaps even a little dumb, but as soon as he goes into battle, he immediately becomes a completely different person. Somehow, he's able to unleash an extremely special soundwave attack with his mouth and nose, and anyone that falls prey to that attack will go completely numb and powerless. I have first hand experience with that myself," Gu Qianxun introduced.

Han Li took another glance at Fang Chan as he committed what he had just been told to memory.

With Sun Tu stepping in as mediator, Chen Yang was naturally more than happy to de-escalate the conflict, and he sat down along with everyone else from Green Goat City.

Fu Jian and Qin Yuan exchanged a glance with each other before sitting down as well.

"When did you two arrive at Profound City?" Sun Tu asked as he turned to Fu Jian and Qin Yuan.

"Just two days ago," Qin Yuan replied with a smile.

"I arrived a few days earlier than him," Fu Jian replied as he closed his eyes again.

"I was delayed by some matters, so I only just arrived yesterday. Come to think of it, it's been a very long time since we last saw each other," Sun Tu said with a smile.

"Indeed, the last time we met was during the previous Five City Martial Gathering. Never did I think that that would be the last time I would ever see Fellow Daoist Du," Qin Yuan sighed.

"It was simply meant to be. Fellow Daoist Chen was able to climb to his current position thanks to his merits, so there's no need to feel sad for Fellow Daoist Du," Sun Tu said.

While the two of them were chatting with each other, the sound of heavy footsteps rang out from outside the hall, following which an ordinary-looking middle-aged man strode over the doorstep, accompanied by a man and a woman, both of whom were clad in suits of bone armor.

The man looked no different from the average farmer, and one could easily miss him in a crowd.

In contrast, the two armorclad figures behind him were both quite stunning in appearance, and their suits of bone armor also had extremely intricate and beautiful patterns engraved upon them.

Their accompaniment made the middle-aged man appear rather remarkable, and one couldn't help but guess at his identity.

As soon as the three of them entered the hall, all four of the city lords in the hall instantly rose to their feet, followed immediately by their entourages.

This reaction from everyone immediately tipped Han Li off to the middle-aged man's identity, and he hurriedly stood up as well.

"We pay our respects to City Lord E Kuai," everyone greeted in unison.

Han Li took a glance at Gu Qianxun, and he noticed that the latter's gaze was fixed on the handsome armorclad man standing behind E Kuai.

"You seem very interested in that man, Fellow Daoist Gu. Do you have feelings for him, or is there some bad blood between the two of you?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

Gu Qianxun paid no heed to his jibe as she replied, "His name is Zhu Ziyuan, and he's using a strange ancient bodily refinement cultivation art that grants him unfathomable power. He's already come out on top in several past consecutive editions of the Five City Martial Gathering leading up to this one, yet I can tell that he's still yet to unleash his full power in any of his battles. You and I should pray that we don't get matched up against him."

E Kuai strode over to the main seat in the hall, and a warm smile appeared on his face as he gestured for everyone to sit down, but no one dared to oblige.

A resigned smile appeared on E Kaui's face, and only after he had taken a seat did everyone finally dare to sit down again.

"Welcome, fellow daoists. My apologies for not staging a more elaborate welcome for you all," E Kuai said, displaying no intentions of discussing the altercation that had just taken place in the hall.

"Not at all, City Lord E Kuai. Being in your presence alone is already more than enough of an elaborate welcome for us all," Sun Tu hurriedly said.

"The Five City Martial Gathering has always been a grand event for our five cities, and it's also an opportunity for the cities to display their powers and strengthen their bonds with one another, so I always look forward to this occasion," E Kuai said with a smile.

Everyone nodded in agreement.

"I can see that there are many new faces among you. That's a very encouraging sight. If there are too many old faces around, then that indicates that there's a dearth of talent beneath them, so I enjoy seeing new faces whenever the Five City Martial Gathering comes around," E Kuai said with a pleased smile, and his gaze lingered momentarily on Chen Yang and the others as he spoke.

Qin Yuan and Fu Jian's expressions remained unchanged, but internally, they were feeling quite disgruntled.

Wasn't E Kuai essentially encouraging Chen Yang's actions by saying something like this? Didn't this mean that if others wanted to take their place, then they would also be endorsed and supported by E Kuai himself?

Of course, they didn't dare to display any displeasure despite what they were thinking. E Kuai was by far the most powerful figure in Profound City, and no one dared to get on his bad side.

"Puppet City has been growing from strength to strength of late. Even though they haven't made any major moves against us, they're already beginning to gain the upper hand in some of the recent minor conflicts that have taken place between our two cities, so we have to be careful," E Kuai suddenly sighed.

"Indeed, City Lord E Kuai. The subsidiary city of Puppet City, Black Frost City, has been frequently making moves against our Excess Passage City of late. They've been sending hunting parties into our territory to hunt scaled beasts, and even though they've always retreated upon confrontation, it still makes me feel quite uneasy that they're testing the waters like this," Fu Jian said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"We're in a similar situation as well. In fact, there have even been a few minor conflicts on our end, but we've managed to come out on top every single time," Sun Tu said with a pleased expression.

"Our Profound End City is quite far away from Puppet City, so things have been relatively more peaceful for us. However, we have caught some spies trying to infiltrate our cities, and prior to coming here, I had to take care of quite a powerful gladiator myself. He had been lurking in our arena for thousands of years, and he only revealed his trump card puppetry abilities after I had backed him into a corner," Qin Yuan said.

"It looks like there's some unrest brewing on the horizon," Sun Tu sighed. "Speaking of which, there's been a major change in Green Goat City of late, so it could be vulnerable to infiltration. Make sure to be on your guard, City Lord Chen Yang."

Chapter 896: Visiting Mistress Liu Hua

"Rest assured, City Lord E Kuai, our Green Goat City has never let our guard down against Puppet City, whether it be now or in the past," Chen Yang assured as he turned to E Kuai with a cupped fist salute.

"It's fine, I only mentioned this matter as it had suddenly sprung into my mind. Let's get back on track and talk about the Five City Martial Gathering," E Kuai replied with a wave of his hand, and everyone fell silent upon hearing this, waiting for him to continue.

"The rules will be much the same compared with past editions. Each of your four cities will nominate twelve people to take part in the martial gathering, while our main city will send out sixteen people for a total of sixty-four. It'll be a single elimination format consisting solely of one-on-one matches, and anyone who makes it into the top three will receive a reward.

“On top of that, the one who claims the top spot will receive an unprecedentedly massive reward," E Kuai continued with a smile.

"What exactly is this reward, City Lord E Kuai? You've been dangling this in front of us for quite some time," Qin Yuan chuckled.

"There are still three months left until the official commencement of the martial gathering, and all will be revealed then. I promise you that you won't be disappointed," E Kuai replied as his smile grew even more pronounced.

No one raised any objections to this.

"In the meantime, all of you will be arranged places to stay, and if you want to get in some match practice during these three months, then you can travel to the arenas in the city to participate in some arena battles," E Kuai said.

After that, everyone chatted for a while longer before they were dismissed.

Following that brief meeting, everyone had certain things on their mind, so they were no longer interested in jousting with one another, and Qin Yuan and Fu Jian promptly departed with their entourages.

Chen Yang and the others were the last to leave the hall, and Tong Song was still waiting for him outside.

"Esteemed guests of Green Goat City, would you like to explore the city or be taken to the courtyard where you'll be staying?" Tong Song asked.

"We're all rather weary from the trip to get here, so please take us to the courtyard first, Fellow Daoist Tong," Chen Yang replied.

"Alright, then please come with me."

Under Tong Song's guidance, everyone left the city lord's manor before traveling west until they arrived at a cluster of buildings that was even more massive than the city lord's manor.

"My sincerest apologies, but the people from the other three cities have already chosen the courtyards with superior locations and environments as they arrived before you. The two remaining courtyards are still quite nice to stay in, but the residences are spread rather far apart, so it may be a little inconvenient for all of you," Tong Song said in an apologetic manner.

Chen Yang's mind was clearly elsewhere, and he replied in a slightly distracted manner, "That's fine. It'll be more peaceful for everyone with the residences more spaced out."

Tong Song thanked Chen Yang for his understanding, then led the group into one of the two remaining courtyards.

The rooms here were constructed in a row next to one another, much like the rooms one would find in inns, and they were entirely constructed from the black stone material that was able to keep out spiritual sense.

There were quite a few rooms, so each person was able to take a room for themselves, and after taking a moment to examine his room to ensure that it hadn't been tampered with, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed.

It didn't take long before night arrived, and Han Li suddenly opened his eyes before emerging from his room.

It was a peaceful night with a bright moon hanging high up in the sky, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he took a glance up at the moon, following which he quickly made his way to a room before knocking on the door.

A few moments later, the door was opened to reveal Daoist Xie.

Han Li took a glance at Daoist Xie, then said, "Sorry to bother you so late at night, Fellow Daoist Chen."

This was Chen Yang's room, and at this moment, he was seated inside.

"Not at all, Fellow Daoist Li. Please take a seat. What brings you here so late at night?" Chen Yang asked with a smile.

"We agreed that if you couldn't find a way to remove the Black Tribulation Centipede in my body, then I could raise another request to you, right? That is the purpose of my visit," Han Li replied in a direct and straightforward manner.

"What is your request, Fellow Daoist Li? As long as it's within the realm of my capabilities, I'll be sure to do everything in my power to fulfill your request," Chen Yang replied with a nod.

"I would like you to find two people for me, one of whom is Shi Kong, while the other is a female cultivator by the name of Violet Spirit. She was cast into the Scalptia Spatial Domain within the last century. Please tell me your findings prior to the commencement of the martial gathering," Han Li said.

A slightly hesitant look appeared on Chen Yang's face as he replied, "I can definitely help you look for this Violet Spirit. As a female cultivator who was cast into the Scalptia Spatial Domain within the last century, she shouldn't be too difficult to track down as long as she actually has come to Profound City. However, Shi Kong is currently in E Kuai's hands, so it'll be rather difficult to gather information on him."

"If it were a simple task, then I wouldn't have to come to you," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"I suppose that's true. I've already failed to fulfill a promise once, so I definitely can't fail again. Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, I'll be sure to give you a response prior to the commencement of the martial gathering," Chen Yang promised in a solemn fashion.

"In that case, I'll be counting on you, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li said with a faint smile, then promptly departed and returned to his own room.

An uneventful night passed by.

The next morning, Han Li was just about to go out when his door was knocked on by a young servant from Green Goat City.

Aside from Han Li and the others, Chen Yang had also brought some servants to Profound City to cater to everyone's needs.

"Senior Li, City Lord Chen would like to invite you to see him," the young servant informed in a respectful manner.

"Do you know why he wants to see me?" Han Li asked.

"I wasn't informed of that," the young servant replied with a shake of his head.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he instructed, "Lead the way."

The servant quickly led Han Li to Chen Yang's residence, and to Han Li's surprise, there were many people already gathered in the room, including the likes of Gu Qianxun, Yi Liya, and Xiong Pei.

Gu Qianxun gave Han Li a smile and a nod upon his arrival, and Han Li responded in kind, but right at this moment, he sensed a hostile gaze, and he turned to discover Yi Liya glowering at him.

Even as their eyes met, Yi Liya didn't back down at all, giving Han Li one final glare before looking away, leaving Han Li feeling rather perplexed.

He had sensed that Yi Liya was harboring some enmity toward him on the entire journey here, but they hadn't even spoken to each other once, so he couldn't understand why Yi Liya resented him so intensely.

Some more time passed, and once everyone from Green Goat City was present, Chen Yang declared, "I have some things to discuss with all of you."

Everyone remained silent, waiting for what he had to say next.

"There's still some time left until the martial gathering is set to commence, and with so many powers gathered in the city, the circumstances are very complicated. Hence, if you don't have anything important to do, then stay in your residences and prepare for the martial gathering.

“Even if you do have to go out, make sure you don't get into conflicts with anyone from other cities. Otherwise, you'll be putting me in a very awkward position," Chen Yang said.

It was clear from the earlier interactions that the people from the other cities were mostly quite hostile toward Green Goat City, so no one raised any objections to this.

"City Lord Chen, may I ask who you're going to send to represent our city in the martial gathering?" Yi Liya suddenly asked, "It was announced yesterday that each of the four subsidiary cities could only send twelve people, and there are clearly more than twelve of us here."

Everyone immediately turned to Chen Yang upon hearing this.

This was a question that was on everyone's mind. Being able to take part in the Five City Martial Gathering was a huge honor, and that wasn't even to mention the huge rewards on the line.

Everyone was very confident in their own powers, so they all desired the opportunity to prove themselves.

"There's no hurry, I'll announce the roster when the martial gathering begins. You can all go now," Chen Yang said.

Everyone was rather disappointed to hear this, but they could only depart.

After leaving Chen Yang's residence, Han Li paused momentarily before turning to leave the courtyard altogether.

Even though Chen Yang had just told them to try and avoid going out, he really did have some important matters to attend to.

Right at this moment, Gu Qianxun's voice rang out from behind him.

"Are you going out, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"That's right. I plan to go out and explore the city a little," Han Li replied as he stopped in his tracks.

"Do you intend to seek out Mistress Liu Hua to try and address the Black Tribulation Centipede in your body?" Gu Qianxun asked through voice transmission.

"That's right," Han Li replied, making no attempt to hide his intentions.

The Black Tribulation Centipede was a constant thorn in his side that had to be removed as soon as possible.

"I intend to do the same thing, so why don't we go together? Mistress Liu Hua is the number one tool refinement master of Profound City, and it's not so easy to secure an audience with him," Gu Qianxun said.

"Sure, why not?" Han Li replied with a nod, and the two of them departed together, shortly following which a group of several figures emerged from under the shade of a nearby tree.

It was Yi Liya, Toxic Dragon, Tu Gang, and a few others, and Yi Liya was observing Han Li's departing figure with a resentful look in his eyes.

With Gu Qianxun leading the way, the two left the courtyard before entering the city.

Due to the upcoming Five City Martial Gathering, the city was extremely busy, and the wares sold in the shops that lined the streets were clearly of a superior quality to what was sold in Green Goat City.

Compared with the enormous scale and opulence of Profound City, Green Goat City was made to resemble a rundown slum.

Chapter 897: Shut Out

"I didn't think it would be so lively and bustling here. This feels like being in a city in the Devil Realm," Han Li remarked.

"This is the main city of Profound City, so it should be like this," Gu Qianxun replied, looking less impressed than Han Li.

After walking for a while, the two of them gradually left the more prosperous area of the city, and they stopped in their tracks in front of a crimson pagoda that was constructed beside a mountain.

The pagoda was quite large, standing at seven hundred to eight hundred feet tall. It was split up into nine levels, and there were countless crimson runes engraved upon it, giving off such intese heat that it felt like standing at the crater of an active volcano.

"Is this Mistress Liu Hua's residence?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. Mistress Liu Hua resides on the top floor of this Molten Flame Pagoda, but it's not so easy to secure an audience with him," Gu Qianxun replied.

"You seem to know quite a bit about Mistress Liu Hua, Fellow Daoist Gu. What type of person is he?" Han Li asked.

"I can't say I know a whole lot about him, he's simply an extremely renowned figure owing to his status as the number one tool refinement master of Profound City," Gu Qianxun replied.

"Just how skilled a tool refinement master is he?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Let me put it this way for you: it's said that prior to being cast into the Scalptia Spatial Domain, Mistress Liu Hua once refined a third tier holy treasure," Gu Qianxun replied.

Han Li was astonished to hear this.

The devil race referred to devilish treasures as holy treasures, and these treasures were also split up into tiers, just like immortal treasures. Up to this point, aside from the Heaven Controlling Vial, which was a treasure of an indeterminate tier, the most powerful treasures that Han Li had seen were the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber and the Virata Lute, both of which were treasures of the third tier.

With his current powers, these two treasures were completely unfathomable to him.

The fact that Mistress Liu Hua was capable of refining a treasure of the same caliber as the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber and the Virata Lute was certainly a testament to his expertise in this field.

"It does sound like he's an exceptional tool refinement master, but here in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, both devilish qi and immortal spiritual power are completely inaccessible, so surely his abilities will be severely handicapped," Han Li mused.

"That's true. However, Mistress Liu Hua was able to develop a method to replace devilish qi or immortal spiritual power with starpower, and it's become his primary calling card," Gu Qianxun said.

"Could it be that all of the starpower restrictions in the city were created by him?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Not only that, but I've heard that Mistress Liu Hua has also found a way to inject starpower into weapons, thereby granting them powers similar to that of holy treasures. However, refining such a weapon is an extremely costly process, so it'll be next to impossible for us to get our hands on such weapons," Gu Qianxun replied.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative look on his face.

"Let's go," Gu Qianxun said, and the two of them arrived before the Molten Flame Pagoda.

Even though the doors were tightly shut, there was still a burst of scorching heat radiating out from inside.

"It's said that this Molten Flame Pagoda is constructed upon an active volcanic crater. It's impossible to use devilish qi in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so natural fire must be used for tool refinement purpose," Gu Qianxun explained.

Han Li nodded in response, then looked around to discover that there was no one else in the entire surrounding area.

"If Mistress Liu Hua really is such an exceptional tool refinement master, then why is it so peaceful here? How is there no one here to request weapons from him?" Han Li asked.

"Mistress Liu Hua is City Lord E Kuai's personal tool refinement master, so he possesses an extremely lofty status. On top of that, he doesn't like to be disturbed, so no one dares to come and bother him," Gu Qianxun replied as she strode over to the doors before knocking on them.

Only after knocking on the door for quite a while was it finally answered by a short and portly young man with a rash on his head.

"How can I help you?" the young man asked in a lazy and slightly arrogant voice.

"We have been long-time admirers of Mistress Liu Hua, and we would like to be granted an audience with him," Gu Qianxun replied as she cupped her fist in a salute, and Han Li did the same.

"That's unfortunate. Mistress Liu Hua went into seclusion a few days ago, so he won't be seeing any guests," the young man said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

"When will Mistress Liu Hua be coming out of seclusion?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Who knows? If you're lucky, maybe seven or eight years, but you could be waiting for up to a century if you're not in luck," the young man replied as he began to close the door.

Gu Qianxun hurriedly stepped forward and called out, "Please wait a moment, Fellow Daoist. We're..."

"Don't make me chase you away! Do you think Mistress Liu Hua is someone that anyone can meet on a whim? Get out of here!" the young man snapped as he shooed Han Li and Gu Qianxun away.

"Indeed, to think that a pair of slaves from Green Goat City would even dream of meeting Mistress Liu Hua. What a joke!"

A mocking voice rang out from behind Han Li and Gu Qianxun, and the two of them turned around to discover that it was none other than Feng Wuchen.

He was accompanied by a dark-skinned middle-aged man with a coarse beard and a pair of sharp and piercing eyes that harbored a ruthless, animalistic gleam.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, but he didn't say anything, while Gu Qianxun's expression remained completely unchanged.

Feng Wuchen took a disdainful glance at the two of them, then turned to the portly young man as he pulled out a golden greeting card and said, "My name is Feng Wuchen, and I've come to see Mistress Liu Hua on behalf of my foster father, City Lord Qin Yuan of Profound End City."

The portly young man's expression changed upon hearing this, and he put on a welcoming smile as he replied, "Please wait for a moment, Fellow Daoist Feng, I'll report your visit to Mistress Liu Hua right away. However, it'll be up to Mistress Liu Hua whether he decides to see you or not."

He was just a gatekeeper, so he didn't dare to make any promises.

"Of course," Feng Wuchen replied with a confident smile.

The young man gave Feng Wuchen a nod, yet right as he was about to enter the pagoda, Gu Qianxun pulled out an antiquated white bone badge with a crack on its surface as she called out to him, "Please wait a moment, Fellow Daoist, I also have a token here that I would like you to present to Mistress Liu Hua."

Several free-flowing runes that were giving off a faint white glow were engraved onto both sides of the badge, and the short young man stopped in his tracks upon hearing this.

He was just about to accept the bone badge from her when Feng Wuchen scoffed, "You call that thing a token? What a joke!"

He knew that Gu Qianxun was quite a powerful cultivator, but ultimately, she was only a lowly gladiator of Green Goat City, so he didn't think very highly of her at all.

A hesitant look appeared on the portly young man's face upon hearing this.

"You're the gatekeeper of this Molten Flame Pagoda, right? In that case, I suggest you do your job and don't try to overstep your authority. Otherwise, you could incur consequences that are too severe for you to handle," Gu Qianxun said in an indifferent manner.

"I understand. Please wait here for a moment, I'll report your visit to Mistress Liu Hua as well," the portly young man replied as he made his decision, accepting Gu Qianxun's bone badge before re-entering the Molten Flame Pagoda.

Feng Wuchen's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, but he didn't dare to step out of line in front of Mistress Liu Hua's residence.

Close to two hours flew by in the blink of an eye, yet the portly young man still hadn't returned, and it was as if he had disappeared.

Right at this moment, the sound of footsteps rang out from inside the Molten Flame Pagoda, following which the portly young man finally reappeared.

"Sorry to keep you all waiting for so long. Mistress Liu Hua doesn't like to be disturbed, and he was doing his morning meditation, so I could only wait until after he was done. Please come in, fellow daoists," the portly young man said in an apologetic manner.

"It's fine. Mistress Liu Hua must be an extremely busy man, so it's only right that we wait for him," Feng Wuchen said with a smile as he began to make his way into the pagoda.

The portly young man hurriedly reached out a hand to stop him, and he didn't dare to look at Feng Wuchen's face as he said, "Mistress Liu Hua has asked you to come back tomorrow, but he would like to see Fellow Daoist Gu and her companion now."

At the same time, he was internally kicking himself. He was in such a hurry to invite Gu Qianxun and Han Li into the pagoda that he failed to properly elaborate, and it was clear that Feng Wuchen wasn't going to be very happy about this.

Sure enough, his face turned bright red, and a furious and humiliated look appeared in his eyes as he asked in an incredulous voice, "What did you just say?"

As for Gu Qianxun, her expression remained completely unchanged, as if she had already anticipated this outcome, and she thanked the portly young man before stepping into the pagoda, while Han Li followed along with an intrigued look in his eyes.

The portly young man took a hesitant glance at Feng Wuchen, then rushed after Han Li and Gu Qianxun as he said, "Please come with me, fellow daoists."

The doors of the pagoda slowly swung shut, leaving Feng Wuchen's duo outside.

"Let's go!" Feng Wuchen snapped with a furious expression as he turned to depart, and before long, he and the dark-skinned middle-aged man had vanished into the distance.

……

Han Li and Gu Qianxun were led by the portly young man down a long corridor before arriving at a spiral staircase that led upward.

"Mistress Liu Hua resides on the top floor of the pagoda, so please come with me," the portly young man said in a respectful manner.

As Han Li and Gu Qianxuan trailed along behind him, the former asked through voice transmission, "Fellow Daoist Gu, if you had this token all along, why did you tell me that it was going to be difficult to secure an audience with Mistress Liu Hua?"

"Please forgive me, Fellow Daoist Li. That token was left to me by my mother, and she told me that I'd be able to use it to meet Mistress Liu Hua. However, I didn't know if it would actually work, and I certainly wasn't expecting things to go this smoothly," Gu Qianxun replied with a smile.

"Is that so?" Han Li mused with slightly furrowed brows.

Chapter 898: Offer

Han Li and Gu Qianxun were led to the top floor of the Molten Flame Pagoda by the portly young man before drawing to a halt in front of a certain room.

"They're here, Mistress Liu Hua," the portly young man declared in a respectful manner.

"Well, what are you waiting for then? Hurry up and bring them inside!"

The portly young man didn't dare to delay, hurriedly pressing hand over several parts of the door in succession, and the stone door slowly slid apart to reveal a large opening, out of which came wafting a fragrant, meaty aroma.

A perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face upon catching a whiff of this smell, and the stone door slowly closed again after he and Gu Qianxun entered the room.

Upon entering the room, the meaty aroma became even more pronounced, and Han Li swept his gaze around the room to discover a large stone table placed next to the window.

There was a large hole at the center of the table, atop which sat a huge pot over a coal flame. The milky white broth in the pot was bubbling incessantly, and some type of beast bone was being cooked inside along with some meat and tendons.

Behind the stone table sat a short yet muscular black-robed elderly man with one sleeve rolled up all the way to his shoulder. Held in that hand was a beast bone that was around the same thickness as his arm, and he was munching on the greasy flesh clinging to the bone while holding the bone badge presented by Gu Qianxun in his other hand.

The elderly man appeared to be no different from a normal human, but his face was bright red, and it was unclear if this was his natural complexion, or if it was simply because he was sitting too close to the coal flame. His head was already displaying signs of balding, but his beard was extremely dense, and it was arranged into three thick braids.

Even though Han Li was already aware that the title of mistress was only a special title granted to a tool refinement master, it still felt quite jarring to see such a title applied to a man of this appearance.

Mistress Liu Hua began turning to Han Li and Gu Qianxun as he raised the bone badge and asked, "Which one of you..."

However, his voice abruptly cut off as soon as he caught sight of Gu Qianxun.

"The resemblance is uncanny! How are you related to the owner of this bone badge?"

The beast bone in Mistress Liu Hua's hand slipped out of his grasp before clattering onto the stone table, following which he rose to his feet before making his way over to Gu Qianxun to scrutinize her face intently.

Gu Qianxun was feeling a little uncomfortable in the face of his intense gaze, and she turned her head slightly to the side as she replied, "The owner of the bone badge was my mother."

"You're Hongyu's daughter? What's your name?" Mistress Liu Hua asked.

"My name is Gu Qianxun," Gu Qianxun replied.

"Your surname is Gu?" A hint of sorrow flashed through Mistress Liu Hua's eyes upon hearing this. "Who is your father?"

"I don't know. I've never seen my father before, and my mother never told me who he was. All she told me was that my father is the former owner of this bone badge, and that my surname comes from this badge," Gu Qianxun replied. [1]

She directed an intrigued gaze toward Mistress Liu Hua as she spoke, and it was becoming clear to her how her mother and Mistress Liu Hua were related.

The same thought had also occurred to Han Li, and he was feeling much more reassured. At the same time, he couldn't help but blame Gu Qianxun for not telling him about this connection earlier. If he had known about this in advance, then he wouldn't have been so worried for so long.

"How is your mother?" Mistress Liu Hua asked as a hint of excitement surfaced in his eyes.

"My mother has... already passed away," Gu Qianxun replied with a grief-stricken expression.

"What? How?" Mistress Liu Hua hurriedly asked as his eyes widened in shock.

"My mother was targeted for her true spirit bloodline and..."

Before Gu Qianxun had a chance to finish her sentence, Mistress Liu Hua began pacing around his room with a furious expression, clenching his fists so tightly that his knuckles were cracking audibly.

In the end, a hint of remorse flashed through his eyes as he stopped in his tracks, then sat back down behind the stone table as he said, "Come and take a seat."

Han Li and Gu Qianxun sat down across from him, and only then did Mistress Liu Hua notice Han Li, upon which his brows furrowed slightly as he asked, "Who's this? Your dao partner?"

Mistress Liu Hua was scrutinizing Han Li with the disapproval and disdain of a father observing his potential son-in-law, and Han Li hurriedly replied, "You're mistaken, Senior Liu Hua. My name is Li Feiyu, and I'm Fellow Daoist Gu's friend."

"Are you here to purchase or request weapons from me? Let me make this clear in advance: if you want to request weapons from me, then you can only state broad requirements and leave the finer details to me. Don't bother bringing me any designs, I only use my own designs," Mistress Liu Hua said in a cold voice, and it was clear that his animosity was directed solely at Han Li.

"We're not here to purchase or request weapons from you, Senior Liu Hua," Gu Qianxun replied.

"What brings you here then?" Mistress Liu Hua asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"We've come here to see if we can have the Black Tribulation Centipedes in our bodies removed," Han Li replied.

A complex look appeared in Mistress Liu Hua's eyes upon hearing this, and he asked, "You two must've come from Green Goat City, right?"

"How did you know?" Han Li asked.

"I've only ever passed down the method to raise Black Tribulation Centipede to Du Qingyang, and as long as he's not a complete moron, I'm sure he wouldn't have passed it onto anyone else. Hence, I can only assume that the two of you came from Green Goat City," Mistress Liu Hua sighed.

"That's right, we did indeed come from Green Goat City. The Black Tribulation Centipedes in our bodies were planted by Du Qingyang, and we've come to you today in the hope that they can be removed," Han Li said.

"In that case, the two of you must've played a hand in Du Qingyang's demise as well, right?" Mistress Liu Hua asked.

"You were the one who taught Du Qingyang how to raise Black Tribulation Centipedes?" Gu Qianxun suddenly interjected in a furious voice.

Gu Qianxun's abrupt tonal shift had Mistress Liu Hua feeling a little uneasy all of a sudden, and a slightly sheepish look appeared on his face as he explained, "I owed him a pretty big favor back then, and that's why I taught him the method to raise Black Tribulation Centipedes. As for how he's been using those Black Tribulation Centipedes, that's completely unknown to me."

"He used them on Fellow Daoist Li, he used them on me, and... he also used them on my mother," Gu Qianxun spat through gritted teeth.

"You're saying Du Qingyang was the one who killed your mother?" Mistress Liu Hua asked as a grim look appeared on his face.

"I can't be certain of that, but back then, my mother was abducted by Du Qingyang from Profound End City, so I'm certain that City Lord Qin Yuan must've played a role in her death as well," Gu Qianxun replied.

"Let's discuss this matter another time," Mistress Liu Hua sighed. "The two of you must be carrying Black Tribulation Stones, right? Otherwise, you wouldn't have been able to survive to this point. Having said that, Black Tribulation Stones are not a permanent solution."

"What do you mean by that, Senior?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Black Tribulation Stones can place Black Tribulation Centipedes into a deep sleep, but their effects will wane over time, so eventually, the Black Tribulation Centipedes in your bodies will awaken, and once that happens, your fates will be sealed," Mistress Liu Hua explained.

"Please help us remove these Black Tribulation Centipedes from our bodies, Senior Liu Hua," Han Li implored once again.

"If you want me to save you, then you'll have to agree to a condition of mine," Mistress Liu Hua said after a brief moment of contemplation.

"Go ahead, Senior," Han Li prompted.

"You have to accept me as your master and become my disciple," Mistress Liu Hua declared.

An incredulous look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and Gu Qianxun was clearly also very much taken aback to hear this.

"Are you unwilling to become my disciple?" Mistress Liu Hua asked in a cold voice.

"No, it's just that I don't understand. Why me?" Han Li asked.

To this day, Doctor Mo's betrayal was still fresh in Han Li's mind, so he was very reluctant to enter another master and disciple relationship. However, he certainly wouldn't mind the opportunity to learn the art of tool refinement from Mistress Liu Hua. [2]

"Because you're also a human, and I like the look of you. Is that reason enough?" Mistress Liu Hua harrumphed coldly.

"I'm naturally honored to have been able to catch your eye, Senior, but may I ask if there will be any restrictions placed upon me if I were to become your disciple?" Han Li asked.

"Of course. If you become my disciple, you'll have to serve me by my side for at least ten thousand years," Mistress Liu Hua replied.

"I can't leave at all within the ten thousand years?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Ten thousand years is nothing more than the blink of an eye for cultivators like us, surely you have at least that much patience. Countless people have begged me to accept them as their disciple, so I suggest you don't squander this opportunity," Mistress Liu Hua said with a proud expression.

"I don't doubt that at all, but it's just that I've entered the Scalptia Spatial Domain on this occasion to find someone very important to me. Before I find her, I can't stay in Profound City, so I'll have to turn down your kind offer," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

[1]. Gu Qianxun's surname of Gu (骨) translates to bone in Chinese.

[Back]

[2]. For more information on Doctor Mo, check out https://rmji.fandom.com/wiki/Mo_Juren

[Back]

Chapter 899: Counteroffer

"You're looking for a woman?" Mistress Liu Hua asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Han Li nodded in response.

"You better think long and hard about this! Not only are you turning down an opportunity to become my disciple, you're also turning down a chance to have the Black Tribulation Centipede in your body removed," Mistress Liu Hua harrumphed coldly.

"I'm aware of that, but seeing as the Molten Flame Pagoda is a place where business is conducted, I would like to propose a deal to you, Senior Liu Hua," Han Li said.

"Piss off! I'm not doing business with an idiot like you!" Mistress Liu Hua snapped as he picked up a beast bone with his right hand, while setting his left hand down onto the table beside him in a way that made it appear as if he were holding an invisible cup.

This subtle detail didn't escape Han Li's notice, and he asked in a seemingly casual manner, "How long has it been since you last had some wine, Senior Liu Hua?"

It seemed to be a completely random question, but Mistress Liu Hua immediately raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, then asked, "How were you able to tell that I'm fond of wine?"

"I can see that your right hand is very greasy all over from the beast bones that you're eating, but your left hand is completely clean and devoid of grease. On top of that, the way that you rest your left hand on the table clearly indicates that you have a habit of holding a cup of wine as you eat," Han Li explained with a smile.

Gu Qianxun's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and she couldn't help but wonder why Han Li would bring up something like this.

"You've got some sharp eyes, it's just a pity that you're not the brightest upstairs. So what if I enjoy having a drink? Do you have wine for me?" Mistress Liu Hua asked.

"I don't have any ready-made wine right now, but perhaps I'll have some if you're willing to wait for some time," Han Li replied.

"What's that supposed to mean? Are you saying that you're going to brew your own wine?" Mistress Liu Hua asked in an incredulous manner.

Han Li nodded in response.

Mistress Liu Hua immediately burst into laughter upon hearing this.

"The Scalptia Spatial Domain is a completely dead and barren place devoid of both devilish qi and world's origin qi. Not only will you not be able to find any spirit ingredients required for brewing immortal wine, you won't even be able to find things like barley or grains in here, so how are you going to brew any wine? Do you have a miraculous ability to squeeze wine out of stone?"

Gu Qianxun's brows became even more tightly furrowed upon hearing this.

However, Han Li remained completely unfazed as he asked, "Have you heard of a type of wine called Blood Plasma Wine, Senior?"

"Blood Plasma Wine?" Mistress Liu Hua repeated with a perplexed expression.

"You may not have heard of it, but I can assure you that I have a way to brew wine from blood plasma. The flavor may be a little... interesting, but you can't ask for too much in the Scalptia Spatial Domain," Han Li said with a smile.

He had learned the brewing method of Blood Plasma Wine from Daoist Hu Yan, but it was a wine with a very strong flavor, and he wasn't a fan of it, so he had never tried to brew it before.

As for whether it would be possible to brew this wine using scaled beast blood in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, Han Li wasn't very confident, but at the very least, it was worth a try.

"Can you really brew wine using blood plasma?" Mistress Liu Hua asked.

"If I can brew this wine, would you be willing to give us the method to remove the Black Tribulation Centipedes from our bodies?" Han Li asked.

"You want me to hand over the Black Tribulation Centipede removal method for a mere flagon of wine?" Mistress Liu Hua scoffed.

Han Li seemed to have already anticipated this response, and he said in a calm fashion, "In that case, what other requests do you have for me? Feel free to state them."

"In addition to this Blood Plasma Wine, I want a fist-sized piece of Heavenly Qilin Crystal as well," Mistress Liu Hua declared.

A spark of hope had just arisen in Gu Qianxun's heart, but it was instantly dashed upon hearing this.

"Senior Liu Hua, Heavenly Qilin Crystal is one of the most premium materials in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, and even a fingernail-sized piece goes for astronomical prices, let alone a fist-sized piece. Even if such a large piece exists, no one would be willing to display it to others, so it'll be impossible for us to obtain," Gu Qianxun said in an urgent voice, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"I'm not just going to ask something from you and not point out a way for you to obtain it. I have reliable information that one of the prizes for this edition of the Five City Martial Gathering is a piece of Heavenly Qilin Crystal. As for what placing you'll need to secure in order to obtain the crystal, that's not something that I'm privy to, but then again, I can't make things too easy for you," Mistress Liu Hua said.

A resigned smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this. He had intended to hold back and conceal his true power during this martial gathering, but it seemed that wasn't going to be possible.

"Are you really able to brew wine using blood plasma?" Mistress Liu Hua asked again.

"My life is on the line here, so I certainly wouldn't dare to just fabricate a story," Han Li replied.

"Alright, if you can really brew this wine and bring me the Heavenly Qilin Crystal, then I'll remove the Black Tribulation Centipede from your body," Mistress Liu Hua declared.

"Thank you, Senior Liu Hua. There's some preparatory work that I have to do, so I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

Following his departure, Mistress Liu Hua and Gu Qianxun were left to sit across from each other in silence.

"At this point, I'm sure you've already guessed the nature of my relationship with your mother," Mistress Liu Hua sighed.

"Why did you leave her?" Gu Qianxun asked as tears began to well up in her eyes.

"Your mother had far too unyielding a personality. I wanted to stay by her side, but the feeling wasn't mutual. It's too long a story to tell here, and there's no point in telling it anyway. Now that Du Qingyang is already dead, I'll go to Qin Yuan myself to ensure that he also pays for the role that he played in your mother's death," Mistress Liu Hua replied with a bitter expression.

"There's no need for that, I'll avenge my mother myself," Gu Qianxun said in a cold voice.

Mistress Liu Hua's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "In any case, the top priority right now is to have the Black Tribulation Centipede in your body removed."

"Why were you only willing to save Fellow Daoist Li if he agreed to become your disciple? Is it really just because he's also a human? I don't believe that," Gu Qianxun said.

"I wanted to keep him as my disciple because I could see that he has a great deal of potential. My intuition and experience tells me that there's more to him than meets the eye," Mistress Liu Hua replied.

"Then why are you making him secure a piece of Heavenly Qilin Crystal now?" Gu Qianxun asked.

"On one hand, I want to use this as a test to see if he really is as impressive as I think he is, and on the other hand, I want the Heavenly Qilin Crystal for your sake," Mistress Liu Hua explained.

Gu Qianxun fell silent upon hearing this.

After leaving the Molten Flame Pagoda, Han Li was feeling much more relaxed, having finally found a solution to a problem that had been constantly weighing on his mind of late, and his footsteps were a little lighter and more springy as a result.

Upon returning to the courtyard where the Green Goat City cultivators were staying, Han Li didn't immediately return to his own residence. Instead, he traveled to Chen Yang's residence before knocking on the door, which was quickly opened.

Chen Yang faltered slightly at the sight of Han Li, then hurriedly invited him inside.

At this moment, there was one more person in the room, namely the horned man by the name of Xuanyuan Xing.

Daoist Xie wasn't present, and it was unclear where he had gone.

"Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan," Han Li greeted as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Xuanyuan Xing rose to his feet before giving Han Li a nod.

Han Li could see that there were two cups of tea on the table, both of which had already cooled down to room temperature, and he asked, "Are the two of you discussing something? In that case, I'll come back later."

"It's fine, we've already finished our discussion. I'm sure you must have some important matters to discuss with Fellow Daoist Chen, so I'll leave you to it," Xuanyuan Xing said with a smile before departing.

Following Xuanyuan Xing's departure, Chen Yang invited Han Li to take a seat, then brewed two new cups of tea as he asked, "What brings you here today, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"I would like some information on the cultivators from the other cities participating in the martial gathering," Han Li replied in a direct and straightforward manner.

"Alright, please wait a moment," Chen Yang replied before standing up and making his way into the inner chamber of his residence.

Shortly thereafter, he re-emerged with a stack of papers in his hands, and he handed them to Han Li as he said, "This is all of the information that we've gathered so far. I have a copy of everything, so you can take this back with you."

Even though Han Li had agreed to fight on behalf of Green Goat City, he had never displayed much interest in the Five City Martial Gathering, so Chen Yang was naturally very happy to see him developing an interest in the event, and he had very high hopes for Han Li.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li said as he accepted the papers.

"Why are you suddenly interested in this information, Fellow Daoist Li? Did something happen?" Chen Yang asked.

"If I'm going to be participating in the martial gathering, then I naturally want to do well. Is that strange?" Han Li asked.

"At the moment, Chen Yang was using Black Tribulation Centipede to control the gladiators under him, just like Du Qingyang had done in the past, so Han Li didn't want him to know about the agreement that he had made with Mistress Liu Hua.

"Not at all! I'm ecstatic to see that you're applying yourself," Chen Yang hurriedly replied.

"In that case, I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li said with a faint smile before standing up to depart, and Chen Yang accompanied him to the door.

As he watched Han Li's departing figure, a contemplative look appeared on his face, and he suddenly clapped his hands together, upon which a young male servant emerged from the inner chamber before getting down on one knee.

It was the same young man that had been sent to fetch Han Li back in Green Goat City, but at this moment, he was wearing a long black robe, and his aura had changed drastically, as if he had become one with the shadows.

"Go and find out where Li Feiyu went and what he did today," Chen Yang instructed.

The young man gave an affirmative response, then abruptly vanished from the spot.

Chapter 900: Mobilization

After parting ways with Chen Yang, Han Li quickly returned to his own room to read through the papers that had just been given to him.

It was clear that Chen Yang had made some very extensive preparations, so the information was very detailed, not only laying out the cultivation arts and fortes of powerful cultivators from other cities, there were even records of their notable past battles, so there was a lot for Han Li to pore over.

Only after a full six hours had passed by did Han Li finally put down the last sheet of paper, upon which he raised his head with a contemplative expression, having gained a rough idea of what he could face in the upcoming martial gathering.

After sitting in silence for a while, he pulled out the deity statue with three heads and six arms before setting it down in front of himself.

After that, he pulled out a jade box, contained within which was the A tier beast core that Chen Yang had gifted to him earlier.

There were still three months until the martial gathering was set to begin, and that wasn't a particularly long time, but he still didn't want to waste it.

After taking a deep breath, a beam of translucent light shot out of his glabella and into the black statue, and it immediately began adopting a series of different poses, while the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts appeared on its back.

Han Li was just about to pull out the beast core to commence his cultivation when his gaze suddenly returned to the black statue before him.

Instead of focusing on the text on the statue, his attention had been caught by the poses that it was cycling through.

Ever since he obtained this black statue, his attention had always been focused on the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, leading him to ignore the twelve poses adopted by the statue, but it had just occurred to him that these poses most likely weren't just for show.

Han Li watched as the black statue cycled through the twelve poses over and over again, and after some contemplation, he suddenly laid down onto the ground, then adopted the first pose displayed by the statue.

As soon as he did this, his eyes immediately widened with shock.

……

Three months flew by in a flash.

On this day, there were many Green Goat City cultivators gathered in the guest hall of Chen Yang's residence.

All of them were chatting spiritedly with one another with excited looks on their faces, clearly very much looking forward to the imminent Five City Martial Gathering.

However, at the same time, there was also some tension in the air.

The martial gathering was set to begin the next day, and according to Chen Yang, he was going to be announcing the roster of Green Goat City representatives soon.

Chen Yang had brought a total of around seventeen to eighteen people with him, most of which were arena area leaders, but that had to be cut down to a lineup of just twelve people.

Anyone who was cut from the list would be unable to participate in the martial gathering, thereby losing the opportunity to win glory for themselves and the tantalizing rewards that were on offer.

Even more importantly, if a slave could make it through the first round of elimination in the martial gathering, then they would be granted freedom, and it would be up to them whether they chose to remain an arena gladiator or not in the future.

Hence, over the past one thousand years, many people had been doing everything in their power to make strides in their cultivation so that they could stand a better chance in the Five City Martial Gathering.

At this point, around a dozen people had already gathered in the room, with Yi Liya sitting at the center, while Tu Gang, Sun Binghe, and the others were seated around him.

Everyone in the room was either seated on their own, or in small groups of two or three.

Toxic Dragon was also in the room, but he was sitting by himself instead of next to Yi Liya.

He would occasionally take a glance at Yi Liya with a series of mixed emotions on his face, including vexation and longing, and he stood up on several occasions to approach him, only for Yi Liya to give him a stern glare that forced him to sit back down.

Right at this moment, the sound of footsteps rang out from outside the hall, and everyone looked up to discover that it was Han Li.

Compared with three months ago, he seemed to have lost some weight, making the contours of the bones in his hands and feet appear particularly pronounced, and his entire body was giving off a formidable aura.

Yi Liya's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and several other people's expressions also changed slightly upon catching sight of Han Li.

Han Li swept his gaze over everyone in the room, then sat down in a corner by himself.

No one in the room stood up to greet him, and this suited him just fine as he closed his eyes to rest.

Even though he was on his own, it didn't feel as if he was being overshadowed by everyone else in the room at all. Instead, it felt like he was standing out like a crane among chickens.

Toxic Dragon cast a hesitant gaze toward Han Li, following which a decisive look appeared in his eyes, and he stood up to approach him.

Yi Liya's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Li," Toxic Dragon greeted in a friendly manner as he sat down next to Toxic Dragon.

Han Li opened his eyes and took a glance at Toxic Dragon, then at Yi Liya, and a smile appeared on his face as he replied, "Indeed, long time no see, Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon."

"The Five City Martial Gathering is coming up tomorrow, it looks like you're already very assured of your spot on the roster," Toxic Dragon remarked.

"Not at all, it's my first time taking part in such a grand event, and I'm only doing my best to remain composed," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"You're far too modest, Fellow Daoist Li," Toxic Dragon chuckled, and the two of them struck up a conversation.

A cold look flashed through Yi Liya's eyes upon seeing this, and he was just about to say something when Gu Qianxun and Yao Li entered the room.

There was a faint layer of translucent light over Gu Qianxun's face, and it seemed she had undergone a slight change as well.

Yi Liya immediately rose to his feet as he greeted with a warm smile, "It looks like you've made very good use of your time cultivating in seclusion, Fellow Daoist Gu. I'm sure all of us can expect an exceptional performance from you."

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Yi," Gu Qianxun replied in an indifferent manner as her gaze roamed over the room, and all of a sudden, her eyes lit up slightly, following which she excused herself with Yi Liya before approaching Han Li.

Yi Liya's expression instantly stiffened slightly upon seeing this, following which he returned to his seat with a furious look in his eyes.

"Is this seat taken, Fellow Daoist Li?" Gu Qianxun asked as she pointed at a seat next to Han Li.

"Not at all. Please take a seat, Fellow Daoist Gu," Han Li replied with a smile.

Gu Qianxun sat down beside Han Li, while Yao Li reluctantly sat down beside her, and a hint of surprise flashed through Toxic Dragon's eyes upon seeing this.

"The Five City Martial Gathering is commencing tomorrow. Have you prepared well, Fellow Daoist Li?" Gu Qianxun asked with a smile.

"The martial gathering is rife with formidable foes. With my paltry powers, I can only do my best," Han Li replied with a modest smile.

"If you need any help, feel free to call upon me," Gu Qianxun said.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Gu," Han Li replied with a nod.

Toxic Dragon and Yao Li were both rather perplexed by how close Han Li and Gu Qianxun seemed to have become, but neither of them raised any questions.

Time slowly passed by, and the rest of the cultivators from Green Goat City arrived one after another, with Xuanyuan Xing the last one to arrive.

Instead of sitting down with anyone, he merely gave Gu Qianxun and Han Li a slight nod, then stood on his own with his hands clasped behind his back.

Shortly thereafter, Chen Yang emerged from his inner chamber, and he seemed to be in high spirits as he said, "Sorry to keep you all waiting."

Everyone stood up to extend respectful bows toward him, and he sat down onto the main seat as he waved a dismissive hand and said, "No need for formalities."

A serious look then appeared on his face as he asked, "Is everyone prepared for the Five City Martial Gathering commencing tomorrow?"

Yi Liya took a glance at Gu Qianxun, then replied in a confident voice, "Rest assured, City Lord Chen, all of us are fully prepared."

Everyone else immediately echoed the sentiment, and their collective voices caused the entire guest hall to rumble and buzz.

With all of Du Qingyang's most loyal subordinates taken out of the picture, most of the Green Goat City cultivators present were newbies who were very confident in their own abilities, but the more experienced ones among them, such as Xiong Pei, appeared to be far less optimistic.

"Good. Without further ado, I'll be announcing the roster for this martial gathering," Chen Yang declared with a smile, and everyone involuntarily tensed up a little upon hearing this.

"Gu Qianxun, Li Feiyu, Yi Liya, Tu Gang, Sun Binghe, Xiong Pei... Toxic Dragon, and Xuanyuan Xing!"

After the twelve names were announced, everyone displayed different reactions, ranging from elation to disappointment.

Gu Qianxun and Han Li's expression remained unchanged, and it seemed that they weren't surprised by this outcome.

Yao Li was clearly not very happy to have missed out on the list, while Toxic Dragon heaved a faint sigh of relief.

Yi Liya's brows furrowed slightly as he turned a cold gaze to Han Li, and it was clear that he wasn't very pleased that Han Li's name had been announced ahead of his.

"This edition of the martial gathering is extremely important for our Green Goat City, so all of you must do your best. If any of you manages to make it into the top four, you'll be receiving a reward from me in addition to the one from City Lord E Kuai!" Chen Yang declared, much to the excitement of the twelve people selected.

"Alright, you can all go back to rest now. Li Feiyu, stay behind please," Chen Yang said.

Everyone turned to Han Li with a surprised expression upon hearing this, then stood up to depart.

Yi Liya's expression darkened even further, and he departed with everyone else.

Before long, Han Li and Chen Yang were the only two people left in the room.

"Have you asked me to stay behind because you've uncovered some information on Violet Spirit and Shi Kong, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The people that I sent out were able to find out some things over the past three months," Chen Yang replied, but there was a slightly awkward look on his face.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li prompted.

Chapter 901: Eve of the Martial Gathering

"Regarding Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit, I've already looked into Profound City and the other three subsidiary cities, but haven't found any leads on her," Chen Yang sighed.

"You didn't find her?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"If Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit were in Profound City, then at the very least, I should've been able to find some information on her. However, there's no trace of her at all, so my guess is that she's either in Puppet City, or she perished to a scaled beast after entering the Scalptia Spatial Domain," Chen Yang replied in a grim voice.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this, and he didn't say anything.

"I wasn't able to find Violet Spirit, but I was able to find out Shi Kong's current whereabouts. He's in the city lord's manor of Profound City right now, but he's been locked up in prison," Chen Yang continued.

"Why?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid the reason is unclear as the people at the city lord's manor have been very tight lipped about this subject, but rest assured, Shi Kong's life isn't under any threat at the moment," Chen Yang replied.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Chen. Even though you weren't able to find Violet Spirit, you were able to track down Shi Kong, so you've fulfilled my request," Han Li said, and Chen Yang heaved an internal sigh of relief upon hearing this.

"If that's all, then I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li said as he turned to depart, and Chen Yang watched his parting figure for a while before returning to his inner chamber.

Daoist Xie was standing in a corner of the room, and upon spotting Chen Yang, he remarked, "You don't seem to be in a very good mood."

"If you were the city lord, and your subordinates went into the martial gathering with unjustified, blind confidence, I would think you would also be in a bad mood," Chen Yang sighed with a wry smile.

Daoist Xie offered no response to this.

"Yi Liya has the ability to make it far, but he's too conceited, and there's still a decent gap between him and the top combatants from the other cities. Gu Qianxun is probably the only one with any hope of reaching the top four. As for Fellow Daoist Li, I can't quite see through him, but I would presume that he's a little inferior to Gu Qianxun," Chen Yang mused.

……

Ater leaving Chen Yang's residence, Han Li returned to his own room and fell into deep thought.

It wasn't going to be easy to rescue Shi Chuankong from the Profound City prison. Having spent some time in Profound City, it had become apparent to him that Profound City was far more powerful than Green Goat City, so he had to proceed with caution.

On top of that, it was unclear whether Violet Spirit was dead or alive.

After sitting in silent contemplation for a long while, Han Li suddenly shook his head to clear his mind, then quickly composed himself.

This wasn't the time to be thinking about Violet Spirit and Shi Chuankong. At the moment, his top priority was to do well in the Five City Martial Gathering so that he could secure the Heavenly Qilin Crystal and remove the Black Tribulation Centipede from his body.

……

Inside a stone hall somewhere in Profound City.

A middle-aged man dressed in a beast hide cloak was sitting on a wide stone chair, and it was none other than City Lord Fu Jian of Excess Passage City.

Seated on each side of him were six Excess Passage City cultivators.

"It's clear that City Lord E Kuai is taking this edition of the Five City Martial Gathering very seriously, so the rewards will surely be quite extravagant. Hence, I want all of you to strive for high placings, particularly you, Duan Tong," Fu Jian said.

The bandaged man by the name of Duan Tong was seated right beside Fu Jian, and he gave a muffled grunt in response before falling silent.

Fu Jian seemed to have already grown accustomed to this, and he continued, "Setting aside Zhu Ziyuan of Profound City, are you confident in your ability to defeat Fang Chan of White Rock City and Feng Wuchen of Profound End City?"

"Feng Wuchen is faster than me, but as long as he can't break through my defenses, I'll be fine, and if he tries to engage me in close quarters combat, then that'll play right into my hands," Duan Tong replied.

"What about Fang Chan?" Fu Jian asked.

"I haven't faced him in battle before, so I'm not sure, but he was able to defeat Gu Qianxun last time, so he's clearly not to be taken lightly. After so many years, I'm sure he would've only become even more powerful," Duan Tong replied.

"I suppose it's a good thing that you're taking such a cautious approach," Fu Jian remarked with a nod.

……

Meanwhile, a steady stream of people was walking out of another stone hall elsewhere in the city, and before long, Qin Yuan and Feng Wuchen were the only ones left inside.

"You've been in seclusion this entire time, Wuchen. Have you made another breakthrough?" Qin Yuan asked with a smile.

"Indeed. Thanks to a culmination of many years of diligent cultivation, I was able to open another profound acupoint just yesterday," Feng Wuchen replied.

"Fantastic! That's a very good sign. A spot in the top three should be all but assured for you," Qin Yuan said as his smile widened even further.

However, Feng Wuchen's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he didn't appear to be all that pleased.

"What's wrong? Is there something on your mind?" Qin Yuan asked.

"For some reason, I can't shake the feeling that something's not quite right with this martial gathering, and it's making me a little uneasy," Feng Wuchen replied.

"Is it because you failed to secure a new weapon from Mistress Liu Hua? No matter how good a weapon is, it's still just an external aide. In the Scalptia Spatial Domain, the only thing that we can truly rely on is our physical bodies," Qin Yuan preached.

"You're right, Father. I must just be overthinking things," Feng Wuchen hurriedly replied.

"Having said that, it is rather surprising that Mistress Liu Hua refused to see you. Even when I personally went to pay him a visit, I was still shut out and refused an audience," Qin Yuan mused.

"Could it be because of those two from Green Goat City? Back when I first went to visit Mistress Liu Hua, Gu Qianxun suddenly pulled out some token, and they were granted an audience, while I was chased away. After that, I went to visit several more times, but I was shut out every single time," Feng Wuchen said.

"There's no way that a pair of rascals from Green Goat City could have so much sway and influence. I can only presume that Mistress Liu Hua is displeased with us for some other reason. I'll go visit him again after the martial gathering," Qin Yuan said.

"Regardless of whether it was because of those two, I'm definitely going to teach them a good lesson if I encounter them during this martial gathering. Gu Qianxun may require some effort for me to defeat, but that human..."

His voice trailed off here as a hint of cold killing intent flashed through his eyes.

……

At the same time, all of the cultivators of White Rock City were also gathered in a stone hall, while Sun Tu was delivering an address.

"The Five City Martial Gathering is about to commence, and all that I ask of you is that you do your best. At the very least, I want all of you to strive to make it out of the first round. Once we return to White Rock City, I'll present all of you with additional rewards based on your performances," Sun Tu declared.

"We'll be sure to give it our all," a gray-robed man immediately declared, and this sentiment was echoed by everyone else.

However, amid all of the raucous cheers, there was one sound that was rather out of place, and that was the sound of someone snoring.

The snores were coming from Fang Chan, who was seated to Sun Tu's left.

At this moment, he was laying sprawled out on a large chair, sleeping like a baby.

It seemed that he was having a great dream, and there was a blissful smile on his hideous face. Drool was dripping down from the corner of his mouth, and he occasionally smacked his lips together and muttered something unintelligible.

The more Sun Tu tried to rally his warriors, the louder Fang Chan's snores became, but everyone seemed to have already grown accustomed to this.

Right at this moment, Fang Chan suddenly opened his mouth slightly, and his snores became quieter, but also higher in pitch.

Before long, a burst of peculiar soundwaves were coming out of his mouth and nostrils, and the furniture in the stone hall began to tremble, following which everyone in the hall began to experience a numb and faint sensation.

"Here it comes again," everyone groaned.

A faint smile appeared on Sun Tu's face upon seeing this, and he flicked Fang Chan gently on the forehead.

Fang Chan shuddered as his eyes immediately sprang open, and he looked around at everyone with a dazed expression.

Sun Tu wiped the drool from the corner of his lips with his sleeve, then smiled as he reassured,, "Everything's fine, go back to sleep."

Fang Chan grinned in response, then got into a more comfortable position before quickly falling asleep again.

……

That night, the bright moon was hanging high up in the sky, and two figures were laying on the rooftop of a palace side by side in the city lord's manor, looking up at the starry night sky.

One of the two figures was none other than Zhu Ziyuan, the man who had claimed the top spot on several consecutive past editions of the Five City Martial Gathering leading up to this one.

He was accompanied by a stunningly beautiful woman wearing a suit of tight-fitting bone armor that hugged her alluring curves, and the woman complained in a quiet voice, "How could the city lord be so lazy and leave everything to you instead of addressing the combatants of our Profound City himself?"

"Ziqing, we're in the city lord's manor right now. No matter how quiet you are, City Lord E will still be able to hear you," Zhu Ziyuan said with an amused smile.

The woman was none other than Zhu Ziqing's younger sister, and she stuck out her tongue in a sheepish manner as she said, "The city lord is so kind and generous, he won't be bothered by something like this."

"This is your first time participating in the Five City Martial Gathering, so make sure to do your homework on all of the other city's combatants. Duan Tong from Excess Passage City..."

Before Zhi Ziyuan had a chance to finish, his sister interrupted him in a disgruntled fashion, "Alright, alright! This is already the seventh time you've said this! My ears are about to develop calluses if you keep this up!"

Chapter 902: Asura Arena

"Alright, in that case, tell me which of the combatants from the other cities you have to pay particular attention to," Zhu Ziyuan said.

"According to what you've told me, basically everyone outside of Green Goat City poses a threat, and I have to be on my guard against all of them," Zhu Ziqing sighed in an exasperated manner.

"That's incorrect. Gu Qianxun of Green Goat City is someone that you also have to be wary of. She may be a woman, but she still poses a very potent threat," Zhu Ziyuan said in a serious manner.

"Ah, yes, yes, yes, Green Goat City has Gu Qianxun. You worry way too much! How could I possibly have such terrible luck that I get matched up against all of the most powerful cultivators from the other cities?" Zhu Ziqing grumbled.

Zhu Ziyuan paid no heed to Zhu Ziqing's grips as he asked, "How do you think I was able to win the martial gathering on so many past consecutive occasions?"

"Of course it was because you're more powerful than everyone else," Zhu Ziqing replied without any thought.

"That was certainly a factor, but it's not the most important one. The most important thing is to take every opponent seriously. Aside from the opponents that we already know about, we have to make sure to be careful when battling the new faces as well," Zhu Ziyuan said with a serious expression.

A serious look finally appeared on Zhu Ziqing's face as well, and she nodded as she replied, "I'll be sure to keep that in mind."

Zhu Ziyuan didn't nag her any further upon seeing this, and the two of them returned to looking up at the starry night sky in silence.

However, only less than a minute had passed by when Zhu Ziyuan continued, "By the way, Feng Wuchen of Profound End City..."

"That's enough from you!"

……

In a vast desert countless kilometers away from Profound City, the wind was howling incessantly throwing up enormous clouds of sand up into the sky.

Under the moonlight, it was as if the entire area had been transformed into a realm of flowing sand.

At this moment, a series of massive black shadows were slowly traversing through the desert, and thanks to the moonlight, it was possible to make out that these black shadows were a series of enormous scaled beasts, at the forefront of which was a Black Scaled Elephant that was over a thousand feet tall and a little different in appearance from the average Black Scaled Elephant.

This Black Scaled Elephant's entire body was covered in a suit of armor, and there were seven or eight fist-sized beast cores embedded into the flesh in front of its chest in a circular arrangement.

The Black Scaled Elephant's tusks had been removed and replaced with a pair of shape spears that gave off a cold gleam under the moonlight.

What was most peculiar of all was that there was nothing but pitch black in the Black Scaled Elephant's eye sockets, and if one were to look closely, they would discover that there were clear signs of atrophy and shriveling in the flesh around its eye sockets.

This Black Scaled Elephant was nothing more than a withered carcass, and the same applied to the dozen or so enormous scaled beast trailing along behind it.

Each of these scaled beasts was carrying a black stone palace on their backs, and there were seven or eight lit braziers in the stone palace on the Black Scaled Elephant's back, illuminating the space inside.

At the center of the palace was a black stone platform that was around three feet in size, atop which sat a woman in a black dress with her legs crossed. She had an exceptional figure, and even though there was a thin veil over her face, just her side profile alone was already extremely captivating.

Seated on a black stone chair not far away from the woman was another woman that also had a black veil over her face. She was reclined against the chair like a seductive, boneless snake, and she asked in a gentle and lazy voice, "How long left until we reach Profound City?"

"Right now, we're still in the territory of our Puppet City. Barring any mishaps, we should reach Profound City within a month," the woman on the stone platform replied.

"Good. After all these years of preparation, the time has finally come," the woman reclining on the chair murmured to herself as she sat up with a bright gleam in her eyes.

……

The next morning.

As the first ray of sunlight passed over the Myriad Profound Mountain Range and shone down upon the city, there was already quite a lively and festive sight to behold.

All of the streets in the city were packed with people, all of whom were converging toward a massive round building at the center of the city. That was the largest arena in Profound City, and it was called the Asura Arena.

The plaza in front of the Asura Arena was already completely packed, and the statue at the center of the plaza was a massive attraction, with people constantly converging from all directions to touch its robes and feet.

It was said that touching this statue could bring good fortune, allowing them to make successful bets on the upcoming battles of the Five City Martial Gathering, so there were many parts of the statue's body that had already been polished smooth by countless hands over the years, and those parts gleamed particularly bright under the morning sun.

On top of that, there were even more people gathered in front of the gates of the Asura Arena, waiting for them to open.

Right at this moment, the sound of a gong being struck rang out in the distance, and the gates slowly opened, allowing the crowd to pour into the Asura Arena before spreading out to make their way toward the eight giant platforms inside.

At the same time, there were dozens of people gathered in a round hall deep underground beneath the Asura Arena, and they were roughly split up into five groups.

These were none other than the sixty-four combatants participating in the Five City Martial Gathering, and Han Li and Gu Qianxun were naturally among them.

"How is your Blood Plasma Wine coming along, Fellow Daoist Li?" Gu Qianxun asked as she approached Han Li, who was seated on his own in a corner.

Yi Liya had already grown accustomed to this, and he only took a glance in their direction before returning to his conversation with several other Green Goat City gladiators.

Xuanyuan Xing and Toxic Dragon were keeping their distance from Yi Liya's group, and the former appeared to be quite composed, while the latter was clearly a little anxious.

"It's coming along nicely. Congratulations on having your Black Tribulation Centipede removed, Fellow Daoist Gu," Han Li said with a smile.

"Mistress Liu Hua is a rather strange man, and for some reason, he insists on having you bring a piece of Heavenly Qilin Crystal to him. My apologies, but I can't really help you here," Gu Qianxun said in an apologetic manner.

"There's no reason why Senior Liu Hua should lend me his assistance free of charge, so it's only right that he asks for something in return. I can only hope that the Heavenly Qilin Crystal isn't reserved for too high a placing," Han Li said with a smile.

"I can tell you now that the Heavenly Qilin Crystal is a reward reserved for the top three, so I think you have very good chances," Gu Qianxun said through voice transmission.

"You certainly think very highly of me, Fellow Daoist Gu," Han Li chuckled. "For the sake of my own survival, I have no choice but to give it my best."

As the two of them were chatting with each other, the entire surrounding space abruptly shuddered as a burst of rumbling rang out from directly up ahead.

Five openings then appeared on the thick and sturdy wall up ahead, revealing five stone staircases that led up to the surface.

"Please welcome the gladiators from the five cities!" a loud voice announced from up above, and the gladiators of Profound City were led up one of the five staircases by Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing.

The other groups in the underground hall also followed suit, making their way up to the surface, where they were immediately overwhelmed by waves of thunderous cheers.

In particular, a few names were being chanted very loudly.

"Zhu Ziyuan, Zhu Ziyuan..."

"Feng Wuchen, Feng Wuchen..."

……

Even though Han Li had fought in many arena battles back in Green Goat City, this was the first time that he felt stunned by the cheering of the spectators, and he could feel his own blood beginning to boil in his veins.

There were a total of eight platforms in the arena, all of which were separated by a distance of over a thousand feet, and at the moment, five of them were occupied by the gladiators from the five cities.

There was an extra person on the platform where the Profound City gladiators were gathered, namely a tall and imposing man with a pair of ox horns on his head, and he was the host of the event.

At the center of the area between the eight platforms was an elevated platform that was over a thousand feet tall, upon which were placed six black stone chairs.

These chairs were clearly reserved for the lords of the five cities, but for some reason, there was an extra chair.

"Please be quiet while the city lords enter the arena," the horned man declared, and the entire arena instantly fell completely silent.

Immediately thereafter, six figures plummeted out of the sky before crashing down onto the elevated platform with a resounding boom.

The entire arena shuddered violently as the six figures were revealed.

Everyone looked up to discover City Lord E Kuai standing at the forefront of the group, while the other figures were arranged in a row slightly behind him.

Despite his unremarkable physical appearance, there was an air of regal majesty surrounding City Lord E Kuai that made him resemble an almighty lion, and many of the spectators in the stands involuntarily lowered their heads.

A hint of befuddlement flashed through Han Li's eyes at the sight of the six figures on the elevated platform.

In addition to the five city lords, there was one more person present, someone that was quite familiar to Han Li.

It was Mistress Liu Hua!

Chapter 903: Extravagant Rewards

Han Li had always known that Mistress Liu Hua possessed a very lofty status, but he still wasn't expecting to see Mistress Liu Hua in such a prominent position during such an important occasion.

"Welcome to Profound City, everyone. In this arena, we will witness the rise of the next champion of the Five City Martial Gathering!" E Kuai declared in a thunderous voice, and a wave of raucous cheers instantly rang out in response.

It was as if the entire arena had exploded, and E Kuai allowed the cheers to go on for a while before raising his hands to make a quieting gesture.

After that, he delivered a brief address, then sat down onto the chair behind him, and the other five men with him sat down as well.

Right at this moment, the horned host stepped forward and declared, "For this edition of the Five City Martial Gathering, one-on-one battles will take place between the sixty-four elite gladiators selected from the five cities. There will be six rounds of competition, at the end of which the king of the arena will be crowned.

“All those who make it into the top eight will receive a B tier scaled beast core, while those who reach the final four will each receive an A tier beast core."

This announcement only further added to the excitement among the spectators, and all of the combatants on the platforms were also very excited to hear this. After all, A and B tier scaled beast cores were all extremely precious cultivation resources.

"Additionally, those who make it into the top three will each receive a piece of Heavenly Qilin Crystal, and extremely rare, premium material for pill and tool refinement purposes," the horned man continued, eliciting a surprised reaction from the spectators.

It had been many years since a Heavenly Qilin Crystal had last appeared in Profound City.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he was thinking to himself that securing a spot in the top three shouldn't be too difficult.

"You're really going all out, aren't you, City Lord E Kuai? Such a reward would've been something that only the champion would be worthy of in past editions. Does it not pain you to offer such extravagant rewards?" Sun Tu asked with an amused smile.

"All of us are citizens of Profound City, so regardless of who claims the rewards, it won't make any difference," E Kuai replied with a smile of his own.

Right at this moment, the horned man continued, "The second place finisher will receive a suit of Scaled Bone Profound Star Armor personally crafted by Mistress Liu Hua. This suit of armor was refined by Mistress Liu Hua in recent years, and 1,236 star bones of different sizes were used to create it, accompanied by various precious materials that are no less precious than Heavenly Qilin Crystal, so it's no exaggeration to call it a priceless treasure."

The spectators immediately erupted into a frenzy upon hearing this, and even the likes of Feng Wuchen had reflexively stood up a little straighter.

Han Li cast his gaze toward Mistress Liu Hua, finally realizing how the latter had been aware that Heavenly Qilin Crystal was one of the prizes for the martial gathering.

In the wake of this announcement, everyone present was speculating about what the first place prize could be.

However, no one could come up with an answer as there was barely anything that could be found in the Scalptia Spatial Domain that could be considered more precious.

Right as everyone was speculating among themselves, the horned man declared, "The first place finisher will receive a Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud."

In contrast with the previous two items, the horned man had only announced the name of this item without any accompanying explanation, and the spectator stands remained completely silent as no one had any idea what this was.

However, on the elevated platform, the expressions of all four subsidiary city lords had changed drastically.

"Is that true, City Lord E Kuai?" Chen Yang couldn't help but ask, and the other city lords turned to E Kuai as well.

"That's right," City Lord E Kuai confirmed with a nod. "The reward for the first place finisher will be a Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud."

"I've heard that this cloud harbors unfathomable bloodline power that can instantly open profound acupoints in one's body upon ingestion, even without the need of a bodily refinement cultivation art, and it leaves no trace behind in its wake," Chen Yang mused with a stunned expression.

"It's not that brilliant. It can open profound acupoints, but not endlessly with no limits. The human body can only tolerate so much Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud, and excessive absorption will result in self-detonation," E Kuai explained with a smile.

"Even so, this is still an extraordinary thing..."

E Kuai made no effort to keep this voice down, and all of the representatives of the five cities possessed exceptional hearing, so they were able to hear what he had said, and looks of astonishment and yearning had appeared on their faces.

In contrast, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he wasn't all that interested in this Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud.

After all, he was able to open profound acupoints far faster than others, so in contrast with the Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud, the Heavenly Qilin Crystal was actually more alluring to him.

At the same time, some of the more knowledgeable individuals in the spectator stands had revealed the effects of Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud, and all of the spectators gradually erupted into a frenzy once again as this information began to spread.

After waiting for some time for the commotion to die down, the horned man continued, "The first round of the Five City Martial Gathering will consist of thirty-two battles, with four batches of eight concurrent battles taking place at a time. All thirty-two battles will take place today, and those who advance will fight in the next round seven days later. No, without further ado, I present the pairings for the first round."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a gray stone wall that was several hundred feet tall slowly rose up from the ground to the left of the elevated platform, and there were four columns laid out on it, with eight matchups displayed in each column.

Han Li took a glance at the stone wall to discover that his and Gu Qianxun's names were absent from the first column, but Tu Gang and Sun Binghe's names were displayed.

Sun Binghe was facing a gladiator from Profound End City who neither Gu Qianxun nor Chen Yang had mentioned before, so he most likely wasn't a particularly formidable opponent. Unfortunately for Tu Gang, his first round opponent was Duan Tong of Excess Passage City.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li found his own name in the second column, and he was set to fight a gladiator by the name of Xu Shun from White Rock City.

Right at this moment, Gu Qianxun's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Looks like both of our battles are part of the second batch, Brother Li. Having said that, the platforms that we're on are quite far away from each other, so we most likely won't be able to spectate each other's battles."

Sure enough, Gu Qianxun's name was also in the second column, and she was battling a gladiator by the name of Wang Zhi from Profound End City.

"Have you heard of this Xu Shun before?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"I recall seeing him once in a past edition of the Five City Martial Gathering, but I don't think he did very well. Having said that, all of the people here have been selected to represent their cities, so none of them should be taken lightly," Gu Qianxun replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then inspected all of the thirty-two matchups for the first round, following which he remarked, "What a coincidence! No cultivators from the same city have been pitted against each other, and none of the hot favorites have been matched up against one another, either."

"That's intentional, and it's always been like this in past editions of the martial gathering. The rule of no cultivators from the same city fighting against each other only applies in the first round. After that, different numbers of cultivators will progress from each city, so it may not be possible to continue enforcing that rule.

“For example, if all twelve of one city's representatives manage to progress to the second round, then there's a good chance that some of them will have to fight one of their own. In order to ensure that none of the hot favorites are prematurely eliminated, matchups between them will generally only start taking place in the quarterfinals," Gu Qianxun explained.

Right at this moment, the horned man's voice rang out once again.

"All gladiators in the first column, please go to your assigned platforms. Everyone else, return to the lobby to wait, and spectators can begin placing their bets now. The battles will commence in fifteen minutes."

Han Li and the others began to depart, while the spectators hurriedly rose to their feet to go and place their bets at the nearest betting stations.

The Asura Arena was so enormous that even if one had a seat that was very high up, it was completely impossible to spectate all eight matches at the same time. Hence, after placing their bets, the spectators generally sat down in the nearest seat to await the commencement of the first round.

The lobby was a ring-shaped passageway beneath the spectator stands that ran along virtually the entire circumference of the Asura Arena, and there were windows in the lobby, so as long as one was willing to make the trek, they would be able to see every platform outside.

Aside from the sixteen combatants in the first column, all of the other gladiators had returned to the lobby.

All of the Green Goat City cultivators who had ties with Tu Gang and Sun Binghe had gathered around the windows that would allow them to see the platforms where those two were fighting.

"What terrible luck for Fellow Daoist Tu Gang to encounter Duan Tong in the first round. Looks like he won't be making it out of the first round..." one of the Green Goat City cultivators sighed.

"This was always bound to happen to one of us. Besides, even if we encounter opponents a little weaker than Duan Tong, it's not like any of us stand much of a chance anyway, so we're not in any better position ourselves," someone else sighed.

"Quit being so pessimistic! We still have Fellow Daoist Yi, don't we? Speaking of which, where is he?"

Only then did everyone discover that Yi Liya seemed to have suddenly disappeared.

In an empty area of the lobby, Yi Liya was walking alongside a tall and imposing middle-aged man, and the two were having a quiet conversation.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Yi. You've made some significant strides in your cultivation base since our last meeting. I must say, I'm feeling very envious," the middle-aged man said with a smile.

"You're far too kind, Brother Xu. Let's not waste any time, I've come to you because I have something to ask of you," Yi Liya said.

"Go ahead," the middle-aged man prompted.

"Your opponent today is Li Feiyu, and he's from our Green Goat City. I want you to..."

Yi Liya's voice trailed off here as he made a throat-slitting motion with his hand.

As it turned out, this middle-aged man was none other than Xu Shun of White Rock City, Han Li's first round opponent.

Chapter 904: Intent to Kill

"Oh? Is there some bad blood between the two of you?" Xu Shun asked with an intrigued expression.

"That's not something you need to know about, Brother Xu. Just be assured that I'll compensate you handsomely once the deed is done," Yi Liya promised with a smile.

"I'm not opposed to the idea, but what am I dealing with here?" Xu Shun asked.

"I just so happen to be in seclusion during the time that Li Feiyu joined the arena, so I've never personally seen him in action. However, I've heard that he's only opened fewer than fifty profound acupoints, but apparently, he's a very capable fighter," Yi Liya said.

"Fewer than fifty? How is it possible that he's been selected for the Five City Martial Gathering then?" Xu Shun asked with a skeptical expression.

"Perhaps he's opened more profound acupoints that he's displayed, but it won't be too many more. If you ask me, I think he's only been allowed to take part in the Five City Martial Gathering thanks to personal relationship with our new city lord. I've heard that it was our new city lord that brought him into our city in the first place," Yi Liya explained.

"Are you referring to Chen Yang? I see. In that case, I can definitely help you out," Xu Shun said.

"Oh, by the way, the cultivation art that he's using seems to be primarily focused on his legs, so he may have a speed advantage over you. Make sure to keep that in mind," Yi Liya cautioned.

"Rest assured, even if he's opened ten more profound acupoints than he's displayed, there's no way he'll be a match for me. Now then, let's talk about how you're going to compensate me," Xu Shun said with a snide grin.

……

Fifteen minutes quickly passed by, and the first batch of battles commenced.

Han Li, Gu Qianxun, Toxic Dragon, and Xuanyuan Xing were all gathered at the window directly facing the platform that Tu Gang was on, and at this moment, Tu Gang and Duan Tong were already on the platform, facing each other from afar.

Tu Gang was observing Duan Tong with a hint of fear in his eyes, intermingled with hesitation and indignation.

In contrast, Duan Tong remained completely expressionless, and he wasn't displaying any derision toward his opponent. However, for some reason, Tu Gang felt as if Duan Tong were completely looking past him, as if he didn't exist, and that was certainly not a good feeling.

A black-robed elderly man was serving as the referee for their platform, and he stood between the two of them as he said, "There are no rules in this battle. You can surrender at any time, and if you don't, then you're responsible for your own life."

Tu Gang and Duan Tong nodded in response, and the elderly man jumped down from the platform.

The two combatants each cupped a fist in a salute toward the other, and the battle commenced.

On top of the elevated platform in between the eight battle platforms, the five city lords and Mistress Liu Hua were conversing casually with one another, seemingly not displaying much interest in the ongoing battles.

All of the profound acupoints on Tu Gang's body lit up one after another as he seized the initiative, charging directly toward Duan Tong, and each footstep of his was extremely forceful, causing the entire platform to rumble violently.

Thankfully, the ground was fortified using star bones, so it managed to remain intact beneath his thundering footsteps.

After charging forward close to twenty steps in succession, he had built up tremendous momentum, and his aura had been elevated to its peak. His right arm was glowing golden under the light of the sun, and he threw a punch at Duan Tong with all his might.

Duan Tong remained completely still on the spot as he observed the oncoming Tu Gang, and only as Tu Gang began to lash out with his fist did Duan Tong slowly take a step back.

A cold gleam flashed through his eyes as he retaliated with his own fist, and a series of profound acupoints lit up over his arm as the two fists clashed with an earth-shattering boom.

A burst of tremendous shockwaves erupted in all directions, and Duan Tong remained as still as an immovable mountain, while Tu Gang let loose an agonized cry as several of the profound acupoints on his arm exploded in unison.

At the same time, the sound of shattering bones rang out from his arm, and he was sent flying all the way back until he fell out of the platform altogether, and by the time he landed on the ground, he had already fallen unconscious.

A wave of thunderous cheers instantly rang out from the nearby spectators, and the attention of the five city lords and Mistress Liu Hua was also drawn to the scene.

"It seems like Duan Tong has become even more powerful since I last saw him, Fellow Daoist Fu," E Kuai remarked with a smile.

"He's made some minor improvements over the years, but he's still far from being able to match Fellow Daoist Ziyuan," Fu Jian replied.

"Even though his opponent wasn't particularly strong, winning the battle with just a single blow is still very impressive," Qin Yuan praised.

Everyone was praising Duan Tong, but Chen Yang remained silent, and even though his expression remained composed and unchanged, he was clenching his fists so tightly within his sleeves that his knuckles had turned white.

Inside the lobby, all of the Green Goat City cultivators were looking on with grim expressions. Even though they weren't the ones who had been defeated, seeing one of their own being crushed in such brutal fashion was still terrible for overall morale. Everyone began walking away while sighing to themselves and shaking their heads, while only Han Li and Gu Qianxun remained standing in front of the window.

Han Li watched as Tu Gang was carried away, and he asked, "What did you think of that battle, Fellow Daoist Gu?"

"Duan Tong has already become far more powerful since I last faced him. In the face of Tu Gang's Titan Vajra Arts, he didn't even use his right arm, only using his left arm instead to defeat Tu Gang with a single blow. It's clear that in his eyes, Tu Gang isn't even a worthy opponent," Gu Qianxun replied with slightly furrowed brows.

"That's not entirely true. As he unleashed that punch, he borrowed some power from his right arm. Otherwise, Tu Gang wouldn't have suffered such a crushing defeat. In any case, there's a huge power gap between the two," Han Li said.

"Indeed. If only he could've forced Duan Tong to reveal more of his tricks," Gu Qianxun sighed.

"What's happened has already happened, let's begin preparing as well. The second batch of battles is about to commence soon," Han Li said with a smile.

"Let's go," Gu Qianxun replied with a nod.

……

Around fifteen minutes later, the first batch of eight battles drew to a conclusion, and unsurprisingly, Sun Binghe was also defeated.

After a half-hour break, during which all of the bets were paid out, the second batch of battles commenced.

Close to half of the Green Goat City cultivators were chalked down to have their first battles, and that included Han Li, Gu Qianxun, and Yi Liya.

All of the remaining Green Goat City cultivators had gone to spectate Gu Qianxun and Yi Liya's battle, including even Toxic Dragon, so there were only a few White Rock City cultivators watching Han Li's battle.

Neither Li Feiyu nor Xu Shun were particularly renowned figures, so there weren't many spectators in the stands near their platform. There were still some people watching, but far fewer than at some of the other platforms.

However, there was a familiar figure seated in the spectator stands, and that was Daoist Xie.

At this moment, Han Li and Xu Shun were standing across from each other on their platform, and a black-robed referee announced the rules of the battle before declaring the battle's commencement.

However, neither Han Li nor Xu Shun made an immediate move, and the two of them continued to stand still on the spot, observing each other from afar.

Before long, a chorus of boos began to ring out from the spectator stands.

Xu Shun was sizing up Han Li with a peculiar look in his eyes. He couldn't see anything remarkable about Han Li, but he couldn't help but lick his lips as he thought of the compensation that Yi Liya had promised.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. It was clear that Xu Shun was coming into this battle with intent to kill, so Han Li was not going to be holding back.

Right at this moment, a series of profound acupoints suddenly lit up on the soles of Xu Shun's feet, and he sprang up into the air before charging directly at Han Li.

Using the momentum of his descent, he sharply elevated his own speed, reaching Han Li in the blink of an eye.

By the time he descended upon Han Li, he had already built up significant momentum, but just like Duan Tong in his battle against Tu Gang, Han Li remained completely still on the spot.

However, right as Xu Shun's fist was about to strike him, he abruptly vanished from the spot, leaving Xu Shun to look on in bewilderment.

He knew that he was in trouble, and he immediately began plummeting toward the ground even faster, trying to reach the ground below as soon as possible so that he would have some purchase to change directions.

However, before he was about to reach the ground, Han Li appeared before him in a wraith-like manner, and close to twenty profound acupoints lit up over his legs in unison as he aimed a vicious knee strike at Xu Shun's chest.

Xu Shun was astonished by Han Li's speed, and he hurriedly crossed his arms in front of himself for protection, but his arms were driven back into his chest by the force of Han Li's knee strike, sending him flying back through the air.

Immediately thereafter, the profound acupoints on Han Li's legs began to glow even brighter as he caught up to Xu Shun in mid-air in the blink of an eye, then slammed a fist down onto his spine.

Xu Shun plummeted down onto the ground, then bounced up and down thrice before tumbling away to the side.

All of this had taken in the span of just several seconds, much to the amazement of the nearby spectators.

There was some occasional interest displayed by the people on the elevated platform, but that was only limited to an occasional glance here or there.

After all, the two combatants hadn't displayed anywhere near enough profound acupoints to truly attract their interest, so it was like watching a fight between children.

Only Chen Yang's gaze would occasionally linger on that platform for a while, but there wasn't any concern in his eyes.

Instead of pressing his advantage, Han Li drew to a halt, then asked through voice transmission, "We've never even met before, why is it that you displayed clear intent to kill me as soon as the battle commenced?"

Chapter 905: Killing Blow

"Looks like I may have underestimated you a little," Xu Shun scoffed instead of answering Han Li's question, then spat out a globule of bloodstained saliva onto the ground.

He stood up straight, then shook out his arms, and a string of loud cracks and pops rang out from his joints.

Han Li remained still on the spot upon seeing this, and a cold look flashed through his eyes.

Xu Shun let loose a thunderous roar as he crouched down slightly before launching himself at Han Li again.

At this point, a total of seventy-eight profound acupoints had lit up over his body, and they seemed to be resonating with one another, creating a membrane of light similar to a True Extreme Film over his entire body.

Instead of taking evasive measures, Han Li took a step forward to face Xu Shun head-on, and several profound acupoints lit up over his arms, causing the platform beneath his feet to shudder violently.

As he continued to step forward, more and more profound acupoints lit up on his arms, while the platform beneath him continued to shudder and quake.

A hint of fear finally appeared in Xu Shun's eyes at the sight of the ever-increasing number of profound acupoints on Han Li's body, and he didn't know if Yi Liya had intentionally deceived, or if his sources had been incorrect as well.

The distance between the two of them was rapidly shrinking, and Han Li let loose an explosive roar as he unleashed Tu Gang's Titan Vajra Arts, revealing all eighteen of the profound acupoints on his arms.

At this point, it was already too late for Xu Shun to turn back, so he could only inject all of his power into his fist.

A pair of profound acupoints lit up on the end of his fist in unison, giving off a resplendent gleam as it crashed toward Han Li's right fist.

Right as the two fists were about to clash, a white bone spike suddenly shot out from the gap between Xu Shun's middle and index fingers.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and he displayed no intention of taking any evasive measures.

Instead, he slightly extended the two fingers on his hand that had been refined from the Flower Branch domain, sending them crashing into the star bone that Xu Shun had concealed between his fingers.

A violent explosion rang out, accompanied by a sound akin to that of shattering ice crystals.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and all that the spectators could see was a vast expanse of radiant starlight, making it impossible for them to make out the two combatants on the platform.

However, in this instant, Xu Shun was clearly able to see the near-hundred profound acupoints that had lit up over Han Li's body, and his heart was filled with remorse and resentment.

He wanted to surrender, but it was already too late.

Han Li charged forward and plunged his fist through Xu Shun's dantian, destroying the nascent soul inside.

At this point, the six people on the elevated platform had also had their attention drawn to the massive explosion that had just taken place, but all they saw was Han Li stumbling back out of the eruption of starlight, while Xu Shun's lifeless body fell to the ground.

All of the spectators were astonished by what they had just witnessed, which was the first casualty of this edition of the Five City Martial Gathering.

I didn't know you were such a good actor, Fellow Daoist Li... Chen Yang chuckled internally as he watched Han Li make a show of stumbling to the ground.

Both he and Daoist Xie were fully aware that Han Li was only putting on an act.

……

Moments later, Han Li was carried away by two armored guards for treatment.

However, on the way there, Han Li sat up on his own and revealed that he was actually completely unscathed.

After that, he sat down in a quiet corner as a cold gleam flashed through his eyes.

As time passed, the other seven battles also concluded one after another, and aside from Gu Qianxun and Yi Liya, the other two Green Goat City gladiators both suffered heavy defeats. Thankfully, they were able to surrender in a timely fashion, so they had survived their battles.

Gu Qianxun's opponent from Profound End City was a far inferior cultivator to her, and he was beaten halfway to death by just two or three blows from Gu Qianxun. Fortunately for him, she had no intention of killing him, and she allowed him to surrender the battle.

As for Yi Liya, he also displayed very impressive power, displaying only seventy profound acupoints to defeat a cultivator from Excess Passage City that had opened eighty profound acupoints. In the end, he was able to knock his opponent unconscious to secure the victory.

As the two of them returned to the lobby, all of the Green Goat City cultivators immediately gathered around to congratulate them.

Yi Liya returned to the lobby with an elated expression, and his elation was only further heightened by the absence of Han Li in the crowd.

A snide grin appeared on his face as he asked, "Where's Fellow Daoist Li? Wasn't he fighting earlier as well?"

"All eight battles are already over, but I haven't seen him come back..."

Toxic Dragon had been watching Gu Qianxun's battle this entire time, and only now did he notice Han Li's absence.

"He must've been carried away for treatment," a Green Goat City cultivator said.

"I'm not sure about that. I heard that one of the two combatants on his platform died..." another Green Goat City cultivator said, and his voice trailed off into a grim silence.

Yi Liya's smile widened even further upon hearing this, while Gu Qianxun's brows had become tightly furrowed.

Right at this moment, Xuanyuan Xing suddenly called out, "Fellow Daoist Li!"

Everyone turned to discover Han Li limping his way into the lobby with his robes in tatters, and the pleased smile on Yi Liya's face instantly turned to shock upon seeing this.

"Did you win, Fellow Daoist Li?" everyone asked as they gathered around him.

"I was very fortunate to have come out on top," Han Li replied with a smile, and a faint smile appeared on Gu Qianxun's face as well.

Han Li intentionally made his way past Yi Liya as he continued, "However, Xu Shun was not so fortunate."

For some reason, a chill ran down Yi Liya's spine, even though Han Li hadn't even taken a single glance at him this entire time.

……

Before long, all thirty-two battles of the first round had drawn to a conclusion.

There were no unexpected upsets, so there were no dark horses stealing the spotlight, nor had any of the hot favorites been prematurely eliminated. Having said that, there were still some interesting stories to have come out of the first round, the most amusing one of which was that Zhu Ziyuan's opponent for the first round had surrendered as soon as their battle began, making it the fastest battle in this edition of the martial gathering thus far.

Han Li and Gu Qianxun had been hoping to witness Zhu Ziyuan in action in his battle, but that plan obviously fell through.

After that, Han Li went to watch Toxic Dragon's battle against Zhu Ziqing.

Even though Zhu Ziqing was a woman who was only participating in the Five City Martial Gathering for the first time, her overall power was superior to Toxic Dragon, and even though she made some slight errors here and there, she was still ultimately able to emerge victorious.

What was rather surprising to Han Li was that Xuanyuan Xing, who had always kept a low profile, had managed to defeat a cultivator from Profound End City, joining Han Li, Gu Qianxun, and Yi Liya as the only four Green Goat City cultivators to reach the second round.

Green Goat City had only claimed four of the top thirty-two spots, which was the worst total out of all of the five cities, but thankfully, there had been no casualties.

……

Seven days flew by in a flash, and the second round of the Five City Martial Gathering commenced.

Countless citizens of Profound City flooded into the Asura Arena once again, followed by the representatives of the five cities.

The Green Goat City cultivators had also arrived at the venue, and due to their lackluster performance in the first round, Green Goat City had been made into a laughingstock, so there were many people pointing and jeering at them along the way.

All of the defeated Green Goat City cultivators could only trudge along with embarrassed expressions, while Chen Yang was also looking far from pleased, not just because of what had happened in the first round, but also because Han Li and the others were all facing formidable foes in their second round battles.

After entering the lobby, Chen Yang led everyone to a secluded area, then said, "Don't get too hung up over the results of the first round. There's a significant element of luck involved there, and it's not necessarily a bad thing to be made aware of your own shortcomings. From here onward, focus on spectating the rest of the battles. This is a very rare opportunity that I want all of you to make the most of."

He then turned his gaze to Gu Qianxun as he continued, "Fellow Daoist Gu, your opponent for today is Zhu Ziqing of Profound City. She is Zhu Ziyuan's sister, and even though she's nowhere near as powerful as him, I still want you to take her seriously."

"I'll be sure to do so, City Lord Chen," Gu Qianxun replied with a nod.

"Fellow Daoist Li, Hao Feng is Profound End City's second-most powerful representative, second only to Feng Wuchen, and my sources tell me that he's already opened more than a hundred profound acupoints. He was also able to reach the final eight during the last edition of the martial gathering, so be on your guard," Chen Yang continued.

Han Li merely nodded in response.

"As for Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan, your opponent for this round is Wu Cong of Excess Passage City. His powers rank in the top five among the Excess Passage City representatives, so just do your best," Chen Yang said, clearly not placing any high hopes in Xuanyuan Xing.

Xuanyuan Xing wasn't disgruntled by this at all, and he cupped his fist in a salute as he declared, "Rest assured, I'll be sure to give it everything that I have!"

Chapter 906: Agreement for the Next Round

Chen Yang gave Xuanyuan Xing a slight nod, then turned his gaze to Yi Liya, who was also looking back at him with a calm expression.

"Yi Liya, you have the toughest opponent of all today. Your opponent is Feng Wuchen of Profound End City. Not only is he the most powerful representative of Profound End City, he also placed in the top four during the previous martial gathering, so..."

A proud smile appeared on Yi Liya's face as he cut Chen Yang off and interjected, "Rest assured, City Lord Chen, Feng Wuchen is a tough opponent, but I've already thought of a strategy against him, so I'm not without chances."

Chen Yang was a little displeased at being cut off, but he didn't show it as he nodded in response.

"Feng Wuchen is an extremely formidable cultivator that even I may not be able to defeat, so don't be careless, Fellow Daoist Yi," Gu Qianxun warned.

Yi Liya's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he replied in an indifferent manner, "Thank you for the cautionary words, Fellow Daoist Gu."

This entire time, Han Li didn't even bother to take a single glance at Yi Liya, and it was as if he hadn't heard the conversation taking place between Yi Liya and Chen Yang at all.

After lecturing the four combatants for a while longer, Chen Yang departed to make his way toward the elevated platform reserved for the city lords.

As soon as Chen Yang departed, Yi Liya strode over to Han Li and said, "You better not lose this round, Fellow Daoist Li. That way, we'll be able to face each other in the next round."

"Likewise, I hope you can defeat Feng Wuchen, Fellow Daoist Yi," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

Indeed, the arrangement of the bracket meant that Han Li would be facing one of Yi Liya or Feng Wuchen if he could successfully progress to the next round.

Yi Liya gave a cold harrumph upon hearing this, then made his way back to Tu Gang and the others, while Han Li sat down on the spot with his legs crossed and closed his eyes to rest.

By the time Chen Yang arrived on the elevated platform, the other four city lords were already there, but for some reason, Mistress Liu Hua was absent.

"My sincerest apologies, City Lord Chen. Your Green Goat City only has four people left, and after this round, at least two more will be eliminated. I wanted to give one of you representatives a free win as a gesture of goodwill, but neither Feng Wuchen nor Hao Feng were willing to surrender their battles, and I couldn't just force them into doing so," Qin Yuan said.

"I appreciate the thought, City Lord Qin, but the Five City Martial Gathering has always produced its fair share of surprises, so who's to say what the outcome of the battles will be?" Chen Yang replied with a smile.

"I admire your composure, City Lord Chen. Let's wait and see then," Qin Yuan said with a faint smile.

Fu Jian and Sun Tu sat in silence, displaying no interest in the conversation taking place between Chen Yang and Qin Yuan.

"It's time, let's begin," City Lord E Kuai declared, and the horned man standing beside him immediately nodded in response before jumping down from the elevated platform to the center of the Asura Arena.

"I'm sure all of you are still buzzing from the spectacular first round that took place seven days ago. Today, the excitement continues with the much-anticipated second round! The rules of this round will be the same as the previous ones, with sixteen total battles held in two batches," the horned man announced, and the gray stone wall slowly began to rise up once again.

This time, there were only thirty-two names and two columns on the stone wall, laying out the matchups for the second round.

Han Li and Yi Liya had their battles in the first batch, while Gu Qianxun and Xuanyuan Xing were scheduled to fight in the second batch.

Yi Liya strode over to his platform in silence, followed by Tu Gang and the others, while Han Li took a deep breath to brace himself for the upcoming battle.

"Good luck, Fellow Daoist Li," Gu Qianxun said.

"Indeed, best of luck to you, Fellow Daoist Li," Xuanyuan Xing chimed in with a friendly smile.

Han Li gave the two of them a faint smile, then made his way onto his platform, where a black-robed referee was already standing.

Han Li gave the referee a slight nod, then took a casual glance at his surroundings to discover that there were far more spectators gathered nearby than for his first round battle, but most of them were from Profound End City, so they were clearly supporters of Hao Feng.

Right at his moment, a gray shadow abruptly appeared on the platform across from Han Li at an astonishing speed.

It was a gray-robed figure that was as thin as a bamboo pole, and he was holding a strange serpentine sword with a layer of viscous green light flashing over its blade.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he thought back to the information that Chen Yang had gathered on Hao Feng.

Just like Feng Wuchen, Hao Feng's cultivation arts were also mostly focused leg cultivation, thereby granting him tremendous speed, and his Green Snake Sword also contained the venom of some type of powerful scaled snake that could directly erode one's profound acupoints.

Hao Feng was also observing Han Li, and he said in a raspy voice, "Li Feiyu, I watched your battle against Xu Shun. Your acting may have been able to fool others, but you didn't fool me."

"I'm honored that you watched my battle," Han Li replied in an expressionless manner.

"I can tell you're a powerful cultivator, and you've hidden your powers well, but it's very unfortunate for you that you had to encounter me. I suggest you surrender this match, it'll be the wisest decision you'll ever make," Hao Feng continued.

"My apologies, but I have no intention of surrendering this match," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

A cold look flashed through Hao Feng's eyes upon hearing this.

"Fine! I gave you a chance!"

"Begin!" the black-robed referee announced, and over a hundred profound acupoints instantly lit up over Hao Feng's body, enshrouding his entire body in brilliant white radiance.

In particular, around forty to fifty of those profound acupoints were gathered in his legs.

The white light radiating from those profound acupoints converged to form a pair of serpentine projections, making it appear as if he had a pair of white snakes underfoot.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and seventy-two of his profound acupoints lit up in unison.

Before he had a chance to do anything else, a cold sneer appeared on Hao Feng's face, and he abruptly vanished from the spot, leaving only a trail of glowing white afterimages in his wake.

In the next instant, a green sword projection appeared directly in front of Han Li, piercing toward his chest, while Han Li remained rooted to the spot, seemingly having completely failed to react.

All of the nearby spectators were immediately put on the edge of their seats upon seeing this.

Was this already going to be the end of the battle?

However, after the Green Snake Sword pierced through Han Li's body, not even a single drop of blood was shed, and he quickly dissipated from the spot, revealing himself to be nothing more than an afterimage.

Right at this moment, the powerful gust of wind swept toward Hao Feng from behind as Han Li appeared behind him without any warning. All of his Wingform Ascension Arts profound acupoints were glowing radiantly, and he was making a grab for Hao Feng with one hand.

Hao Feng was quite startled by this turn of events, and he didn't have time to turn around, so he could only lash out behind himself with his Green Snake Sword, sending a wave of green sword projections sweeping toward Han Li.

All of the sword projections were as fast as lightning, and they sped toward Han Li with tremendous power.

Han Li immediately clenched his outstretched hand into a fist, and a layer of golden light emerged over his arm as he threw a punch at the oncoming green sword projections.

A resounding boom rang out as a burst of radiant golden light erupted from Han Li's right arm, instantly tearing through the wave of green sword projections.

Hao Feng shuddered violently as he was forced back a step, and he looked down to discover that a layer of golden fur had appeared over Han Li's fist, leaving several white marks on the edge of his Green Snake Sword.

Hao Feng harrumphed coldly as his body abruptly dissipated into a series of white afterimages, and in the blink of an eye, he was behind Han Li, thrusting his Green Snake Sword toward Han Li's back.

However, Han Li was able to turn around in time to throw another punch into the Green Snake Sword, forcing back Hao Feng once again.

In the wake of his two consecutive failed attacks, Hao Feng was beginning to grow a little agitated, and he quickly accelerated to his top speed, conjuring up layers upon layers of afterimages that connected together to form what appeared to be a giant white serpent rapidly coiling around Han Li.

At the same time, gusts of fierce wind swept through the air, forming a tornado that was over a hundred feet in size around Han Li.

"Fellow Daoist Hao Feng is using his Snake Shadow Movement Technique! There's no way Li Feiyu will be able to survive this time!" a spectator from Profound End City exclaimed in an excited manner.

A series of green sword projections shot out of the surrounding tornado, targeting several of Han Li's vital regions at once.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, then casually threw a punch forward, and a burst of tremendous power erupted out of his fist in all directions.

All of the surrounding sword projections were instantly stopped in their tracks as if they had struck an invisible wall, following which they abruptly shattered with a resounding boom, while the surrounding tornado also exploded.

Chapter 907: Fierce Battle

Hao Feng stumbled out into the open with a stunned look on his face, and before he had a chance to steady himself, Han Li appeared right in front of him in a wraith-like manner, then thrust his right index finger toward Hao Feng's heart.

A burst of tremendous power erupted out of his fingertip, causing the nearby space to tremble and screech.

Hao Feng knew that if he were to allow Han Li's finger to strike him, a hole would instantly be pierced into his heart, even with his True Extreme Film protecting himself.

With that in mind, he hurriedly lashed out with his Green Snake Sword, unleashing around a dozen sword projections that swept toward Han Li's arm.

However, all of a sudden, Han Li's finger veered off its original trajectory, and at the same time, he extended his middle finger as well, reaching into the mass of sword projections to pluck the Green Snake Sword between his fingers with unerring accuracy.

Immediately thereafter, he made a twisting motion with his wrist, and the Green Snake Sword was instantly wrenched out of Hao Feng's grasp.

Hao Feng immediately shot back in retreat with an alarmed look on his face while simultaneously raising his left hand, releasing a flurry of green needles out of his sleeve, all of which descended upon Han Li from above.

All of the needles were flashing with viscous green light, and it was clear that they were also highly poisonous.

In response, Han Li thrust his left palm forward, releasing a burst of fearsome power that scattered the oncoming volley of green needles with ease.

On top of that, he displayed incredible speed, catching up to Hao Feng in the blink of an eye.

A stunned look appeared on Hao Feng's face, and he knew that he wouldn't be able to get away. Hence, he let loose a loud roar as he clenched his fists tightly and lashed out with all his might.

The space in front of him shuddered violently with a resounding boom, and an unnatural flush appeared on his face as he stumbled back several steps before steadying himself.

At that point, the blade of the Green Snake Sword was already resting on his neck, and his expression instantly stiffened as he raised his arms and declared, "I surrender."

Due to the astonishing speed of the two combatants, the battle had concluded before any of the spectators truly had a chance to see what was happening, and a surprised look flashed through the black-robed referee's eyes as he declared, "The winner is Li Feiyu!"

Han Li gave Hao Feng a slight nod, then returned his Green Snake Sword to him.

"You've definitely opened more than seventy-two profound acupoints. What is your true power?" Hao Feng asked with tightly furrowed brows.

Han Li merely gave a faint smile in response, then made his way down from the platform, while Hao Feng heaved a faint sigh before stepping down from the platform as well.

On the elevated platform, Chen Yang and Qin Yuan were displaying vastly different reactions in response to the outcome of the battle between Han Li and Hao Feng.

Chen Yang's eyes were bright with elation, while Qin Yuan's face had become a facade of steely rage.

"Looks like Hao Feng decided to let Li Feiyu win, after all," Chen Yang said with a hint of mockery in his voice.

Qin Yuan harrumphed coldly in response, while Chen Yang's smile grew even wider.

He had constantly been made fun of by the other city lords ever since the commencement of the Five City Martial Gathering, and it was finally his turn to retaliate for once.

"I didn't know you had such an impressive wild card up your sleeve, City Lord Chen," Sun Tu said with a faint smile, while Fu Jian also turned to him with a solemn expression.

"You're far too kind, City Lord Sun. Li Feiyu still can't even begin to compare with many of the cultivators under your command," Chen Yang chuckled in a modest fashion, and a hint of fury flashed through Qin Yuan's eyes upon hearing this.

Profound End City's second-most powerful representative had just been defeated by Han Li, so by downplaying Han Li's powers, Chen Yang was indirectly insulting Profound End City.

"You're far too modest, Fellow Daoist Chen. I'd say that even Fang Chan may not be able to best Li Feiyu in battle," Sun Tu mused.

Right at this moment, E Kuai suddenly said, "I don't recall seeing this Li Feiyu during the previous martial gathering. Did he only recently join your Green Goat City?"

"That's right, Li Feiyu only joined our Green Goat City several decades ago," Chen Yang replied in a truthful manner.

E Kuai nodded in response, and the other city lords fell silent as they continued watching the rest of the battles.

……

As Han Li stepped down from his platform, all of the nearby spectators hurriedly parted to let him through with looks of awe and veneration in their eyes.

Gu Qianxun, Xuanyuan Xing, Toxic Dragon, Yao Li, and several other Green Goat City cultivators were gathered nearby, and they hurriedly gathered around him as Gu Qianxun said with a wide smile, "Congratulations, Fellow Daoist Li! Hao Feng's scalp is a massive one to claim."

"I was merely fortunate," Han Li replied with a modest smile, and Xuanyuan Xing and the others also offered him their congratulations, while Yao Li looked on with mixed emotions.

She had always looked down on him, and thinking back to the attitude that she had displayed toward him in the past, she was overcome by embarrassment as she also quietly congratulated him on his victory.

Han Li smiled and nodded at Yao Li, seemingly not harboring any animosity toward her, much to Yao Li's relief.

"Let's go and take a look at Fellow Daoist Yi's battle," Gu Qianxun suggested, and everyone quickly followed along.

At this moment, the battle between Feng Wuchen and Yi Liya had already reached a state of white-hot intensity.

This was Han Li's first time seeing Yi Liya in action, and the latter had opened significantly more profound acupoints than even Hao Feng.

Yi Liya's cultivation arts were also more focused on speed enhancement, and he had fifty to sixty profound acupoints on his legs, allowing him to move with incredible speed.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this.

The quality of Yi Liya's character may not have been all that stellar, but his powers certainly did make him worthy of a spot in the top three most powerful Green Goat City representatives.

However, Feng Wuchen had a clear edge over him.

Even when it came to Yi Liya's forte of speed, Feng Wuchen had the clear advantage, moving around like the wind, at times as gentle as a breeze, while at other times as violent as a storm.

All of Yi Liya's attacks were evaded with ease, while Feng Wuchen's attacks were constantly keeping Yi Liya on his toes.

At this point, Several gashes had already been sliced onto Yi Liya's body, and if it weren't for his outstanding speed, he would've already been defeated.

Even though he was clearly outmatched, Yi Liya was still attacking with single-minded ferocity, displaying no intention of backing down.

At this rate, it looks like Yi Liya's loss is sealed. However, he did mention that he had some measures prepared against Feng Wuchen, I wonder if they'll work, Han Li thought to himself.

He could immediately tell that Yi Liya was going all out instead of concealing his true power, yet he was still no match for Feng Wuchen, who clearly still had more to give. Hence, there was no way that Yi Liya could win this battle through conventional means.

Gu Qianxun and the others were also looking on with grim expressions.

Even though Yi Liya had been quite hostile toward Han Li and Gu Qianxun, both of them were still rooting for him, seeing as they were all from Green Goat City.

Tu Gang and the others were already gathered at the platform that Yi Liya was on, and they only took a hurried glance at Han Li and the others as they arrived before directing their attention back to the battle with anxious looks on their faces.

Right at this moment, a decisive look appeared in Yi Liya's eyes, and the black whip that he was wielding abruptly straightened itself out like an extremely long sword before sweeping toward Feng Wuchen.

In response, Feng Wuchen sprang up into the air like a willow leaf, evading the whip strike with ease while retaliating with his thin sword, slashing it toward Yi Liya's wrist.

Yi Liya immediately shot back in retreat, and with a flick of his wrist, his whip instantly returned to its former soft and pliable state, aiming to wrap itself around Feng Wuchen's arm and body like a spirit snake.

A cold sneer appeared on Feng Wuchen's face, and he abruptly vanished from the spot.

As a result, the whip struck nothing but empty air, and Yi Liya's body was tipped slightly off balance by the momentum of the whip strike.

In the next instant, Feng Wuchen appeared behind Yi Liya without any warning, following which he lashed out while Yi Liya was still off balance, dealing nine consecutive blows with his willow leaf sword in rapid succession.

The nine sword strikes were able to pierce through the True Extreme Film around Yi Liya with ease before striking his body, but to everyone's astonishment, the sword strikes weren't able to do anything aside from knock him forward a couple of steps.

Feng Wuchen was also very much taken aback to see this, and right at this moment, a fierce gleam appeared in Yi Liya's eyes as he swept his whip through the air, unleashing dozens of whip projections that formed a series of black circles, all of which converged rapidly toward Feng Wuchen.

The black circles were giving off tremendous power that instantly encompassed the entire platform, and all of the nearby space began to collapse inward in the face of the formidable whip projections.

All of a sudden, the entire platform and the nearby area around it had been transformed into an inhospitable death zone, and all of the surrounding spectators hurriedly backed away with alarmed expressions.

Chapter 908: Public Provocation

A hint of surprise had also appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of the ferocious storm raging over the platform.

"That's Yi Liya's Heaven Locking Seal! It's become far more powerful than since I last saw it," Gu Qianxun murmured to herself.

Feng Wuchen's expression darkened slightly as he assessed the grim situation that he was in, and a string of cracks and pops rang out from within his body as over 150 profound acupoints lit up over his skin.

At the same time, he stomped a foot down onto the ground, almost causing the entire platform to collapse with just a single stomp.

Using the power of the stomp, Feng Wuchen launched himself up diagonally up into the air, flying out of the vast expanse of whip projections around him.

Meanwhile, Yi Liya continued to swing his black whip through the air, and his entire body was already completely inundated by whip projections, which transformed into black circles that sped toward Feng Wuchen as if they had eyes.

However, Feng Wuchen's speed was clearly superior, and he was able to just barely evade all of the whip projections that came his way.

"This is an extremely formidable attack from Yi Liya. If the target is caught by one of the whip projections, then they'll immediately be overwhelmed by the rest of the whip projections. However, unfortunately for him, Feng Wuchen possesses top-notch speed, and Yi Liya isn't going to be able to keep this up for long,"

"I think Yi Liya still has more tricks up his sleeve, but even so, I think Feng Wuchen is too powerful for him to defeat," Gu Qianxun said.

All of a sudden, Han Li's expression changed slightly as he said, "Here it comes!"

All of a sudden, countless starry runes emerged over Feng Wuchen's willow leaf sword, releasing a halo of bright white light that instantly swept over the entire platform.

Rays of white starlight shone down from the radiant white halo, all of which converged toward the willow leaf sword, causing it to buzz and tremble.

Immediately thereafter, the willow leaf sword flew out of Feng Wuchen's grasp, transforming into a dazzling blade of white light that struck the point between a pair of nearby black whip circles.

A gash was instantly sliced into the space there, and Feng Wuchen was able to dart through the opening in a flash.

An intrigued look appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of the willow leaf sword.

The sword was giving off incredibly formidable energy fluctuations, and he couldn't help but wonder what type of treasure it was.

Right at this moment, all of the whip projections around Yi Liya abruptly faded away, revealing him with a peculiar smile on his face.

All of a sudden, he thrust a palm forward, and a plume of white light erupted out of his sleeve, consisting of countless radiant white threads.

Each thread was as translucent as jade, and a series of tiny specks of white light could be seen dancing around them.

The thin threads converged to form a huge white net that descended upon Feng Wuchen at an incredible speed, and he was caught completely off guard.

Before he had a chance to take evasive measures, the net wrapped itself around him in layers to form a white cocoon, which then tumbled down onto the platform, while all of the nearby spectators gasped in astonishment.

An ecstatic look appeared on Yi Liya's face upon seeing this, but his smile quickly faded as his face turned an unnatural shade of bright red, as did the skin all over the rest of his body.

All of a sudden, his entire body had become as red as blood, and there were also countless veins bulging beneath his skin.

However, in the next instant, the red coloration of his skin faded away, leaving him as pale as a sheet. At the same time, blood came gushing out of his mouth, and his footsteps had also become very feeble and unstable.

"He's mastered the Hazy Helmet Technique! No wonder he was able to withstand Feng Wuchen's attacks so easily just now. I wonder what those white threads that he used to trap Feng Wuchen were," Xuanyuan Xing murmured to himself.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon hearing this. He had heard of the Hazy Helmet Technique during his time in the arena of Green Goat City. It was a type of secret technique that allowed one to spread their bloodline power into all of the profound acupoints in their body to drastically enhance their defenses in a short time.

It was an extremely powerful secret technique, and the more profound acupoints one opened, the more powerful it would become. However, cultivating it required one to refine their profound acupoints in an extremely excruciating process.

On top of that, unleashing the secret technique required one to expend a third of their bloodline power each time, and it was extremely risky to use as it could easily damage the foundation of one's physical body, so it was a very rarely pursued secret technique.

"That's the All-encompassing Net! Mistress Liu Hua used the bonded silk of an A tier Scaled Spider Beast to refine a special weapon over a hundred years ago. It's not a star artifact, but it's not far away from one. However, the weapon was somehow lost over time, but it seems to have found itself in the possession of Yi Liya. No wonder he's so confident," Gu Qianxun mused.

All of the other Green Goat City cultivators erupted into cheers upon seeing this, while a look of pleasant surprise had appeared on Chen Yang's face as well.

However, out of his peripheral vision, he could see that Qin Yuan remained calm and completely unconcerned, and his heart immediately sank slightly.

On the platform, Yi Liya took a deep breath to steady himself, then took a glance at the willow leaf sword, which was still flying up toward the heavens.

With a flick of his wrist, his black whip shot forth in a flash, wrapping itself around the white cocoon before hurling it off the platform.

However, right at this moment, a loud tearing sound rang out as the cocoon was split into two, and Feng Wuchen sprang out from within before pouncing at Yi Liya with incredible speed.

Yi Liya's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he immediately attempted to use his black whip to defend himself.

However, he was still reeling from the backlash of using the Hazy Helmet Technique, and he was only able to raise his arm halfway before a burst of white light crashed into his chest with tremendous power.

His chest immediately caved in as blood came gushing out of his mouth once again, and he was sent flying back before tumbling down from the platform.

Right at this moment, Chen Yang appeared in mid-air in a wraith-like manner to catch Yi Liya before slowly lowering him down onto the ground, and all of the Green Goat City cultivators immediately gathered around to inspect his condition.

Meanwhile, Han Li was observing Chen Yang with his brows slightly furrowed.

Chen Yang had been on the elevated platform just a moment ago, yet he was able to instantly appear near the platform completely without Han Li's detection.

Even though this could be partially attributed to the fact that Han Li was distracted by the battle taking place on the platform, this was still a clear indication that Chen Yang's true power was beyond what he had revealed thus far.

At this moment, blood was still gushing out of Yi Liya's mouth, but he had already fallen unconscious.

Chen Yang pulled out a crimson jade vial and forced open Yi Liya's mouth, then fed him a crimson pill from inside the vial.

As soon as the pill entered Yi Liya's mouth, a hint of color instantly returned to his deathly pale cheeks, and his caved-in chest also began to return to its original state.

A relieved look appeared on Chen Yang's face upon seeing this, and he cast his gaze up toward Feng Wuchen on the platform to discover that he was holding a willow leaf sword identical to the one that was still flying through the air.

A look of realization appeared on Chen Yang's face upon seeing this, and he made a beckoning motion, upon which the two halves of the white cocoon flew into his grasp.

The two halves of the cocoon then fused together as if they were living creatures, forming a fist-sized white ball.

Feng Wuchen also made a beckoning motion with one hand, and the willow leaf sword that was still flying toward the heavens immediately stopped in its tracks, then flew back to him before landing in his grasp.

The two willow leaf swords were resonating with each other to produce a ringing sound akin to the chirping of a flock of birds.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly at the sight of the pair of swords, and Feng Wuchen seemed to have detected his gaze.

Their eyes met, and sparks immediately began to fly.

"You're next, Li Feiyu! I suggest you write your will because you won't live past the next round!" Feng Wuchen declared as he pointed one of his swords at Han Li from afar.

Everyone immediately turned to Han Li upon hearing this.

Indeed, Han Li was scheduled to battle Feng Wuchen in the upcoming round of sixteen.

Everyone's attention had been focused on Feng Wuchen's battle against Yi Liya, so not only were most people not even aware of the fact that Han Li had emerged victorious in his battle, they had also failed to consider the possibility that these two could encounter each other in the round of sixteen.

Feng Wuchen was the undisputed most powerful representative of Profound End City, while Han Li was someone that no one had even heard of, and very few people had even witnessed his battles in the first two rounds.

However, at this moment, it was the vastly renowned Feng Wuchen who was going out of his way to provoke a no-name like Han Li, and all of the bystanders couldn't help but wonder if this meant that Han Li should be considered a hot favorite or at least a dark horse from here onward.

"See you in the next round," Han Li said in an indifferent manner.

A furious look flashed through Feng Wuchen's eyes, seemingly very displeased with Han Li's lackadaisical demeanor.

"Feng Wuchen is the winner!"

With the outcome of the battle officially announced, a chorus of thunderous cheers erupted from the nearby spectator stands, and Feng Wuchen finally turned his gaze away from Han Li before cupping his fist in a salute toward Qin Yuan on the elevated platform.

Chen Yang paid no heed to what was happening around him as he gently placed the white ball in his hand down the front of Yi Liya's robe, then carried him away as he said, "Come with me, Li Feiyu. Everyone else, stay here to support Gu Qianxun and Xuanyuan Xing."

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he excused himself with Gu Qianxun and Xuanyuan Xing before setting off after Chen Yang.

Chapter 909: Star Artifact

Chen Yang carried Yi Liya out of the Asura Arena altogether, and he and Han Li returned to the courtyard assigned to the Green Goat City cultivators.

After setting Yi Liya down to rest in another room, Chen Yang joined Han Li in the side hall outside.

"Will Fellow Daoist Yi be alright?" Han Li asked.

"His injuries are very severe. He's in no life-threatening danger, but his bloodline power has been severely deplected after unleashing the Hazy Helmet Technique, so he won't be waking up anytime soon," Chen Yang replied.

Han Li nodded in response.

"Do you know why I asked you to come and see me?" Chen Yang asked with a solemn look on his face.

"I presume you want to speak to me about the next round," Han Li replied.

"That's right. Do you have any strategies against Feng Wuchen?" Chen Yang asked.

"No, but I'll be sure to give it my all, so rest assured, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li replied.

"I don't know exactly how many profound acupoints you've opened up to this point, but judging from your battle against Hao Feng, it shouldn't be any fewer than him," Chen Yang said.

Han Li offered no reply, merely giving a faint smile in response.

"I had thought that with your powers and your true spirit bloodlines, you should be able to match up against Feng Wuchen just fine, but the fact that he has a pair of star artifacts at his disposal is very bad news for you," Chen Yang continued.

"What exactly is a star artifact, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Han Li asked.

"You don't know? I suppose that's understandable, considering you've never come to Profound City before. A star artifact is a type of advanced weapon refined by Mistress Liu Hua using the stapower of this realm. They are extremely powerful, but also exceedingly rare, yet somehow, Qin Yuan has managed to get his hands on that pair of swords," Chen Yang explained in a grim voice.

The image of Feng Wuchen's twin swords resurfaced in Han Li's mind upon hearing this.

"However, he's not the only one with star artifacts at his disposal," Chen Yang said as a smile appeared on his face, and he pulled out a small white shield that was riddled with starry runes before handing it to Han Li.

Engraved onto the center of the shield were eighteen star designs that formed the shape of a dragon, and every single one of the star designs was radiating white light that was fluctuating rhythmically in brightness, almost as if they were beating hearts.

"What's this?" Han Li asked as he accepted the white shield, and he could feel it resonating with the profound acupoints in his body.

"This is a star artifact called the Star Shield. Normally, a star artifact has to be nurtured using one's blood essence for a long time before they can be used, but we don't have much time here, so refine it with your blood essence as much as possible over the next few days. That way, by the time the third round begins, you should be able to unleash some of the shield's power to help you ward off Feng Wuchen's twin swords," Chen Yang said.

Han Li took a glance at the shield, then said, "Thank you, Fellow Daoist Chen. I won't disappoint you in the upcoming round."

Chen Yang smiled in response, then briefly taught Han Li how to use the Star Shield before dismissing him.

Han Li returned to his room with the Star Shield, and after conducting a brief inspection, he bit through the tip of his own finger to release a drop of blood essence onto the shield.

The drop of blood essence immediately fused into the shield, upon which a layer of white light emerged over its surface.

A pleased look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

He could clearly sense that a connection had been formed between himself and the shield, but at the moment, the connection was still very weak.

A wisp of spiritual sense emerged from his glabella before entering the Star Shield, helping it to better absorb the drop of blood essence.

The process felt very similar to that of refining immortal treasures, except it was far slower without the help of immortal spiritual power.

Close to two hours passed by in a flash, and right at this moment, a commotion suddenly began to ring out outside.

Han Li stowed the Star Shield away, then made his way out into the courtyard to discover that all of the Green Goat City cultivators had returned.

Everyone had excited looks on their faces with Gu Qianxun at the center of the group, looking much like a bright moon surrounded by stars, but Xuanyuan Xing was nowhere to be seen.

"Looks like you won your battle as well, Fellow Daoist Gu. Congratulations," Han Li said as he approached her with a smile.

"I was merely lucky," Gu Qianxun replied with a modest smile.

Despite her humble response, she wasn't carrying any injuries at all, so she had clearly enjoyed a very easy victory, something that came as no surprise to Han Li.

Everyone quickly departed to allow the two of them to speak in private, and Han Li asked, "What happened to Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan?"

"Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan won his battle as well. His opponent was more powerful than him, but he was able to successfully execute his strategy to secure a very difficult victory. He sustained some rather severe injuries in the process, and he's been sent to the city lord's manor for treatment," Gu Qianxun replied with a smile.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

After a brief hesitation, Gu Qianxun continued, "Fellow Daoist Li, your third round opponent is Feng Wuchen. Those star artifacts of his are extremely formidable, do you have any strategies against him?"

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Gu, I've already discussed some strategies with City Lord Chen," Han Li replied.

"That's good to hear," Gu Qianxun replied with a nod, making no attempt to pry any further.

The two of them chatted with each other for a while longer before parting ways.

Han Li returned to his room to continue refining the Star Shield, and as time passed, the white starlight radiating from the Star Shield became brighter and brighter.

Han Li could also sense his own profound acupoints resonating with the Star Shield, and it was as if the two were becoming one.

It was as if the Star Shield had become an extension of his own body, and Han Li's eyes sprang open as he cast his gaze toward the shield with a surprised look on his face.

It seemed that these star artifacts really were quite extraordinary.

……

Seven more days flew by in a flash.

Early in the morning, the Asura Arena was already packed with people.

Following the first two rounds, the number of combatants in the Five City Martial Gathering had dropped down to sixteen, and this was going to be the round that decided who would progress to the quarterfinal.

The city lords and Mistress Liu Hua arrived on the elevated platform to a wave of thunderous cheers.

Despite his best efforts, the horned man who was serving as host of the event was unable to suppress the cheers, so he could only wait until the commotion died down before declaring, "This round is going to decide who makes it into the final eight. All those who emerge victorious today will receive a B tier scaled beast core, so let's all wish the remaining gladiators the best of luck."

The spectators instantly erupted into a frenzy in the wake of this announcement.

"We are about to cross the halfway mark of the martial gathering, and for this round, only two platforms will be in use, with four batches of two battles for the round. The first two matches will see Zhu Ziyuan of Profound City go up against Jin Gong of Profound End City, and Feng Wuchen of Profound End City up against Li Feiyu of Green Goat City," the horned ma n announced.

On the elevated platform, Chen Yang was looking on with a concerned expression.

Green Goat City had been utterly humiliated after the first round, with only four of their twelve representatives advancing, but three of those four had advanced from the second round, which was a splendid outcome.

However, his joy was very short-lived as both Han Li and Gu Qianxun had extremely tough battles on their hands for this round, and he had no confidence in their ability to come out on top.

Even though he had managed to secure a star artifact for Han Li, this was his first time using something like this, so he definitely wasn't going to be as proficient in its usage as Feng Wuchen was.

On top of that, in his mind, Feng Wuchen was more powerful than Han Li to begin with, so he was very pessimistic about this matchup.

As for Gu Qianxun, he assumed her to be stronger than Li Feiyu, but Fang Chan had defeated her in the past, so things weren't looking good for her, either.

Xuanyuan Xing was up against Luo Chongwei of Profound City for this round, a matchup that was certainly the easiest of the three, but his chances of securing victory were looking rather slim as well.

He had thought that at least one of the three should be able to reach the final four, but it seemed that having one of them progress to the top eight may be too much to ask.

If all of the Green Goat City cultivators were eliminated before the quarterfinals, that would be an even worse outcome than during the Du Qingyang era. Not only would that mean that none of them would get a reward from Profound City, his authority as city lord would undoubtedly be shaken by such a terrible outcome.

"Shouldn't the top representatives of each city only be encountering each other starting from the quarterfinals? Why is Gu Qianxun of Green Goat City already going up against Fang Chan of White Rock City?" Mistress Liu Hua suddenly asked.

"That's how things normally play out, but there aren't actually any official rules stating that this has to be the case. These two just so happen to be in the same bracket, so barring any mishaps, they were always going to clash in the round of sixteen. I don't think this is necessarily a bad thing. At the very least, it adds some excitement to this first half of the martial gathering," Qin Yuan said.

"Gu Qianxun has put on quite a formidable display in the first two rounds, and I'm sure she'll be eager for vengeance against Fang Chan. Perhaps the outcome of their previous battle could be reversed this time," Fu Jian mused as he took a meaningful glance at Sun Tu.

Chen Yang's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but he was aware of what Fu Jian was implying.

Even though it appeared that he was paying Gu Qianxun a compliment, he was clearly simply using that as an excuse to mention the fact that Gu Qianxun had been defeated by Fang Chan in their last encounter.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Fu. All Fang Chan does is eat and sleep all day, and he hasn't improved much at all since the last martial gathering. I'm afraid he may be reduced to a mere stepping stone for Gu Qianxun on this occasion," Sun Tu sighed, but there was a faint smile playing on his lips, and it was clear that he wasn't actually concerned at all.

"I think the battle between Li Feiyu and Wuchen will be very much worth watching as well. There already seems to be some bad blood between them, so this is a highly anticipated matchup for all of the spectators," Qin Yuan said.

Chapter 910: Stop Running

"Now that I think about it, this Li Feiyu has shown himself to be quite courageous. It's only his first time taking part in the Five City Martial Gathering, yet he already dares to provoke the top gladiator of Profound End City in public. I think he has some good qualities that make him very much worth nurturing, City Lord Chen," E Kuai remarked.

"Indeed, City Lord E. Our Green Goat City doesn't have as strong a foundation as the other three cities, so I do need to work on nurturing some talent," Chen Yang replied.

Han Li and the others weren't paying any attention to what was happening on the elevated platform. After all of the spectators had placed their bets, the two battles commenced.

Zhu Ziyuan's battle against Jin Dong was hardly even worth watching, and the odds for betting on Zhu Ziyuan were extremely low. Hence, very few people chose to bet on that battle, while the majority of spectators placed their bets on the battle between Han Li and Feng Wuchen.

Han Li was a previously unknown dark horse that had stormed into the top sixteen in stunning fashion, while Feng Wuchen was the top representative of Profound End City. On paper, there was a clear power gap between the two, so Han Li's odds were far higher than Feng Wuchen's.

The higher the odds, the smaller one's theoretical chance of securing victory, so among the people betting on this battle, over 90% of them had placed their bets on Feng Wuchen.

As for the rest, they were simply hoping to essentially win the lottery by betting on Han Li.

Gu Qianxun and and all of the other spectators stepped down from the platforms, and prior to her departure, Gu Qianxun suddenly made a request to Han Li through voice transmission.

"Fellow Daoist Li, please inflict some severe injuries upon Feng Wuchen if possible, and it would be ideal if you could kill him altogether. If you can do that, I'll be sure to compensate you for your efforts."

"You think far too highly of me, Fellow Daoist Gu. Having said that, it doesn't look like Feng Wuchen is keen on a peaceful resolution, so I certainly won't be holding back against him," Han Li replied with a smile.

He had a rough idea of Gu Qianxun's bad blood with Profound End City, so he wasn't surprised by this request.

"I'll be counting on you then, Fellow Daoist Li," Gu Qianxun said before departing.

Toxic Dragon and the others were still yet to fully recover from their injuries, but all of them were able to move at this point, so they were all gathered in the spectator stands to watch Han Li's battle against Feng Wuchen.

Out of all of the Green Goat City cultivators, the two most severely injured ones were Tu Gang and Yi Liya, both of whom were only able to reach the spectator stands with assistance from others.

After everyone had sat down, Yao Li cast her gaze toward Han Li with mixed emotions in her eyes.

Back when they had first met in the Green Goat City arena, he had been a completely unremarkable looking human, yet for some reason, Gu Qianxun had taken an interest in him.

Looking back now, Yao Li realized that she had indeed been mistaken about Han Li, and that he was far more powerful than she imagined. No wonder Gu Qianxun had warned her not to make an enemy out of him.

"What do you think of Fellow Daoist Li's chances, Fellow Daoist Toxic Dragon?" Yao Li asked.

Toxic Dragon took an awkward glance at Yi Liya upon hearing this, then replied, "That's... really hard to say. Honestly, I feel like Fellow Daoist Li has never shown his true power, so I don't know what he's capable of."

Yi Liya was already in a terrible mood, and he harrumphed coldly, "So what if he's concealed some of his power? Even Gu Qianxun may not be a match for Feng Wuchen, you think he can win? What a joke!"

"Just because you're too weak doesn't mean everyone else is the same. I don't know if Fellow Daoist Li can defeat Feng Wuchen, but Fellow Daoist Gu definitely can," Yao Li sneered.

"She'll have to worry about Fang Chan first," Yi Liya harrumphed in a disdainful manner.

Yao Li had no response to this, and she could only clench her fists in a disgruntled fashion.

It was true that Gu Qianxun had been defeated by Fang Chan during their last encounter, so her chances of winning certainly weren't great.

"Let's all settle down now, the battles are about to begin," Toxic Dragon mediated.

Yao Li gave a cold harrumph before falling silent, while Yi Liya glowered at Han Li from afar.

Daoist Xie was also sitting nearby, and he took a glance at Yi Liya before shaking his head with a faint smile.

……

The four gladiators participating in the two battles were already in place, and as the referees stepped onto the platforms, the cheering from the spectators gradually subsided.

On one platform, Zhu Ziyuan was standing in a suit of bone armor with a bone spear held in his hand. Judging from the radiant starlight emanating from the spear, it was clearly an extremely formidable star artifact.

Standing across from him was Jin Gong, who was also from Profound City. He was a giant of a man standing at over twenty feet tall, with bulging muscles all over his entire body and a layer of green fur growing on his skin, giving him the appearance of a hulking ape.

On his right arm was a bone glove that seemed to have been stitched from some type of beast hide with star bones of different sizes embedded onto it, and even though it wasn't quite on the level of a star artifact, it still appeared to be quite formidable.

After announcing the rules of the battle, the referee declared for the battle to commence before flying down from the platform.

Jin Gong let loose a near animalistic roar as he clenched his fists tightly while stomping a foot down onto the ground, and the platform quivered beneath his feet as over eighty profound acupoints lit up over his body one after another, sending powerful shockwaves erupting in all directions.

At the same time, a layer of starlight appeared over the glove on his right hand as well.

"How many times have I told you? Releasing your aura like this will only discount your power. It puts on a good show, but it provides no other benefits," Zhu Ziyuan scolded in a cold voice.

Jin Gong's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he took a deep breath as his aura became far more restrained, looking as if he had suddenly run out of power.

However, all of the experts present could clearly see that the starlight emanating from the glove on his right fist had become far more condensed.

"That's better, but it's still not enough," Zhu Ziyuan said with a shake of his head, and a wry smile appeared on Jin Gong's face upon hearing this.

As opposed to an arena battle, it appeared more like the two of them were having a casual sparring match, and it was clear that Zhu Ziyuan had instructed Jin Gong quite extensively in the past.

A short while later, Zhu Ziyuan finally gave a nod of approval as he said, "Alright, I want you to remember this feeling and replicate it in your future battles. Come at me now."

Jin Gong nodded in response, then charged at Zhu Ziyuan while all of the spectators looked on with speechless expressions, booing at the terrible show on display.

……

Meanwhile, Han Li and Feng Wuchen were also facing each other from afar on their platform.

Feng Wuchen was dressed in his usual white robe with his willow leaf sword in his hand, and many of the spectators in the stands were cheering for him.

As for Han Li, he was dressed in a simple black robe with his hands joined together in his sleeves, looking very calm and relaxed.

"Before we begin, I'll give you a chance to kneel down and beg for forgiveness. If you pass up this opportunity now, you won't get another chance," Feng Wuchen said in a cold voice.

"Hurry up and fight, don't waste time with all this chit-chat," Han Li said in an indifferent manner.

Feng Wuchen's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this, and he harrumphed coldly, "Alright, I gave you a chance!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, dozens of profound acupoints lit up over his legs, and in the blink of an eye, he completely vanished from the spot.

The spectators had completely lost sight of Feng Wuchen, but Han Li was able to see him very clearly, and he sprang into action as well.

The profound acupoints of his Wingform Ascension Arts lit up over his legs, and he vanished from the spot as well.

Immediately thereafter, an explosive boom rang out from the spot where he had just been standing a moment ago, and the ground there was completely shattered by hundreds of streaks of white swordlight.

Feng Wuchen flashed past that spot without pause as he continued to pursue Han LI like lightning while lashing out with his sword once again.

A string of explosions rang out in rapid succession alongside flashes of light as Feng Wuchen pursued Han Li all over the platform, while the latter continued to take evasive measures.

Initially, the spectators were watching with keen interest, but this repetitive show of flashing lights and explosions quickly became boring to watch, and boos began to ring out from the stands.

All of a sudden, Feng Wuchen stopped in his tracks, and Han Li did the same a safe distance away. The former was glowering intently at the latter with a furious look in his eyes. Feng Wuchen had thought that he would be able to completely dominate Han Li with his speed, but Han Li was able to keep up with him just fine.

"Stop running like a coward!" Feng Wuchen sneered.

"Maybe you'd be able to catch me if you weren't so slow," Han Li countered with a faint smile.

Chapter 911: Display of Power

"Shut your mouth!"

Feng Wuchen flared up with rage as he grabbed onto the hilt of his willow leaf sword with both hands, and the sword split up into two, one in each hand. Immediately thereafter, his arms began to sway gently along with the two swords like willow branches in a light breeze.

At the same time, countless radiant white sub-branches were emerging from the pair of longswords, and it was as if the two swords really had become a pair of willow branches.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he didn't make any rash moves.

Right at this moment, Feng Wuchen suddenly swung his swords through the air, and hundreds of willow branches formed by starpower swept toward Han Li in an almighty wave.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and he immediately darted back in retreat, but as soon as he sprang into motion, the air currents that he stirred up with his body caused all of the sword projections to veer off their original trajectories to continue pursuing him, and they had also become several times faster.

To Feng Wuchen's surprise, Han Li didn't appear to be all that concerned in the face of the formidable storm of sword projections.

He slowly extended his right hand out of his sleeve, and a small, white shield flew out from within, hovering around three feet in front of him.

The shield was trembling incessantly as the eighteen star designs on its surface glowed radiantly,as if it were struggling to contain some type of pent-up power.

In the instant that the storm of sword projections descended upon Han Li, a faint draconic roar rang out, and a burst of radiant white light erupted out of the white shield, forming an ethereal starry light barrier around Han Li.

A string of loud booms rang out in rapid succession as the storm of sword projections ravaged the starry light barrier from all directions, causing the nearby space to ripple and warp violently.

The starry light barrier immediately began to tremble, and it was being rapidly stripped away. As a result, the light barrier was also shrinking around Han Li, and before long, it had shrunk down to no more than three feet away from Han Li.

A cold sneer appeared on Feng Wuchen's face upon seeing this, but Han Li remained as calm and collected as ever.

In fact, he was so composed that he had his left hand clasped behind his back, and he extended his right hand forward as he let loose a loud roar.

Immediately thereafter, profound acupoints that he had never revealed before began to light up over his body one after another in rapid succession.

The number of profound acupoints on Han Li's body increased all the way to 138, and at that point, a projection of a dragon suddenly flew out of the eighteen star designs on the surface of the Star Shield.

Another draconic roar rang out as the dragon projection abruptly swelled to over a hundred times its original size, and it circled around Han Li momentarily before rising up into the heavens.

The dragon projection stirred up extremely formidable spatial fluctuations that erupted forth in all directions, causing all of the oncoming willow leaf sword projections to shatter into specks of starlight before dissipating into nothingness, and Feng Wuchen's triumphant smile immediately stiffened upon seeing this.

"138!" Yao Li exclaimed as she clapped a hand over her own mouth.

Toxic Dragon's eyes were also wide with astonishment, while Yi Liya's hands had balled up into tight fists, and a conflicted look had appeared on his face.

In contrast, Gu Qianxun was watching the battle from the lobby with a faint smile on her face.

On the elevated platform, Chen Yang was finally able to heave an internal sigh of relief.

He had always known that Han Li had never revealed his true power, but he had no idea exactly how powerful Han Li was.

At this point, he was beginning to think that as long as Han Li wished for it to be so, he could keep displaying more and more profound acupoints indefinitely.

"This Li Feiyu is quite proficient at concealing his powers, isn't he?" E Kuai remarked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Indeed, he and Fellow Daoist Gu Qianxun are the pillars of our Green Goat City," Chen Yang replied with a smile.

"Are we sure he's not a spy sent by Puppet City? It seems a little suspicious that he's hiding so much," Qin Yuan remarked in a skeptical manner.

"Don't go spouting such nonsensical accusations if you don't have any proof, City Lord Qin! Otherwise, you'll have to bear the consequences!" Chen Yang snapped in a cold voice.

"What consequences will I have to bear? Do you want to fight me right here? If so, I'd be more than happy to oblige," Qin Yuan countered in a cold voice, while Fu Jian and Sun Tu remained silent, eager to watch a conflict erupt between the two.

Right at this moment, E Kuai scolded in a cold voice, "Settle down!"

Even though no profound acupoints had lit up over his body, he was suddenly giving off a tremendous aura, one that was filled with unmatched power and regal authority.

Chen Yang and Qin Yuan immediately reined in their own auras upon seeing this, following which both of them cupped their fists in an apologetic salute.

E Kuai's aura also slowly faded away as his expression eased slightly, and he said, "Fellow Daoist was only making a joke just now, so don't get so worked up, Fellow Daoist Chen. It's a blessing for our Profound City that you've managed to unearth such a bright talent."

"Indeed, City Lord E," Sun Tu and the others hurriedly chimed in in a flattering fashion.

Meanwhile, Mistress Liu Hua remained completely uninterested in what was happening around him, and his gaze was fixed firmly on Han Li and Feng Wuchen's platform.

The majority of the spectators present also had their attention focused on this battle. After all, the battle between Zhu Ziyuan and Jin Gong was hardly worth watching at all.

"So what if you have 138 profound acupoints?" Feng Wuchen sneered before abruptly vanishing from the spot, circling rapidly around Han Li while waiting for an opportunity to strike.

At the same time, he continued swinging his swords through the air, unleashing flurries of willow leaf sword projections that were even more powerful than before, but Han Li's defenses remained as watertight as ever.

As the stalemate wore on, Feng Wuchen's expression darkened further and further.

Right at this moment, he drew to an abrupt halt, and over 150 profound acupoints lit up over his body, while countless starry runes emerged on the willow leaf swords in his hands.

Immediately thereafter, a radiant wave of white light erupted out of the two swords, and rays of white starlight began to shine down from the heavens before converging toward the two swords, producing a faint buzzing sound.

Han Li was immediately able to identify this attack as the one that had severely wounded Yi Liya, and a serious look finally appeared on his face.

"Go!" Feng Wuchen yelled as he swept his left hand through the air, and his willow leaf sword instantly flew out of his grasp before hurtling directly toward Han Li as a radiant blade of white light.

The space in the wake of the blade of light rumbled and collapsed violently, and in response, Han Li thrust both of his palms forward as the eighteen profound acupoints of the Titan Vajra Arts lit up over his arms.

The starlight radiating from the Star Shield instantly swelled outward to oppose the oncoming blade of light, and a resounding boom rang out as the two clashed.

The surrounding space began to fracture as brilliant white light that was as radiant as the sun erupted from the point where the blade of the light and the Star Shield were in contact with one another,

All of a sudden, a faint crack rang out, and Han immediately noticed that a hair-thin crack had appeared on the surface of the Star Shield.

As a result, the starry light barrier released by the Star Shield instantly began to tremble in an unsteady fashion, and holes of different sizes were beginning to appear on its surface.

An elated look flashed through Feng Wuchen's eyes upon seeing this, and he began swinging the willow leaf sword in his right hand like a willow branch once again.

Countless willow leaf sword projections erupted out of the sword, culminating in a violent storm that cascaded down upon Han Li.

The starry light barrier wasn't able to protect him any longer, and over a hundred sword projections instantly fell upon him, tearing countless gashes into his robes.

Through the gashes in his clothes, it could be seen that a True Extreme Film had emerged over his body, and it was easily able to keep out the sword projections descending upon him.

A cold sneer appeared on Feng Wuchen's face as he grabbed onto the hilt of his sword with both hands, and over 160 profound acupoints lit up over his body, while a series of bright specks of light also began to emerge along the blade of his sword.

Those are star acupoints!

Only after learning about star artifacts from Chen Yang did Han Li become aware of the concept of star acupoints.

Just like the number of profound acupoints on a cultivator's body, the number of star acupoints on a star artifact was a direct indication of its caliber. The more star acupoints a star artifact possessed, the more powerful it was, but at the same time, it would also be more difficult to refine.

Once a star artifact was refined to a certain extent, it would begin to feel like an extension of one's body, and at that point, the star acupoints on the star artifact would also become pillars of strength for the wielder, just like the profound acupoints on their body.

The Star Shield had a total of eighteen star acupoints, but with only seven days to refine it, Han Li was currently only able to draw upon the power of eight of its eighteen star acupoints, while Feng Wuchen had already completely refined his willow leaf swords long ago.

At this moment, there were twenty-one star acupoints glowing radiantly on his willow leaf sword, and his aura had swelled to unprecedented heights.

All of a sudden, he appeared directly in front of Han Li in the blink of an eye, then thrust his longsword diagonally upward, aiming at Han Li's lower abdomen, which was currently exposed by one of the holes in the starry light barrier released by the Star Shield.

Chapter 912: Stunning Performance

This was an extremely fast and vicious attack, and it was clear that Feng Wuchen was striking to kill.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly as he thrust his palm downward, lowering the shield to oppose the willow leaf sword piercing at him from down below.

Right as the two were about to clash, a string of star designs abruptly lit up over the willow leaf sword, and it was as if the blade of the sword had suddenly become twice as wide as before, granting it immense power as he struck the underside of the shield.

A loud crack rang out, and the crack on the shield instantly began to widen.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he decided to abandon the Star Shield as he sprang up into the air.

Immediately thereafter, the Star Shield abruptly exploded as a streak of swordlight erupted into the air, only just barely glancing past the tip of Han Li's nose.

"You're not getting away this time!" Feng Wuchen declared with a triumphant smile as he launched himself up into the air like a speeding arrow, catching up to Han Li in the blink of an eye.

At the same time, all of his profound acupoints and his sword's star acupoints lit up in unison, basking his entire body in a layer of starlight. All of the starpower around his body converged toward his sword as he slashed it through the air, unleashing a blindingly bright streak of swordlight.

The two of them were very close to each other, and the streak of swordlight was extremely fast. Suspended in mid-air with nowhere to hide, it seemed like Han Li had been reduced to a sitting duck.

An anxious look immediately appeared on Chen Yang's face upon seeing this, while Qin Yuan and the others were looking on with calm and relaxed expressions.

Gu Qianxun also shook her head in dismay as she heaved a forlorn sigh.

As for Yi Liya, he was feeling quite conflicted. After realizing that Han Li was clearly more powerful than him, he had begun rooting for him, hoping that he would be able to defeat Feng Wuchen, but it seemed like his hopes were about to be dashed.

Even Daoist Xie's brows had become tightly furrowed with concern.

Right at this moment, all of the profound acupoints on Han Li's legs lit up as he channeled his Wingform Ascension Arts with all his might, and tremendous starlight erupted out of the eighteen profound acupoints.

Two dull thumps rang out in unison as Han Li was somehow able to use the empty air beneath himself as purchase, forcibly darting away to the side to change directions, thereby allowing him to evade what had appeared to be an unavoidable strike.

"Impossible!" Feng Wuchen exclaimed, while a wave of thunderous cheers rang out from the spectator stands.

On the elevated platform, Chen Yang heaved a sigh of relief, and it was Qin Yuan's turn to feel a little anxious.

Meanwhile, Mistress Liu Hua was nodding to himself with a pleased expression, clearly impressed with Han Li's stunning display.

At this point, there was barely anyone watching the battle taking place between Zhu Ziyuan and Jin Gong anymore.

After evading Feng Wuchen's sword strike, Han Li didn't retreat or attempt to get away. Instead, he twisted around, stomping down onto the air below once again to launch himself directly at Feng Wuchen.

"It's your turn now!" he yelled as more and more profound acupoints lit up over his body, and the total number was quickly approaching 180.

Not only were the spectators in the stands astonished to see this, even those on the elevated platform couldn't help but be stunned by what they were seeing.

Never had any of them imagined that Han Li could be so powerful.

A hint of surprise had even broken through E Kuai's perpetually expressionless facade, and he took a glance at Chen Yang, seemingly trying to gauge his reaction.

Upon detecting E Kuai's gaze, Chen Yang turned to give him a faint smile.

In reality, he was just as shocked as everyone else, but he was putting on a composed facade to make it appear as if he were already aware of the extent of Han Li's power.

On the battle platform, a hint of fear and alarm flashed through Feng Wuchen's eyes at the sight of the dense clusters of profound acupoints on Han Li's body, but at this point, he had no choice but to face Han Li head-on.

He was going to make one final roll of the dice, and he was willing to even make some sacrifices to secure this victory.

With that in mind, Feng Wuchen let loose a thunderous roar as he summoned his other willow leaf sword back to himself, then brought the pair of swords together, upon which a total of over forty star acupoints lit up over the surface of the combined sword.

At the same time, all of his 168 profound acupoints also began to glow radiantly, injecting all of their power into his sword in a frenzy to produce a giant sword of starlight that was aimed directly at Han Li.

In contrast, Han Li was taking a much more calm and composed approach.

He channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts as he adopted a very strange pose in mid-air, tipping himself upside down as he extended his right palm downward.

His movements were quite languid and unhurried, but with every single inch that his right palm descended, the surrounding space would bend and warp further and further. There were large areas of space that were already beginning to fold in on themselves, and his right arm was fully extended right before Feng Wuchen's willow leaf sword was about to reach him.

All of a sudden, Qin Yuan sprang to his feet with an alarmed expression as he yelled, "Wuchen, get back!"

However, it was already too late, and Han Li's right palm struck the tip of Feng Wuchen's sword.

A string of loud cracks rang out as the giant sword of starlight was completely shattered, exploding into countless specks of radiant white starlight.

The two willow leaf swords in Feng Wuchen's hands also shattered into pieces, following which Han Li's palm struck him on the shoulder.

Feng Wuchen's robes instantly exploded to reveal a suit of antiquated white bone armor, which was releasing a barrier of gentle starlight to try and oppose Han Li's attack.

However, the light barrier was also shattered in an instant along with the suit of bone armor, and Feng Wuchen's right shoulder and right arm were completely pulverized, sending blood, bone shards, and muscle fragments erupting in all directions.

Immediately thereafter, Feng Wuchen crashed heavily down onto the ground, and even in his unconscious state, blood was gushing out of his mouth.

The entire platform also shuddered violently, and even though it was just barely able to hold itself together thanks to the star bone fortifications, the entire platform had sunk down by about three feet, and countless cracks had appeared on its surface.

Han Li still recalled the request that Gu Qianxun had made to him, and he clenched his right hand into a fist as he continued to descend toward Feng Wuchen.

"Don't you dare!"

A furious roar rang out as a figure plummeted out of the sky, and with the impact of his landing, the platform was finally shattered into countless pieces.

Han Li cast his gaze forward to discover Qin Yuan glowering at him with intense fury and killing intent in his eyes, and immediately thereafter, all of the other city lords descended onto the destroyed battle platform as well.

Chen Yang had descended right next to Han Li, who cupped his fist in a salute toward E Kuai as he said, "City Lord E, my opponent hasn't surrendered yet, so the battle is still not over. Why has City Lord Qin suddenly stepped onto the platform?"

"You've already won this battle, Fellow Daoist Li, so why not spare his life? What do you say?" E Kuai asked with a warm smile.

"Of course, City Lord E," Han Li replied as he took a step back so that he was half a step behind Chen Yang.

Qin Yuan cradled Feng Wuchen's unconscious body in his arms, then pulled out a small black vial and tipped out several red pills that he fed to Feng Wuchen.

Immediately thereafter, he declared, "Please pardon me, City Lord E, I must take my leave now."

"Go ahead," E Kuai replied with a nod, and Qin Yuan promptly departed with Feng Wuchen still in his arms.

All of the spectators were caught off guard by this sudden turn of events, but it didn't take long before a chorus of boos began to ring out as everyone expressed their displeasure at Qin Yuan's intervention.

E Kuai paid no heed to the reaction of the spectators as he turned to Chen Yang and Han Li and said, "Fellow Daoist Qin is at fault here, but I can understand his actions. I'll get him to compensate your Green Goat City for this."

"Thank you, City Lord E," Chen Yang hurriedly replied as he cupped his fist in a salute, and Han Li also followed suit.

"Alright, the martial gathering still has to continue, so let's not delay things any longer," E Kuai said as he flew back onto the elevated platform.

Sun Tu and Fu Jian exchanged a peculiar glance with each other, then returned to the elevated platform as well.

"That was a splendid performance, Fellow Daoist Li. My status as city lord will surely be significantly bolstered in the wake of your battle. Rest assured, I'll reward you handsomely for your efforts," Chen Yang said through voice transmission.

"It's fine. He provoked me first, and that's why I decided to teach him a lesson. I hope I haven't caused any trouble for you," Han Li replied with a smile.

……

Before long, all of the spectators began loudly chanting Li Feiyu's name.

Zhu Ziyuan and Jin Gong weren't able to see what was happening on the other platform due to there being multiple platforms in the way, but they had been listening carefully this entire time while fighting their sparring match of a battle.

Now that the other battle had concluded, Zhu Ziyuan didn't waste any more time, knocking Jin Gong down from the platform with a single punch, and this entire time, his spear had just been for show.

With that, the two wildly contrasting battles had both drawn to a conclusion, and the next batch of two battles was set to begin shortly thereafter.

The platform used by Zhu Ziyuan and Jin Gong was still largely unscathed, but the other platform had been completely destroyed, so the battle between Gu Qianxun and Fang Chan had to be moved to another platform.

Chapter 913: Conjoined Star Artifact

Gu Qianxun and Fang Chan were standing across from each other on their platform.

A battle between the top representatives of two cities in the third round was a rather rare occurrence, and the nearby stands were packed with spectators who were eagerly awaiting the commencement of the battle.

Instead of returning to the lobby, Han Li had also found a seat in the spectator stands to watch the battle from.

"I learned a lot from our last battle, Fellow Daoist Fang. I had thought that it would have to be at least the semifinals before I encountered you again, but it looks like our rematch has come early," Gu Qianxun said.

At this moment, Fang Chan had become a completely different person compared with his usual dull and foolish self, and his eyes were glowing with fierce battle intent as he said, "I'm very pleased to be able to do battle with you again, Fellow Daoist Gu."

"Begin!" the referee declared, and Gu Qianxun immediately launched herself forward, stomping a large hole into the ground beneath her in the process.

Her body was like a speeding arrow, covering a distance of over a hundred feet in the blink of an eye, and she was seizing the initiative as she lashed out with a delicate-looking fist.

Around twenty to thirty profound acupoints lit up over her arm, and all of the air within a radius of several dozen feet exploded violently in the face of her tremendous power.

However, Chen Yang's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Fang Chan possessed an incredibly powerful physical body, second only to Zhu Ziyuan of Profound City out of all of the combatants in the Five City Martial Gathering, so it was clearly unwise for Gu Qianxun to be engaging him in close quarters combat.

A hint of surprise flashed through Sun Tu's eyes upon seeing this, and Fang Chan was also slightly taken aback, but that didn't affect his reaction speed at all as he lashed out with his own right fist in response.

The two fists clashed with an explosive boom, sending powerful shockwaves erupting in all directions.

Fang Chan's expression changed slightly as he was forced back three steps in retreat, with each step leaving a deep footprint and large cracks on the ground beneath him.

Chen Yang and Sun Tu were astonished to see this, but before they even had a chance to process what they had just witnessed, Gu Qianxun's sleeve erupted into shreds, revealing a rainbow armband on her arm.

There were twenty-one specks of white light on the armband, and it looked as if it were fuse to the skin on Gu Qianxun's arm, making it appear as if the specks of white light were profound acupoints on her body.

"That's a conjoined star artifact! I thought that it was still a project in development, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua," E Kuai exclaimed as he turned to Mistress Liu Hua with a raised eyebrow.

"I was finally able to perfect it after close to a hundred thousand years of experimentation," Mistress Liu Hua replied with a smile, while the other city lords turned to him with stunned expressions.

Han Li looked up at the people on the elevated platform with an intrigued look in his eyes.

They hadn't been communicating through voice transmission, so he was able to overhear their conversation, but he had never heard of a conjoined star artifact before.

"A conjoined star artifact is a star artifact that can fuse with one's body, directly enhancing the user's physical body with the power of the star artifact. Unlike a normal star artifact, not only is there no energy cost to using a conjoined star artifact, there's no need for a refinement process, either, so essentially, Fellow Daoist Gu has been gifted twenty-one profound acupoints.

“Having said that, conjoined star artifacts have only been considered to be theoretically feasible up to this point," Chen Yang explained.

Han Li turned to Mistress Liu Hua with a look of admiration in his eyes upon hearing this. As expected of the Scalptia Spatial Domain's number one tool refinement master to be able to produce something so extraordinary.

"Your tool refinement expertise is truly unmatched, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua. However, may I ask why you've granted Gu Qianxun the honor of possessing such an incredible star artifact?" Sun Tu asked.

"Do I have to receive your approval before I decide who I want to refine weapons for?" Mistress Liu Hua scoffed as he rolled his eyes in disdain.

Sun Tu took a glance at E Kuai, then hurriedly replied, "Of course not, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua. Please forgive me, I was just curious."

Mistress Liu Hua gave a cold harrumph before turning his attention back to the ongoing battle.

After that initial clash, Gu Qianxun continued to charge at Fang Chan without pause, and this time, she unfurled her bone belt from around her waist, upon which it abruptly straightened to form a golden spear.

The tip of the spear was producing a sharp screeching sound as it was thrust directly at Fang Chan's face.

Even though Fang Chan had just been outmatched in strength by Gu Qianxun, he remained completely unfazed, and the battle intent in his eyes only grew even brighter.

He stomped a foot down onto the ground to rush back in retreat while reaching behind himself with his hands, and all of a sudden, a pair of large black axes appeared in his hands.

The axes clashed against the tip of the golden spear, and the latter was instantly knocked away.

Tremendous energy fluctuations erupted in all directions from the clash, causing everyone gathered near the platform to stumble back a few steps.

Gu Qianxun twisted around in a pirouette as she swept her golden spear through the air, targeting Fang Chan's abdomen this time.

In response, Fang Chen swung one of his axes at the oncoming golden spear while simultaneously swinging the other at Gu Qianxun, combining attack and defense into one.

Gu Qianxun darted away to the side while swinging her golden spear around, unleashing a flurry of golden spear projections that descended upon Fang Chan.

Fang Chan remained completely unfazed as he charged directly into the storm of spear projections, and his two axes were dancing around him like a pair of black whirlwinds, keeping the golden spear at bay while also unleashing fierce retaliative blows.

A string of metallic clangs rang out in rapid succession, and several hundred exchanges took place in the blink of an eye.

With neither side willing to back down, both of them soon began sustaining injuries.

A gash that was around half a foot in length had been sliced into Gu Qianxun's lower abdomen, while large holes had also been pierced into Fang Chan's body, but neither of them paid any heed to their injuries as they continued to clash over and over again.

The entire platform was trembling violently beneath them as if it were struggling to contain their power, and all of the spectators were a little dumbstruck by the intensity of the battle.

Fang Chan's was desperately trying to turn the tables, but Gu Qianxun's physical prowess was superior to his thanks to her conjoined star artifact, and her spear techniques were also extremely dangerous and versatile. As a result, Fang Chan was constantly being forced back, and before long, he had arleady reached the edge of the platform.

An agitated look flashed through his eyes as he swept both of his axes through the air to knock the golden spear aside, then opened his mouth up wide as a layer of white light emerged over his face, while a series of profound acupoints appeared near his nose and mouth.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of white soundwaves erupted out of his nose and mouth before sweeping toward Gu Qianxun.

However, Gu Qianxun had clearly already anticipated this attack, and she instantly darted away to the side to evade the soundwaves.

In the blink of an eye, the white soundwaves spread over an area of several thousand feet.

By the time they reached the spectator stands, the soundwaves had already become far less potent, but many of the spectators still experienced whole-body numbness, immobilization, and even asphyxiation.

Han Li just so happened to have been caught within the soundwaves as well, and to his surprise, his entire body had become so numb that even lifting a finger had become a very difficult task.

Even though Gu Qianxun had reacted very quickly, she was still able to completely evade the white soundwaves, and her body instantly stiffened, while her face turned deathly pale.

However, in the next instant, an unnatural flush suddenly appeared on her face, followed by her entire body. Her skin began quivering as if there were something moving beneath it, and she instantly regained her mobility befored thrusting her golden spear at Fang Chan's waist.

Is that the Hazy Helmet Technique? No, she's managed to shrug off the effects of the soundwaves by forcibly elevating her bloodline powers to their peak, Han Li thought to himself with a contemplative expression.

However, this was clearly extremely taxing on the body, and he didn't know how many more times Gu Qianxun would be able to employ this strategy.

Fang Chan clearly hadn't anticipated that Gu Qianxun would be able to immediately retaliate even after being struck by his soundwave attack, so he was a little slow to dodge, and Gu Qianxun's golden spear sliced a gash into his waist that was deep enough to expose bone.

Fang Chan's eyes instantly turned bright red as a string of cracks and pops rang out from his joints, and his body abruptly swelled to twice its original size, while his skin turned a dark red color.

In the blink of an eye, he had transformed into a ferocious humanoid beast, and his aura was instantly significantly elevated, while the wounds on his body began to rapidly heal.

What was even more astonishing was that the white light emanating from his profound acupoints had also turned a bright red color, releasing bursts of crimson energy that swirled around him.

The nearby space trembled and buzzed, while the entire platform was also quaking violently, and a series of cracks began to appear on its surface, as if it weren't unable to withstand Fang Chan's power.

On the elevated platform, both Chen Yang and Sun Tu were looking on with serious expressions, while a hint of intrigue had also appeared in E Kuai's eyes.

Chapter 914: Sudden Suspension

"I was planning to save this for Zhu Ziyuan, but it looks like you'll be getting a taste before him!" Fang Chan chortled with a wild, animalistic look in his eyes.

Gu Qianxun's expression remained unchanged, as if she couldn't even see Fang Chan's transformation, and she sprang forward while his transformation was taking place to plunge her golden spear into his back.

However, as soon as the spear struck the crimson energy circling around his body, it was instantly stopped cold in its tracks before sliding away to the side.

Fang Chan swung one of axes around in retaliation to strike the golden spear, and a resounding clang rang out as Gu Qianxun stumbled back in retreat, with her spear almost wrenched out of her grasp.

Fang Chan then immediately pounced at her, moving far faster than before, reaching her in the blink of an eye before swinging his axes viciously down upon her.

The crimson energy around him surged onto the pair of axes as they sliced through the air, causing the space in their wake to tremble violently.

Gu Qianxun hurriedly dodged to the side, only just barely managing to evade the pair of axes, which crashed down onto the platform, slicing it apart like a giant piece of tofu.

"Everyone, get back!" E Kuai ordered in an authoritative voice as he rose to his feet, and the people gathered around the platform hurriedly dispersed, while Han Li also retreated into the distance with the other spectators.

Even though the platform had collapsed, the battle was still far from over, and at this moment, Fang Chan was like a deranged demon, swinging his axes through the air with devastating power.

Gu Qianxun didn't dare to fight fire with fire, so all she could do was take evasive measures.

Thankfully, with the platform destroyed, the battlefield had increased significantly in area, granting her more space to maneuver around in.

One giant rift after another was sliced into the ground, sending loose rocks flying in all directions, while the spectators in the stands hurriedly fled for their lives.

On the elevated platform, Chen Yang was looking on with an anxious expression, while Sun Tu was also intently observing Fang Chan with a grim look of concern on his face.

Fang Chan's expression was becoming more and more deranged by the second, and the entire area around him was filled with countless ax projections.

Gu Qianxun was made to resemble a small raft in a vast and turbulent sea, looking as if it could capsize at any moment, but she was always able to evade Fang Chan's attacks right in the nick of time.

After unleashing such a ferocious barrage of attacks, much of the crimson energy around Fang Chan's body had already faded away. A look of agitation flashed through his eyes as he let loose a furious roar and swung his axes toward Gu Qianxun from both the left and the right, trying to end the battle in one fell swoop.

Gu Qianxun's eyes instantly lit up upon seeing this, and she twisted around in mid-air, adopting a very strange pose to just barely evade the pair of axes, following which she pounced forward with her golden spear extended in front of her.

The spear passed through the gap between the pair of axes, then pierced through the layer of crimson energy around Fang Chan en route to his throat.

"I've got you now!" Fang Chan chortled as he brought his axes back in the blink of an eye, positioning in front of himself to form a barrier that kept the golden spear at bay.

At the same time, a burst of even more formidable white soundwaves erupted out of his nose and mouth toward Gu Qianxun, while the crimson energy around him transformed into a volley of crimson arrows that rained down upon her, encompassing the entire area within a radius of several dozen feet.

The arrows produced a terrifying screeching sound as they raced through the air, leaving trails of black marks in the space in their wake.

A grim look appeared on Chen Yang's face upon seeing this, while Sun Tu's eyes lit up with elation.

However, right at this moment, Gu Qianxun suddenly twisted around once again, and she darted away to the side at an incredible speed, almost as if there were some type of external force dragging her away. To everyone's astonishment, she was able to evade all of the soundwaves and crimson arrows to outflank Fang Chan.

Fang Chan was completely caught off guard, and he hurriedly attempted to turn around, but all of a sudden, a pained look appeared on his face. At the same time, the crimson light radiating from his profound acupoints began to tremble as his entire body stiffened in agony.

Gu Qianxun immediately pounced on this opportunity as several dull thumps rang out within her body, and her arms abruptly swelled to around twice their original thickness as she thrust her golden spear toward Fang Chan's temple at an astonishing speed.

After unleashing that all-out attack, most of the crimson energy around Fang Chan had faded away, and what little remained was no match for Gu Qianxun's spear.

The golden spear pierced through the thin layer of crimson energy with ease, yet right as it was about to plunge its way into Fang Chan's head, a thin beam of white light hurtled through the air to strike the spear from the side, instantly knocking it away.

Gu Qianxun hurriedly grabbed onto the spear with both hands to prevent it from flying out of her grasp, following which she turned her gaze to the elevated platform.

On the elevated platform, E Kuai lowered his arm, and the speck of white light on his fingertip faded away as he said, "Let's end the battle there. The winner is Gu Qianxun of Green Goat City."

Gu Qianxun cupped her fist in a salute toward the elevated platform upon hearing this, following which the golden spear in her hand reverted back into a golden bone chain that she wrapped around her own waist.

At this point, Fang Chan had also recovered from his immobilized state, and he began tapping various parts of his own body with his fingers, upon which his enlarged body quickly shrank back down to its original size.

After such a grueling battle, Fang Chan was left looking extremely pale, and he turned to Gu Qianxun as he declared, "I underestimated you this time, but you won't win next time."

All of the nearby spectators were running for their lives just a moment ago, and it took them some time to register what had just happened before all of them erupted into thunderous cheers.

The Green Goat City cultivators were all ecstatic, and they immediately swarmed Gu Qianxun to congratulate her.

Meanwhile, Han Li was still observing Gu Qianxun from the spectator stands, thinking back to the last evasive maneuver that she had displayed with a contemplative look on his face.

On the elevated platform, Chen Yang was barely able to contain his own excitement.

He had gone into this round mentally prepared for both Han Li and Gu Qianxun to be eliminated, so this outcome was an incredibly pleasant surprise.

Mistress Liu Hua also heaved a sigh of relief as a hint of elation appeared in his eyes.

Sun To naturally wasn't very pleased by Fang Chan's unexpected loss, but he remained composed as he rose to his feet and cupped his fist toward E Kuai in a grateful salute.

"Thank you for saving my disciple, City Lord E."

"Your disciple is a very bright talent, so I naturally had to save him," E Kuai replied with a dismissive wave of his hand.

Sun Tu thanked E Kuai once again, then offered his congratulations to Chen Yang before sitting back down.

Right at this moment, a black-robed man hurriedly rushed over from afar with an urgent look on his face, and he swooped onto the elevated platform before whispering something into E Kuai's ear.

E Kuai's expression instantly changed slightly as he sprang to his feet, and he cast his gaze out of the city with a grim look on his face.

"Did something happen, City Lord E?" Chen Yang and the other city lords hurriedly asked.

The black-robed man had spoken to E Kuai using voice transmission just now, so they hadn't heard what was said, but it was clear from E Kuai's reaction that a crisis was afoot.

……

"From this moment onward, the Five City Martial Gathering will be temporarily suspended. Everyone, return to your homes, and do not come out unless it's absolutely necessary!" E Kuai ordered, and his voice rumbled across the entire Asura Arena.

Everyone was rooted to the spot upon hearing this, and the two combatants fighting on the other platform also stopped what they were doing with confused looks on their faces.

All of a sudden, the entire arena had fallen deathly silent.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze up toward the elevated platform, where E Kuai had turned to the other city lords, and he ordered, "Take your people and return to your respective courtyards. From now on, all of you are forbidden from wandering in the city!"

Meanwhile, the black-robed man flew away like a giant eagle, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

The other city lords' expressions changed slightly upon seeing this.

The speed displayed by the black-robed man exceeded even their own.

After everyone had a chance to register what E Kuai just announced, a commotion slowly began to ring out within the Asura Arena, and the spectators began to file out of the venue.

The other city lords also gathered their subordinates before departing from the Asura Arena to return to the courtyards that they were staying in, and not long after their departure, the sound of a drum began to ring out from deep within Profound City.

As soon as the sound of the drumming was heard, the entire city instantly erupted into a frenzy, with shops hurriedly closing their doors and pedestrians rushing back to their homes.

"That's the sound of the Heavenly Might War Drum... What's happening?" Chen Yang asked with a grim expression.

"The Heavenly Might War Drum is only struck during times of crisis. Could it be that Profound City is under attack?" Sun Tu mused.

"Perhaps we're being attacked by Puppet City," Qin Yuan speculated.

"That's definitely a possibility. If so, then they sure came at an interesting time," Sun Tu said as he clasped his hands behind his back.

Han Li paid no heed to the discussion taking place between the four city lords as he cast his gaze out of the city, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

"In any case, let's follow City Lord E's orders and return to our courtyard," Gu Qianxun said.

"You're right, Fellow Daoist Gu. Let's go," Chen Yang said, then bade farewell to the other three city lords before promptly departing.

Chapter 915: Ulterior Motive

"Stay in your residences and don't go anywhere. I don't want to hear any baseless speculations, either. Don't do anything until I come back," Chen Yang ordered as soon as he and the other Green Goat City cultivators returned to their courtyard.

After that, he immediately turned and made his way out of the courtyard.

Everyone else exchanged a few glances with one another, then returned to their residences.

As Han Li returned to his room, he couldn't help but wonder what was happening. Could it be that Profound City really was under attack from Puppet City?

He was planning to ask Gu Qianxun if she had any information to share, but it was clear from her earlier reaction that she was just as perplexed as everyone else.

He had no interest in the conflict between Profound City and Puppet City at all, but with the Five City Martial Gathering put on hold, there was no telling if he would be able to secure a Heavenly Qilin Crystal, and with the threat of the Black Tribulation Centipede constantly looming over his head, it was very difficult for him to do anything or go anywhere.

After some contemplation, Han Li shook his head to rid himself of this pointless train of thought.

At this point, all he could do was watch the situation unfold.

Meanwhile, the entire city was placed under lockdown, with groups of armorclad guards stationed at all of the city's important roads.

At the same time, a burst of rumbling rang out from the ground near the city gates, and a series of entrances of underground passageways appeared, out of which more armorclad guards came pouring out before stationing themselves atop the city walls.

The stone slabs on the city walls also began to part and split, while a black stone pagoda emerged roughly every one thousand feet.

The pagodas were fitted with astonishingly massive crossbows with enormous arrows nocked on them, and the arrows were giving off a sharp and forbidding gleam.

Most of the arrows were silver in color, but some were of a fiery red color with a series of white patterns engraved upon them, and they were clearly a special type of arrow.

Aside from these pagodas, many catapults, mechanical weapons, and even puppets of different descriptions had appeared on the city wall, while some giant mechanical weapons had also emerged on the Myriad Profound Mountain Range near Profound City.

……

After meditating in his room for close to a day, Han Li was suddenly visited by a Green Goat City servant, who invited him to Chen Yang's residence.

Upon arriving in the guest hall of Chen Yang's residence, Han Li discovered that there were already seven or eight people gathered inside, with the likes of Gu Qianxun, Yi Liya, and Xuanyuan Xing among them.

Gu Qianxun gave Han Li a slight nod as he entered the room, and he sat down beside her.

"Right now, the entire city has already been placed under lockdown, and things are not looking good," Gu Qianxun said.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he offered no response.

"I know what you're worried about, Fellow Daoist Li," Gu Qianxun said through voice transmission. "Rest assured, even if the Five City Martial Gathering is canceled altogether, I'll help you secure a Heavenly Qilin Crystal."

"Why would you help me?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I have my reasons. To put it in simple terms, you're still useful to me at the moment," Gu Qianxun replied.

"I feel much more reassured after hearing you say that," Han Li said with a smile.

Before long, all of the Green Goat City cultivators had arrived, and Chen Yang emerged from the inner chamber.

"I've gathered all of you here to discuss what's happening outside. I have been informed by City Lord E that a large number of Puppet City troops have been sighted thousands of kilometers to the north of Profound City," Chen Yang declared with a grim expression.

Even though everyone had already guessed at the possibility of an attack from Puppet City, everyone's expressions still changed slightly upon hearing this.

In contrast with the fear and hatred that had appeared in everyone else's eyes, Han Li's eyes had lit up slightly, and he saw this as an opportunity.

After failing to find Violet Spirit within Profound City, he had planned to travel to Puppet City once the opportunity arose, and this exact opportunity was presenting itself.

"How many people have come from Puppet City? Is it possible that this is merely a group of Puppet City troops that have stumbled into our territory?" someone asked.

"We don't know exactly how many of them there are at the moment, but City Lord E has already confirmed that City Lord Sha Xin of Puppet City is also among them. Profound City has already issued a warning, but it's fallen upon deaf ears, and they're continuing to march toward Profound City," Chen Yang said in a grim manner.

"Is there going to be another war between our two cities?" Gu Qianxun mused with tightly furrowed brows.

"The fact that City Lord Sha Xin is personally leading the Puppet City troops on a march toward Profound City without any forewarning is definitely not a good sign," Chen Yang said.

The entire room fell silent, and everyone turned their attention to Chen Yang, waiting for him to continue.

"Rest assured, everyone. Right now, all of the most powerful cultivators of our five cities are gathered in Profound City right now, and we also have the home advantage, so we're extremely well prepared to handle an attack from Puppet City," Chen Yang said, and the tense atmosphere was instantly eased a little.

"During this time, prepare as much as you can. If a war really does begin, we'll definitely all be called upon," Chen Yang continued, and everyone gave a collective affirmative response.

Chen Yang gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, then announced some new rules that had been introduced in the city during this special time.

"Fellow Daoist Gu, do you think the objective of the lord of Puppet City really is just to attack Profound City? Is it possible that there's an ulterior motive at play here?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"I don't know. Profound City and Puppet City have joined forces at certain points in history, but they've always been at each other's throats the majority of the time, and a lot of bad blood has been accumulated over the years, so whenever the two cities clash, there's always a great deal of bloodshed," Gu Qianxun replied.

"I'm assuming the times when the two cities have joined forces were when certain external factors were at play, right?" Han Li asked.

"It's almost always when there's a natural disaster or a large-scale scaled beast attack is afoot. If I recall correctly, the last war between the two cities took place thirty thousand years ago, and White Rock City was the main battlefield on that occasion.

“Almost the entire city was destroyed, and countless casualties were suffered on both sides. It was during that war that the previous lord of White Rock City perished, and it was only then that Sun Tu was able to take over as city lord," Gu Qianxun replied.

"I didn't think that there would be such an intense conflict between the survivors in this realm that's almost been completely forgotten by the outside world," Han Li mused.

"Resources in this realm are extremely scarce to begin with, and all of the past conflicts have arisen over these scarce resources. Regardless of whether it's Profound City or Puppet City, both of them share the same ultimate objective, which is to leave this godforsaken place," Gu Qianxun replied.

"I should've guessed that this was the case. However, I presume that it's most likely those in positions of power in the two cities that are trying to leave this realm, right?" Han Li asked.

"Who knows? In any case, if the two cities really do clash, then make sure to proceed with the utmost caution. In such a large-scale conflict, any single of us is as insignificant as a speck of dust," Gu Qianxun cautioned.

"City Lord Chen, even though the troops of Puppet City have appeared outside Profound City, there's no guarantee that our Green Goat City isn't also one of their targets. Right now, with all of us in Profound City, if they decide to attack Green Goat City, then our city stands no chance," Yi Liya said.

"I'm well aware of that. However, we're currently forbidden from leaving Profound City, and even if we set off back to Green Goat City right away, we definitely won't be able to get there in time, so all we can do now is pray," Chen Yang sighed.

The meeting concluded shortly thereafter, and everyone was dismissed.

The cultivators of the other three cities had also been informed of the approaching Puppet City army, and everyone was making preparations for a potential war.

Some time later, the beating of the Heavenly Might War Drum rang out once again.

At this point, the previously lively and bustling streets had become completely deserted, and the few pedestrians walking on the streets were hurriedly rushing back to their homes, while all of the shops were closed.

Patrol groups of armorclad guards were constantly roaming the main streets and roads in the city, further adding to the tension that was permeating throughout the entire city.

Countless armorclad soldiers were busy at work on the city wall above the main gate of Profound City, and right at this moment, a group of people arrived on the city wall.

The soldiers in front of them hurriedly parted to let them through, and it was a group of seven or eight people that was led by E Kuai.

Upon arriving atop the city wall, E Kuai cast his gaze into the distance in silence, and none of the people with him dared to disrupt him.

Moments later, E Kuai's expression darkened slightly, and he could see a gray line approaching on the distant horizon amid a burst of thunderous rumbling.

The armorclad soldiers on the city wall quickly spotted the approaching gray line as well, and all of them tightened their grips around their weapons in anticipation of a potential clash.

E Kuai swept an arm through the air in an expressionless manner, and the city gate down below instantly swung open.

Countess armorclad soldiers flooded out of the city, with most of them traveling on foot, while roughly a third of them were riding atop various types of scaled beasts, and they arranged themselves into several formations in front of Profound City.

At the same time, a sharp screech rang out from the nearby Myriad Profound Mountain Range, and a flock of flying scaled beasts swooped down from the mountains. Most of them were a type of vulture scaled beast, and they were also carrying armorclad soldiers on their backs, forming a series of aerial formations.

At this point, the gray line on the horizon had become far larger than before, and one could begin to make out a formidable army consisting of countless puppets.

The puppet army seemed to have detected the hostility from Profound City, and it drew to a halt hundreds of kilometers away from Profound City, not advancing any further beyond that point.

The hearts of the soldiers on the city wall were brimming with battle intent, and all of them were looking at E Kuai, waiting for him to issue the order for them to charge into battle.

However, to everyone's surprise, the puppet army in the distance continued to remain in the distance without advancing any further, and E Kuai's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this as he refrained from issuing any orders.

As a result, an impasse ensued.

Chapter 916: False Alarm

Close to half a day passed by in a flash, and it was starting to get dark.

The puppet army continued to refrain from advancing, but nor did it retreat, and it remained in the distance like a permanent fixture on the horizon.

On the city wall, the black-robed man asked in a disgruntled voice, "What the hell are these bastards up to? Are they plotting something?"

The other people gathered around E Kuai were just as perplexed, and all of them were speculating about Puppet City's intentions.

As for E Kuai himself, he remained standing in silence with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Even after much speculation, no consensus was reached, and the black-robed man turned to E Kuai with a hesitant expression as he began, "City Lord E, should we..."

"So long as the enemy doesn't move, we won't do anything, either. There's no need to make any rash moves. Keep a lookout for any sneak attacks and send out some scouts to find out exactly how many people Puppet City have sent on this occasion," E Kuai instructed.

The people around E Kuai promptly departed to carry out his orders, and soon, only the black-robed man was left.

"City Lord E, why haven't we called upon the people from the four cities to face the enemy together? There may not be many of them, but all of them are the cream of the crop from their respective cities, so they're still a force to be reckoned with," the black-robed man said.

"At this point, the situation is still unclear, so I won't call upon them for now," E Kuai replied with a shake of his head.

A perplexed look flashed through the black-robed man's eyes upon hearing this, but he didn't say anything further.

"I have to go take care of something, so I'll leave things here to you, Shao Ying. If the Puppet City army makes any hostile moves, then do as you see fit, and there's no need to consult me," E Kuai said.

Shao Ying faltered slightly upon hearing this, but before he had a chance to ask any questions, E Kuai had already vanished from the spot.

As night fell, the standoff between the two cities continued, with neither side initiating an attack.

The gentle moonlight basked the entire landscape in a cold, white glow, and at this moment, there was a woman in a white dress standing on a short hill hundreds of kilometers away from Profound City, looking up at the sky while humming a tune to herself.

The woman's features were concealed behind a black veil, but she had an extremely seductive figure that also somehow gave off an air of childlike purity and innocence.

It was a very strange combination of qualities to possess, presenting a unique sense of allure to the beholder.

Right at this moment, E Kuai suddenly appeared around a hundred feet away from the woman, and he said in a cold voice, "I can see that you've made some great progress in your Profound Maiden Seduction, Fellow Daoist Sha Xin. Having said that, it's quite courageous of you to have ventured away from your army to come here on your own so close to my Profound City."

"If you wish to attack me, then go right ahead, Fellow Daoist E," Sha Xin said in a lazy voice as she slowly turned to face E Kuai.

At the same time, the air of purity and innocence about her abruptly faded, and a wave of boundless seduction surged out of her body, causing even the surrounding landscape to appear more gentle and alluring.

E Kuai gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, but didn't attack.

"I knew you wouldn't attack a frail woman like myself unprovoked, Fellow Daoist E," Sha Xin giggled.

"Cut the chit-chat. Why did you invite me to meet you here through voice transmission? If you wish to spark another war between our two cities, then I'll gladly oblige," E Kuai declared in a cold voice, seemingly completely unaffected by Sha Xin's seduction.

"I have no intention of instigating a war between our two cities, Fellow Daoist E. Instead, I've come here because I have some important matters to discuss with you," Sha Xin said with a faint smile.

Her aura changed drastically once again as she spoke, and all of her seductive qualities faded, while her exquisite body also instantly lost all of its allure. It was as if she had suddenly become a completely ordinary and unremarkable woman.

"What do you want to discuss with me?" E Kuai asked.

"I would like to propose a joint venture between the two of us," Sha Xin replied with a smile.

"If you have something to say, then spit it out," E Kuai harrumphed coldly.

"There's no need to play dumb, Fellow Daoist E. Even after all these years, that place has still constantly been on our minds, and my Puppet City has already found the entrance to it. I hope you didn't intend to keep that place entirely to yourself," Sha Xin said in a cold manner.

E Kuai's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, and he began to glower intently at Sha Xin with a hostile look in his eyes.

"There's no need to look at me like that, Fellow Daoist E. I didn't find the location of that entrance through any snide or underhanded tactics. Instead, our Puppet City found the entrance fair and square through extensive exploration," Sha Xin declared in a righteous manner.

"I'm sure that's true," E Kuai harrumphed in an unconvinced fashion. "How could I possibly be planning to keep that place to myself? If you've discovered the entrance, then I'm sure you're already aware of the situation inside. Given how perilous it is in there, I have no intention of venturing inside anytime soon."

"Do you take me for a fool, Fellow Daoist E? I may have only recently discovered the entrance, but even I could sense that the many natural hazards inside were gradually becoming less and less potent over time. I presume the potency of those natural hazards fluctuate on a cyclical basis, and this is when they're at their weakest.

“On top of that, I heard that you're offering some very extravagant rewards for this edition of the Five City Martial Gathering. Aren't you doing this so that you can select people to venture into that place?" Sha Xin asked with a seductive smile.

E Kuai offered no response, but his expression had darkened even further.

"Even though the natural hazards inside are waning in power, they're still far too powerful for our two cities to contend with individually. The only chance we have of entering that place is for our two cities to join forces, and that's why I've come all this way to discuss this matter with you. I hope you can make the right decision, Fellow Daoist E," Sha Xin continued.

"And what if I disagree?" E Kuai asked.

"In that case, I'll have no choice but to begin attacking Profound City, and I'll continue attacking until the natural hazards regain their potency, so none of us will be able to go in," Sha Xin replied with a faint smile.

A cold look flashed through E Kuai's eyes upon hearing this, and a terrifying aura erupted out of his body, causing the entire space within a radius of dozens of kilometers to tremble violently.

However, Sha Xin remained standing on the spot in a calm and composed fashion, while E Kuai's aura automatically parted around her, leaving her completely unaffected.

E Kuai took a deep breath, and his aura receded like the tide.

After a brief silence, he asked, "What type of collaboration do you propose, Fellow Daoist Sha?"

A pleased smile appeared on Sha Xin's face upon hearing this.

……

The night quickly passed by, and to everyone's surprise, the Puppet City army began to retreat the next morning.

Before long, the Puppet City army had vanished without a trace, and Profound City was lifted from its state of lockdown.

With that, a major crisis was averted, leaving all of the citizens of Profound City feeling a combination of befuddlement and relief.

After all, everyone wanted to avoid a war between the two cities if possible.

Several days later.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed in his room, channeling the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts to refine the A tier beast core.

The A tier beast core contained an enormous amount of starpower, and even though he had already been refining it for many days with the assistance of the Heaven Controlling Vial, he was still yet to fully absorb it.

A new profound acupoint had appeared on his body, and it was displaying signs of opening, but was ultimately still yet to be fully opened.

Han Li opened his eyes, then strode over to the window to cast his gaze toward the city lord's manor outside.

At this point, several days had already passed since the Puppet City crisis, and the Puppet City army hadn't been sighted since its retreat.

Even so, E Kuai displayed no intention of continuing the Five City Martial Gathering, and the cultivators from the four subsidiary cities continued to remain in their respective courtyards.

However, early this morning, E Kuai had summoned the four city lords for a meeting.

Right at this moment, the sound of footsteps suddenly rang out from outside, and Han Li opened his door to discover a servant from Green Goat City.

The servant was quite startled to see the door suddenly open in front of him, and he extended a respectful bow as he said, "Senior Li, City Lord Chen would like to see you."

Han Li nodded in response, then took another glance in the direction of the city lord's manor before making his way to Chen Yang's residence.

Shortly thereafter, he arrived at Chen Yang's residence, only to find the doors tightly shut.

Han Li was just about to knock on the door when they swung open on their own, and Chen Yang's voice rang out from inside.

"Come in, Fellow Daoist Li."

Han Li stepped into the room, and the door swung shut behind him, following which a layer of white light appeared over its surface, completely isolating the room from the outside world.

At this moment, Gu Qianxun and Xuanyuan Xing were also in the room with Chen Yang, while Daoist Xie was standing silently behind him in his usual expressionless manner.

Han Li was rather surprised to see this. He had thought that Chen Yang would've summoned everyone for a debriefing about the current situation in Profound City, but that was clearly not the case.

Chapter 917: Great Ruins

"Take a seat, Fellow Daoist Li," Chen Yang said to Han Li with a hint of excitement in his eyes.

Han Li took a glance at Chen Yang's excited expression, then sat down beside Gu Qianxun.

"I've summoned the three of you here today because I would have a huge opportunity to present to you," Chen Yang declared, and Han Li's trio was rather taken aback to hear this.

"To make a long story short, a secret area has appeared deep within the Scalptia Spatial Domain, one that's filled with countless precious treasures. This is an extremely rare opportunity, and City Lord E Kuai has decided to end the Five City Martial Gathering and lead the top sixteen cultivators into this secret area," Chen Yang continued with a smile.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

How had this supposed secret area suddenly popped up out of nowhere?

However, Gu Qianxun and Xuanyuan Xing were both quite excited to hear this, and the latter asked, "Is that true, City Lord Chen?"

"As true as true can be," Chen Yang replied with a smile.

"Would you be able to elaborate any further, City Lord Chen?" Han Li asked.

"You only recently arrived in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so you may not be very familiar with this place, Fellow Daoist Li. The Scalptia Spatial Domain is an extremely mysterious place, and even though our Profound City has already been standing for countless years, we've still yet to uncover all of the domain's secrets.

“There are many secrets lurking deep within the Scalptia Spatial Domain, as well as countless precious natural treasures, and all of the most premium resources in our Profound City, including the prizes for this Five City Martial Gathering, like the Heavenly Qilin Crystal and the Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud, are all obtained from the domain's depths.

“This secret area is the most significant opportunity to have arisen within the Scalptia Spatial Domain in the past one million years, so this is truly not an opportunity to be passed up on," Chen Yang explained.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but internally, he was also beginning to grow a little excited.

"This does sound like a splendid opportunity, but I'm assuming that a place that's harboring so many precious natural treasures is also going to be very dangerous, right?" Han Li asked.

"Of course. These secret areas are filled with all types of unknown dangers. However, risk and reward have always come hand in hand, so consider this matter carefully, and if you don't want to go, then I won't force you," Chen Yang replied.

Han Li's trio fell silent upon hearing this, and Chen Yang made no effort to rush them, merely waiting in silence as they weighed up their options.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he took a glance at Daoist Xie out of his peripheral vision.

Daoist Xie remained standing completely still on the spot in an expressionless manner, but one of his fingers moved ever so slightly.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon seeing this, and he suddenly said, "City Lord Chen, there's something that I want to ask you: does the incident concerning the Puppet City army a few days ago have something to do with this secret area?"

"The people from Puppet City did indeed come for the secret area, and they'll also be sending their own cultivators into it," Chen Yang replied.

Slightly concerned looks appeared on the faces of both Gu Qianxun and Xuanyuan Xing upon hearing this.

Profound City and Puppet City were sworn enemies, so conflicts would be sure to break out if cultivators from the two cities were to encounter each other in the secret area, thereby making the secret area an even more dangerous place.

After some brief contemplation, Han Li declared, "I would like to go and take a look at this secret area."

Chen Yang was ecstatic to hear this, and he replied, "Great! What do you say, Fellow Daoist Gu, Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan?"

The hesitant look on Xuanyuan Xing's face faded away as he nodded and replied, "This is too alluring an opportunity for me to pass up."

With both Han Li and Xuanyuan Xing agreeing to go, Gu Qianxun's doubts seemed to have also been erased, and she smiled as she declared, "In that case, I would like to come along as well."

"Alright, with all three of you agreeing to come, our Green Goat City won't lose to any of the other subsidiary cities in terms of overall power. You can go back to rest now. The date of departure still hasn't been decided, so I'll keep you posted," Chen Yang said with a smile.

Han Li's trio nodded in response before standing up to depart, when Chen Yang suddenly continued, "By the way, this is still a confidential matter at this point, so don't tell anyone else."

Han Li's trio immediately gave a collective affirmative response before the three of them departed.

Following their departure, Chen Yang also left his residence to travel to the city lord's manor.

One morning, around half a month later.

At this moment, there were close to twenty people gathering on a white stone plaza in the city lord's manor, and they were split up into the five groups.

The group that was furthest to the left had the most people at five, and they were led by none other than Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing.

"Ziqing, you didn't make it into the final sixteen to begin with, so listen to me and stay in Profound City for your own safety," Zhu Ziyuan said with tightly furrowed brows.

"I don't care! Wherever you go, I go! Besides, City Lord E already agreed to let me come, so it doesn't matter what you say," Zhu Ziqing replied with a smile.

Zhu Ziyuan had always been absolutely obedient to E Kuai, so he could only heave a resigned sigh upon hearing this.

The group to their right consisted of a trio of White Rock City cultivators, led by Fang Chan.

The loss that he had suffered to Gu Qianxun didn't seem to have affected him at all, and at this moment, he was still tearing chunks of flesh off from a thick and greasy beast bone with a joyous smile on his face.

In contrast, the group of Profound End City cultivators next to them were in far lower spirits. Their leader, Feng Wuchen, was standing in silence with a dark look on his face, and he refused to converse with anyone, only taking the occasional glance at the Green Goat City cultivators to their right.

After half a month of recuperation, he had mostly recovered from his injuries, and he had also grown a new arm, which was wrapped in bandages like Duan Tong's.

Right next to them were the Green Goat City trio, while the Excess Passage City trio were situated the furthest to the right.

"The fact that the city lord's manor gathered all of us here indicates that we're most likely going to be setting off today, but I still don't know exactly where we're going. Have you received any information, Fellow Daoist Gu?" Han Li asked.

"Prematurely ending the Five City Martial Gathering is already a very strange occurrence, and a temporary alliance between Profound City and Puppet City is an even stranger one. Both cities have been very tight-lipped about all of this, so I haven't received any information, either," Gu Qianxun replied as her brows furrowed slightly.

Profound City and Puppet City had been sworn enemies for countless years, so it was near unimaginable for the two to work together for a common cause.

"The fact that the two cities are willing to set their differences aside and join forces most likely means that we're going somewhere extremely dangerous indeed," Xuanyuan Xing mused in a concerned manner.

"Didn't City Lord Chen say that you're free to back out if you don't want to go?" Gu Qianxun jibed with an amused smile.

"He did, but he's also made it clear that this is perhaps one of the biggest opportunities to have ever arisen in the history of the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so how could I let it slip through my fingers? I wouldn't be feeling so conflicted if the potential reward wasn't so tantalizing," Xuanyuan Xing sighed with a wry smile.

Han Li didn't really care much about all of that. Instead, he was much more interested in finding a way to remove the Black Tribulation Centipede in his body, as well as to find out more information about Shi Chuankong and Violet Spirit.

With the Five City Martial Gathering coming to a premature end, he was unable to fulfill his agreement with Mistress Liu Hua, and once he left Profound City, it was going to be very difficult to find out more information about Shi Chuankong.

Right as these thoughts were running through his mind, the sound of footsteps rang out near the plaza, heralding the arrival of a group of around a dozen figures, led by none other than E Kuai.

Behind him were Mistress Liu Hua and the other four city lords, and there were five or six more people further behind them, the two of which that stood out the most to Han Li were Daoist Xie and the black-robed man, who were standing behind Chen Yang and Mistress Liu Hua, respectively.

As he swept his gaze over the other four figures, one more person caught his attention.

It was a figure standing beside the black-robed man. The lower half of his face was concealed behind a black cloth, and his entire body was clad in a suit of bone armor, leaving only his purple eyes exposed.

On top of that, he had a head of extremely distinctive curly, silver hair, and with those two features alone, Han Li was able to identify him as none other than Shi Chuankong!

Han Li was ecstatic to see him, and he was just about to communicate with Shi Chuankong through voice transmission when he spotted Chen Yang shaking his head at him, warning him not to make any rash moves.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he turned his gaze back to Shi Chuankong to discover that his face was completely devoid of emotion, and he was staring blankly forward without any deviation, clearly indicating that he wasn't in a normal state of mind.

Gu Qianxun quickly noticed the look on his face, and she asked, "What's wrong?"

"It's nothing, I just suddenly thought of an old acquaintance of mine," Han Li replied with a smile, following which his expression returned to normal.

Gu Qianxun cast a skeptical gaze toward Shi Chuankong upon hearing this, but she didn't notice anything amiss.

After arriving on the elevated platform in front of the plaza, E Kuai swept his gaze over everyone present as he declared, "I'm sure all of you have already been informed of the emergence of the Great Ruins. That is the reason why the Five City Martial Gathering has been canceled, and we have decided to work with Puppet City to venture into these ruins together. The fact that all of you are standing here today means that you have all agreed to come as well."

A variety of different expressions appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this, ranging from elation to concern, and Han Li asked through voice transmission, "What are these Great Ruins, Fellow Daoist Gu?"

Chapter 918: Doubts

Gu Qianxun was clearly very surprised by this question, and she replied through voice transmission, "You don't know of the Great Ruins, Fellow Daoist Li? The Great Ruins are the most special area in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, and it's said to be home to a vast amount of hidden treasures. I've heard that Profound City and Puppet City have both already been searching for it for countless years, it looks like they must've finally found it."

Right at this moment, E Kuai swept his gaze over everyone present and declared, "This is going to be a long and perilous journey, so if anyone's still hesitating about whether to go or not, this will be your last chance to pull out. Once you leave the city, abandoning your post will be seen as desertion."

Not a single one of the sixteen cultivators from the four cities expressed a desire to back out.

"Good. It looks like all of you possess the mental fortitude required to reap significant rewards on this trip. Even though we are temporarily working with Puppet City on this occasion, make sure you do not lower your guard against them. I hope all of you can work together so that we can all collectively reap as much benefits from this trip as possible," E Kuai continued.

Everyone gave a collective affirmative response, and around two hours later, the main city gate slowly swung open, following which a procession of around a dozen giant scaled beasts emerged from the city.

The scaled beast at the forefront of the line resembled a giant crocodile that was over a thousand feet tall with a black stone palace on its back. The palace was riddled with ornate engravings and star bones, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

Behind the crocodile-like beast were around a dozen massive Black Scaled Elephants, all of which also had black stone palaces on their backs. However, these palaces were much more simplistic in design, and they couldn't even compare with the opulence of E Kuai's palace.

One of the stone palaces was occupied by Chen Yang and Daoist Xie, while Han Li, Gu Qianxun, and Xuanyuan Xing shared another one.

The stone palace was quite large, and even with each of them taking a room, there were still rooms to spare.

After the procession of scaled beasts emerged from the city, Han Li didn't immediately enter the stone palace to rest. Instead, he stood on the Black Scaled Elephant's back and cast his gaze into the distance. However, he wasn't able to look very far with the enormous Myriad Profound Mountain Range in the way.

Around fifteen minutes later, the line of scaled beasts passed over a col in a valley, and everyone's horizons were instantly broadened from there.

As Han Li looked down from above, he noticed around a dozen Black Scaled Elephants resting on a hill elsewhere in the mountain range.

All of them were clad in armor with star bones embedded into their chests, and not only had their tusks been replaced with sharp spears, they appeared to be completely dead and devoid of vitality.

These are all puppets!

Right at this moment, a figure suddenly flew through the air above, then drew to a halt in mid-air in front of everyone.

Han Li looked up to discover a handsome young man in a suit of black armor with a pair of short bone halberds strapped to his back, and he was currently hovering over a thousand feet up in the air.

With spiritual and devilish qi completely inaccessible in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, taking flight was physically impossible for most, so the fact that this man was able to hover in mid-air immediately drew a great deal of attention.

Many of the Profound City cultivators emerged from their stone palaces, but none of them city lords had emerged.

Zhu Ziqing was standing beside her brother, looking up at the young man with an infatuated expression as she murmured, "He's so handsome..."

"Nonsense! He's an enemy of our Profound City!" Zhu Ziyuan scolded as he gave her a firm tap on the head.

"Alright, I get it," Zhu Ziqing replied as a serious look appeared on her face.

Han Li was looking up at the handsome young man with everyone else, and for some reason, the young man struck him as a little odd.

He directed his gaze upward, all the way to the clouds in the sky, and only then did he notice that the clouds hanging directly above the young man were slightly darker than the ones around them.

"Fellow daoists of Profound City, Mistress Sha Xin has sent me here with a proposal. In order to avoid unnecessary misunderstandings and conflicts, Mistress Sha Xin suggests that our two groups travel with some distance between us," the young man declared.

He had a gender-neutral voice that was very pleasant and alluring.

The Profound City cultivators were silent for a moment, following which Zhu Ziyuan seemed to have suddenly received an instruction, and he replied, "Master E Kuai has agreed to this proposal."

The young man's gaze fell upon Zhu Ziyuan, and he cupped his fist in a parting salute before turning to depart.

As he did so, Han Li noticed a black shadow moving with him deep within the clouds up above. As he descended toward the Puppet City camp, it was finally revealed that there was a giant scaled bird hanging above its head.

Just like the Black Scaled Elephants, this bird was clearly also long dead. It seemed to be a puppet that was under the young man's control, and he was only able to take flight by attaching himself to the bird puppet with barely visible threads.

Shortly thereafter, the sound of a blowing horn rang out from the Puppet City camp, and the scaled beast puppets on the hill stood up one after another before setting off.

Once the Puppet City camp was several thousand feet away, the Profound City camp began to move as well.

The landscape was completely barren and derelict, and Han Li quickly grew bored of the monotonous scenery, so he returned to his room to cultivate.

……

That night.

Han Li awakened from his meditation, then emerged from the stone palace.

He sprang up into the air from the Black Scaled Elephant's back to land on another Black Scaled Elephant, then made his way over to the stone palace on the latter's back.

Before he had a chance to announce his arrival, Chen Yang's voice rang out from within the palace.

"I've been waiting for you, Fellow Daoist Li."

Han Li made his way directly into the stone palace upon hearing this.

Upon entering the palace, Han Li was greeted by the sight of Daoist Xie standing by the entrance, and the latter led him to a room in the palace, making no attempt to communicate with him in the process.

Han Li was already accustomed to this, and upon entering the room, he was invited to take a seat by Chen Yang.

"Fellow Daoist Chen..." Han Li began, only for Chen Yang to raise a hand to cut him off.

"I'm afraid Fellow Daoist Shi Kong is no longer the same person that you once knew," Chen Yang sighed.

"What happened to him?" Han Li asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"Du Qingyang was very secretive about sending Fellow Daoist Shi Kong to Profound City, so I have no clue exactly what happened to him. This is the first time I've seen Fellow Daoist Shi Kong in Profound City, and to me, he feels like... a puppet," Chen Yang replied in a hesitant manner.

Han Li's brows became even more tightly furrowed upon hearing this.

"However, he also feels somewhat different from a puppet, but I can't put my finger on what the difference is. In any case, approaching him at a time like this is not a wise move," Chen Yang added.

On the surface, Han Li appeared to be quite composed, but internally, he was feeling very perplexed.

Before they entered the Scalptia Spatial Domain, Shi Pokong had given each of them a jade pendant that could allow them to leave the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

Despite all of the perils that he had encountered, Han Li had refrained from using his jade pendant thus far as he wasn't willing to leave without finding Violet Spirit first, but what was happening in Shi Chuankong's case?

If he were in such a dire situation that he was about to be made into a puppet, then why hadn't he used the jade pendant? Han Li was unconvinced that someone of Shi Chuankong's powers would've been rendered unable to use the jade pendant all this time.`

After some contemplation, Han Li said, "I'll have to count on you to continue keeping an eye out for more information on Fellow Daoist Shi."

"Rest assured, I'll be sure to keep an eye out and update you on any information that comes my way," Chen Yang promised.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

"No need to thank me. There's going to be a long journey ahead, and no one knows what'll await us in the Great Ruins, so make sure to rest up on the way there, Brother Li," Chen Yang said.

The two of them chatted for a while longer before Han Li departed, and upon returning to his room, he spent some time to contemplate the information that he had just received before closing his eyes to cultivate the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

……

Over a month flew by in a flash.

On this day, the two processions of scaled beasts were passing through a narrow valley with roughly ten thousand feet of distance between them.

The group at the front was still yet to exit the valley, while the rear group had only just entered the valley, when an enormous two-headed scaled falcon swooped down from the heavens with a thunderous roar.

With its wings spread open, it cast an enormous black shadow that encompassed virtually the entire valley, and as it flapped its wings, two bursts of ferocious air currents came crashing down violently upon the mountain faces on either side of the valley.

The mountain faces collapsed violently, sending a huge cloud of dust rising up into the air.

All of the Profound City scaled beasts immediately began backing out of the valley in alarm, while the scaled beast puppets up ahead continued onward without pause.

Han Li was cultivating in his room when he felt the disturbance outside, and he flew out just in time to see an avalanche of giant rocks tumbling down up ahead, quickly blocking up the entire valley.

At the same time, the view up ahead was completely obscured by the dense cloud of dust that had risen up into the air.

All of the Profound City cultivators hurriedly rushed out to see what was happening when all of a sudden, a burst of formidable starpower erupted forth within the valley up ahead, forming a wave of radiant white light that swept up into the air.

A resounding boom rang out as rocks, sand, and soil were flung up into the air like a volcanic eruption before raining down in all directions, and a burst of powerful shockwaves also surged out of the valley, clearing the blockage.

Chapter 919: Venturing Into Peril

As the dust settled, Han Li spotted a Black Scaled Elephant puppet with its head raised up at the heavens.

It had been buried under the rocks that had tumbled down from the collapsed mountain faces, but it had managed to blast its way out by brute force.

Han Li couldn't help but be impressed by how powerful the puppefied Black Scaled Elephant was.

It seemed that while the cultivators of Puppet City couldn't couldn't compare with their Profound City counterparts when it came to bodily refinement, they were extremely adept in the art of puppetry, and that was what had allowed them to establish themselves in the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

All of the Profound City cultivators displayed reactions upon seeing this.

The city lords remained calm and composed, while everyone else was either stunned by what they had seen, or were proclaiming that the Puppet City cultivators had done this on purpose.

All of a sudden, the roof of a stone palace on the back of another Black Scaled Elephant puppet up ahead suddenly opened up, and a spear around the same thickness as an adult human's arm shot out with an explosive boom.

At this point, the two-headed scaled falcon had already flown far into the distance, but the spear was able to catch up to it in a flash before piercing into its abdomen.

The two-headed falcon screeched in pain, but it was able to remain aloft as it continued flying away into the distance.

However, it had only flown for just over ten thousand feet when it abruptly exploded amid an eruption of white light.

Clearly, the spear that had pierced into its body had been fitted with Explosive Scaled Beast star bones.

After this brief interlude, the Puppet City camp continued onward, as did the Profound City camp.

……

Half a year later.

Gusts of fierce wind were howling over a rocky black desert, and even though it was noon, the swirling sand in the sky made it feel as if it were just as dark as nighttime.

The ground was rumbling incessantly as countless large rocks were rolling around everywhere in the face of the fierce winds, and at this moment, the two groups of scaled beasts were huddled together in a pair of circles around a thousand feet apart with their heads facing inward to withstand the elements.

All of a sudden, the roof of a stone palace on the back of one of the scaled beasts was abruptly torn off by the wind, then swept away like a kite.

Immediately thereafter, a tall and imposing figure launched himself up into the sky out of the stone palace and into the ferocious sandstorm outside.

Profound acupoints were glowing on his legs, allowing him to tread on air and rush after the stone roof.

No more than twenty seconds later, the figure returned with the black stone roof held above his head with both hands, and he returned the roof back to its original place on the stone palace.

The figure was none other than Han Li, and after restoring the roof, he swept his gaze around the room with a wry smile on his face. Even though the roof had only been missing for less than twenty seconds, a thick layer of sand had already accumulated underfoot, and the stone table at the center of the room had also been smashed into pieces by a flying rock.

This black sandstorm has already been raging for over two months, when is it going to end?

Han Li heaved a resigned sigh as he swept away the sand on his stone bed with his sleeve before sitting down on it.

Initially, in the face of scaled beast attacks, the two parties from the two cities had been trying to compete against each other, with neither side willing to be outdone by the other, but as the journey wore on, the conditions had become more and more inhospitable, to the point that the two parties had no choice but to set their differences aside and work together.

……

Several more years passed.

The sound of a blowing horn rang out on a vast plain, and the Puppet City party that was leading the way suddenly stopped in its tracks.

The Profound City camp was trailing over a thousand feet behind them, and they also drew to a halt.

Inside a stone palace on the back of one of the Black Scaled Elephants, Han Li, Gu Qianxun, and Xuanyuan Xing were seated around a stone table.

"We've stopped again," Gu Qianxun remarked as her brows furrowed slightly.

"It must be another attack. The deeper we venture into the Scalptia Spatial Domain, the greater the spatial pressure, and the more powerful the scaled beasts that we encounter, so progress has been getting slower and slower," Xuanyuan Xing sighed.

"I thought that I would be able to cultivate in seclusion over this entire journey, but we keep being interrupted by scaled beast attacks. The only silver lining is that we get to keep the beast cores of the scaled beasts that we slay," Han Li said with a wry smile.

"Let's see what we're dealing with this time," Gu Qianxun sighed as she rose to her feet.

The three of them made their way out of the stone palace together, only to discover that the situation outside was not quite like what they had anticipated.

It was very calm and peaceful outside, with no danger in sight.

Han Li jumped onto the roof of the stone palace before peering into the distance, and he could see clear distortion in the space dozens of kilometers away.

Countless chaotic spatial rifts were wreaking havoc there like a storm, slicing the space there apart.

Directly below the densely packed array of spatial rifts was a bottomless abyss that stretched as far as the eyes could see in both directions, and wisps of black mist were rising up out of the abyss.

Giant black vortexes were visible at set intervals, stirring up the black mist to make it resemble demonic eyes that were looking into the abyss.

"What's that?" Gu Qianxun murmured as she arrived beside Han Li.

"I don't know, but I can sense that the spatial power in that area is extremely violent. Even from so far away, I can feel a faint tearing force in the air. I hope that's not where the Great Ruins are," Han Li replied.

Right at this moment, Chen Yang flew over to them with Daoist Xie, and the three of them cupped their fists in a respectful salute at his arrival.

"No need for formalities," Chen Yang said with a smile as he waved a dismissive hand. "I've come here to let you know that the Great Ruins are on the other side of that abyss up ahead."

Xuanyuan Xing and Gu Qianxun both turned to look at Han Li upon seeing this. It seemed that he had spoken their worst fear into existence.

"Do we have a way to cross the abyss?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not sure, but City Lord E Kuai has already gone to meet with Sha Xin, and I'm assuming they'll come up with a plan together," Chen Yang replied.

"I wonder if it's even possible to cross such a perilous abyss," Xuanyuan Xing said in a concerned manner.

"I heard from City Lord E that this black abyssal storm is already at its weakest point in the past one million years. Even as recently as a century ago, the area encompassed by the spatial rifts was several hundred kilometers wide, so we wouldn't have even been able to stand this close," Chen Yang sighed.

"In that case, why don't we wait a bit longer? Perhaps after another century, the storm won't pose any obstacle at all," Gu Qianxun said.

"Profound City and Puppet City have both already been monitoring this place for countless years, and both are afraid that the other will enter the Great Ruins before them. The main objective of this edition of the Five City Martial Gathering was to select people to enter the Great Ruins, but with Puppet City coming to us to propose a collaboration, City Lord E had no choice but to commence his plan a little earlier than expected," Chen Yang explained.

"It seems like Puppet City must've only proposed a collaboration out of necessity. I doubt that any one of the two cities would possess the power required to traverse this abyss on its own," Gu Qianxun mused.

"I don't think that's the entire reason. I think Puppet City was most likely also concerned that if they were to try and venture into the Great Ruins on their own, Profound City would take the opportunity to attack while all of their most powerful cultivators were away," Han Li said.

"That sounds like a very shrewd assessment, Fellow Daoist Li," Chen Yang said with a smile.

Right at this moment, a figure suddenly rose up from the Puppet City camp, ascending to an altitude of over a thousand feet before descending toward Profound City camp, where he was revealed to be none other than E Kuai.

As he descended, he pressed a palm down onto the air below, and the speed of his descent was instantly slowed, allowing him to land on the head of the giant crocodile-like scaled beast as lightly as a feather.

"Everyone, travel in the northeastern direction along the abyss. Make sure to look out for spatial rifts along the way," E Kuai ordered in a voice that wasn't very loud, but rang out clearly within everyone's hearts.

"Looks like we're setting off," Chen Yang remarked before departing with Daoist Xie, and the two camps continued onward.

As everyone traveled along the abyss, they discovered that its width wasn't uniform. Instead, some areas were clearly wider than others, and the spatial rifts above those areas also covered larger areas.

Occasionally, some scaled beasts would be spotted, stumbling into the range of the spatial rifts, upon which they would immediately be swept up and torn into pieces, dying extremely horrific deaths.

There were also some flying scaled beasts that were under the impression that they would be safe as long as they flew over the abyss, only to be sucked down into the masses of spatial rifts below by the tremendous suction force released by the giant vortexes within the abyss.

Han Li had personally witnessed a four-winged scaled eagle soaring out of the clouds at an altitude in excess of ten thousand feet in an attempt to fly over the abyss, only to plummet out of the sky like a dead weight before crashing down into one of the black vortexes.

Chapter 920: Collaboration

Over half a year flew by in a flash.

On this day, the rays of the setting sun were spilling down onto the ground, basking the entire plain in a dim, yellow glow.

The two groups of scaled beasts were still trundling along with some distance between them, traveling toward a giant mountain range in the distance over the gradually rising terrain.

Han Li was seated on the rooftop of a black palace on one of the scaled beasts, looking into the distance.

Half of the mountain range on the horizon was basked in the light of the setting sun, giving it a rosy, golden glow, while the other half was completely dim and had a strange, blue coloration.

After observing the mountain range for a while, Han Li's brows began to furrow slightly. He could sense some strange energy fluctuations from the mountain range, and as they drew closer and closer, the energy fluctuations became more and more pronounced, while a glacial aura also began to sweep over the area.

More and more people were beginning to detect these abnormalities, and they emerged from their stone palaces to investigate.

It didn't seem like they were very far away from the mountain range, but only on the eighth morning of travel did they finally arrive at the foot of the mountain range.

This time, the Puppet City camp stopped at the foot of the mountain range to wait for the Profound City camp to catch up.

Han Li and Gu Qianxun were standing beside each other on the back of their Black Scaled Elephant, looking at the mountain range from afar. They could see that the black abyss had extended all the way here, and it seemed to have passed through the entire mountain range.

One half of the mountain range was a crystalline blue, while the other half was bright red, and each half was giving off a different peculiar aura.

"This is a very strange place. I don't know about you two, but even with my physical constitution, it feels really cold here," Gu Qianxun said as she rubbed her own arms for warmth.

"This half of the mountain range is as cold as ice, releasing a glacial aura, while the other half is as scorching as fire. It's indeed quite a miraculous sight to behold," Xuanyuan Xing remarked.

Han Li remained silent with his brows tightly furrowed.

Right at this moment, the sound of a blowing horn and a gong being struck rang out in unison, and the three of them exchanged a glance with each other before descending from their Black Scaled Elephant.

Before long, everyone else had also arrived, while the cultivators of Puppet City also gathered around twenty meters away.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the Puppet City camp to discover that they were led by the handsome young man controlling the scaled bird puppet.

To his left was a giant of a man who was over twenty feet tall. Half of his head was bald, and there was a braid on the top of his head that pointed directly up at the heavens, giving him a rather comical appearance. However, what was far less comical were the thick bands of muscle all over his body and the thick veins that were bulging beneath his skin.

On the handsome young man's right stood a diminutive man who was less than four feet tall. He was just as handsome as the young man, and he was clad in a suit of white bone armor. Despite his tiny stature, there was an air of confidence and authority about him.

The dozen or so people behind those three were mostly women with alluring bodies, and all of them were dressed in the same attire, consisting of thin black robes with light veils over their faces.

Han Li's gaze swept over them before settling on the three people at the very back of the Puppet City camp.

Those three were also wearing the same black robes, but they somehow felt very different from their companions.

Right as Han Li was about to take a closer look, two figures descended out of the sky before landing in front of the two camps.

One of them was none other than E Kuai, and he was accompanied by a breathtakingly elegant woman who radiated seduction from every single pore of her body.

Even Gu Qianxun couldn't help but be momentarily entranced by her.

She's not using any seductive or illusory abilities, but there's a natural air of innate allure about her... Han Li thought to himself, and the image of Violet Spirit sprang into his mind.

However, this woman wasn't Violet Spirit. Instead, it was the lord of Puppet City, Sha Xin.

"Everyone, the Great Ruins that we've been searching so arduously for are on the other side of the black abyss, and the path to cross the abyss is in this mountain range of fire and ice. I'm aware that there have been many past conflicts between our two cities, and many of you have had loved ones perish at the hands of cultivators from the other city," Sha Xin declared.

The cultivators from the two cities exchanged a glance with one another upon hearing this, and there was clear resentment and animosity in their eyes.

"The resentment between our two cities is not something that can be stifled, and there's no need to stifle it," Sha Xin continued, and both camps erupted into a frenzy upon hearing this, with many of them reaching for their weapons with fierce killing intent in their eyes.

"Hold on a second, everyone," E Kuai said with a warm smile, and everyone stopped what they were doing, but the wariness in their eyes hadn't waned in the slightest.

"Regardless of how much all of you resent one another, I hope that you can set your differences aside while we pass through this mountain range," Sha Xin continued.

"The Bipolar Extreme Mountain Range is far more perilous than all of you can imagine, so we must all band together and proceed with caution. As City Lord Sha Xin just said, we must set aside our personal differences for now and work together," E Kuai said.

Following a brief silence, everyone reluctantly accepted this arrangement.

"We're going to enter the Bipolar Extreme Mountain Range from here. In order to avoid any mishaps, all of us will enter the mountain range in an alternating fashion," Sha Xin said.

Everyone gave a collective affirmative response before returning to their scaled beasts in preparation to continue onward.

By the time Han Li turned back to look at the three figures at the back of the Puppet City camp, they were already nowhere to be seen.

E Kuai and Sha Xin's scaled beasts entered the mountain range at the forefront, immediately followed by a scaled beast puppet from Puppet City, then a scaled beast from Profound City.

All of the scaled beasts and puppets entered the mountain range one after another in this alternating pattern, and upon venturing into the valley up ahead, everyone was immediately greeted by the sound of wailing winds that resembled a woman's sobs.

Even though there was no ice or snow to be seen, the entire valley was filled with a very uncomfortable glacial aura.

Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed as he inspected the landscape up ahead momentarily, then returned to his room to continue cultivating.

As the scaled beasts ventured deeper and deeper into the mountain range, the surrounding crystalline blue rocks became darker and darker in color, and the glacial aura in the air also became more and more pronounced.

Initially, Han Li was able to focus on his cultivation without being disrupted, but over the past few days, even he was occasionally being roused from his meditative state by the pervasive chill in the air, thereby rendering him unable to continue cultivating.

One night, as he was once again awoken from his meditation, he stood up and made his way out of the stone palace.

It was very late at night, and the rocks in the valley were reflecting the cold light of the moon and the stars up above. As a result, the path ahead was brightly illuminated, but it was only becoming colder and colder.

As Han Li was looking up at the moon, Gu Qianxun also made her way out of the stone palace.

He turned to her to discover that she had changed into a set of new clothes, and there was also a thick beast hide coat draped over her shoulders. The coat was slightly too large for her, giving her an adorable, childlike appearance.

Gu Qianxun was rather perplexed by Han Li's gaze, and she asked, "What are you looking at, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"Where did you get that coat from?" Han Li asked in a slightly awkward manner.

"We were recently attacked by a pack of demon beasts with coats of fur as opposed to scales. I slew a few of them, and I skinned one to make this coat. This only happened two days ago, how do you not know about this?" Gu Qianxun asked.

"I heard the commotion, but I was at an important point in my cultivation at the time, so I didn't come out to investigate," Han Li explained.

At the time, he was on the verge of opening a profound acupoint, so he chose to remain in his room even though he could hear the attack taking place.

"I see. Your mental fortitude is truly remarkable, Fellow Daoist Li. Under these freezing temperatures, several of our fellow daoists are already experiencing cracking in their skin, so they don't dare to sit still for any length of time, yet you're still able to cultivate. That's truly impressive," Gu Qianxun praised.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Gu. By the way, how powerful were the demon beasts that attacked us two days ago?" Han Li asked.

"Very powerful, far more so than the ones that we've encountered along the journey up to this point. Even the weakest ones among them were still C tier demon beasts, and they have massive numbers as well. One of the cultivators of our Profound City was dragged down the back of his Black Scaled Elephant in a moment of complacency, and he was quickly dismembered and devoured," Gu Qianxun replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"That's why all of us have been particularly vigilant in case those demon beasts attack again," Gu Qianxun continued.

Han Li cast his gaze into the distance to find that a steep slope had appeared up ahead, leading up to a tall mountain ridge.

"It looks like the terrain up ahead is also becoming more unforgiving," Han Li sighed.

"No matter how difficult the terrain is to traverse, we have to keep going. We've come way too far to turn back now, no one would be willing to turn around so close to the Great Ruins," Gu Qianxun said.

"Hopefully, it's not actually just a set of ruins with nothing in it," Han Li chuckled.

"Don't say that!" Gu Qianxun exclaimed with a displeased pout before returning to the stone palace.

Following her departure, Han Li's smile faded as he cast his gaze into the distance with a contemplative look on his face.

Chapter 921: Traitor

As the line of scaled beasts continued onward, they gradually ascended higher and higher in altitude, and only on the next morning did they finally reach the halfway point up the mountain.

From there, the path ahead became narrower and even more arduous to traverse, to the point the scaled beast and the puppet at the forefront of the line had to eventually begin clearing out a path as they went, so progress was naturally very slow.

Almost all of the Profound City cultivators had come out to stand on the backs of their scaled beasts with grim looks on their faces.

All of a sudden, a burst of thunderous rumbling began ringing out from the valley beneath the mountain face, and everyone hurriedly looked down to discover a plume of white mist rising up rapidly from within the valley.

Concealed beneath the white mist were clusters of formidable blades of wind that gave off a bone-chilling glacial aura.

"Look out, here it comes again!" someone yelled, and profound acupoints lit up over everyone's bodies as they sprang into action.

Duan Tong was standing on the back of a Black Scaled Elephant, and he raised his enormous, bandaged right arm, then clenched his fist tightly and took a half-step backward before slamming his fist down onto an oncoming plume of mist.

It seemed that the tip of his fist was enshrouded within a vortex of starlight, and the space in front of him shuddered as a burst of tremendous force came crashing down.

The burst of force clashed against the plume of white mist, and both dissipated in unison upon contact.

On the back of another Black Scaled Elephant, Fang Chan was holding a roasted demon beast leg in his left hand, and he was gleefully tearing off chunks of flesh from the leg with his teeth.

The leg was already completely cold, with a revolting layer of frozen fat on its surface, yet Fang Chan didn't seem to mind at all.

He caught sight of a plume of white mist hurtling toward him out of his peripheral vision, and his brows furrowed slightly with displeasure, seemingly discontent at the fact that his meal had been interrupted.

All of a sudden, a cold gleam flashed through his eyes, and he set down the beast leg in his hand before turning to the white mist and letting loose a piercing screech.

A burst of incredibly powerful soundwaves erupted through the air before crashing into the plume of white mist, scattering the latter in all directions.

Han Li was observing this from afar when an alarmed look suddenly appeared in his eyes, and he yelled, "Look out!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a black shadow shot out of the scattered plume of mist, immediately following which the head of a giant scaled python emerged, opening its cavernous mouth to bite down upon Fang Chan.

The scaled python had been concealed within the mist in the valley, but just its head alone was comparable in size to a Black Scaled Elephant, and it seemed to be capable of swallowing an entire Black Scaled Elephant whole in a single bite.

Despite his dull appearance, Fang Chan wasn't slow to react at all, having already sprung high up into the air as soon as he heard Han Li's warning. At the same time, he opened his mouth up wide and let loose another high-pitched screech toward the scaled python.

Halos of white starlight erupted out of his mouth, forming shockwaves that were visible even to the naked eye, and as soon as these shockwaves made contact with the scaled python's head, it immediately exploded, sending vast volumes of blood and countless scales erupting in all directions.

The remnants of its head crashed down onto the Black Scaled Elephant below, completely pulverizing the stone palace on its back, and the two other White Rock City cultivators hurriedly jumped up onto the nearby mountain face.

The mountain face beneath the Black Scaled Elephant crumbled under the combined weight of the elephant and the scaled python's head, and as a result, its two front feet were left suspended in mid-air.

The Black Scaled Elephant hurriedly stumbled back in a panic, crashing into the scaled beast puppet behind it.

As a result, the scaled beast puppet was knocked off balance, and it slid off the mountain face and began tumbling down into the valley below, while the blue rocks beneath it also began to crumble.

There were two women in light black dresses on the puppet's back, and they began swinging their arms through the air, while the white bone rings on their arms flashed with starlight.

The circle of star bones embedded into the giant scaled beast puppet's chest also began flashing brightly as it attempted to climb back up onto the mountain face with all its might, but the rocks beneath its feet were crumbling too quickly, and despite its best efforts, its fall appeared to be inevitable.

With the scaled beast puppet on the verge of being buried under the falling rocks, the two women finally decided to abandon it, springing up into the air toward the mountain face above.

However, right at this moment, the scaled python that had just been struck down by Fang Chan was somehow able to suddenly raise its head again, and it opened its cavernous mouth to release a burst of bone-chilling blue light.

The air in the wake of the blue light was completely frozen solid, and it was sweeping rapidly toward the two women.

The two of them had only just landed on the mountain face when the wave of glacial light descended upon them, and they hurriedly thrust their palms upward in retaliation.

Han Li could see that many profound acupoints had lit up over their arms, and it was clear that they were also accomplished bodily refinement cultivators.

However, their strength couldn't compare with that of the likes of Duan Tong and Fang Chan, so they were only able to scatter some of the glacial blue light before the rest descended upon them, completely freezing them solid.

As a result, the two of them were instantly immobilized, and they began falling involuntarily back down toward the valley below.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and all of a sudden, he abruptly vanished from the spot.

A string of loud thumps rang out as Han Li trod down onto the space beneath his feet to pursue the two women.

The profound acupoints on his legs were glowing radiantly, elevating his speed to the maximum, and he was able to grab the two women by their arms before darting back onto the mountain face.

At this point, the handsome young man from Puppet City had also arrived on the scene, and he was clearly taken aback to see Han Li swooping in to save the two women.

With the women already saved, he grabbed onto one of the short halberds strapped to his back, then twisted around before hurling the halberd through the air with all his might.

The bone halberd shot forth through the air as a streak of radiant silver light, giving off a burst of formidable starpower fluctuations.

The streak of silver light pierced straight into the scaled python's head before emerging on the other side, following which the handsome young man raised a hand, and a translucent white thread that was connected to the halberd swept through the air to slice the python's head open.

With a casual tugging motion, the halberd flew back into the young man's grasp, and hanging from the crescent-shaped blade attached to the main blade was a fist-sized beast core that was completely unharmed.

The body of the giant python tumbled down into the valley below, while the young man took the two women from Han Li as he said with a smile, "Thank you, Fellow Daoist. My name is Zhuo Ge, may I know yours?"

"Li Feiyu," Han Li replied.

"Please accept this B tier beast core as a gesture of my gratitude," Zhuo Ge said as he casually tossed the scaled python beast core at Han Li, who caught the beast core and cupped his fist to extend a salute before flying back toward Gu Qianxun.

"What an interesting guy," Zhuo Ge mused to himself before departing with the two women.

Upon Han Li's return, Gu Qianxun turned to him with tightly furrowed brows as she complained, "That was way too reckless of you, Fellow Daoist Li!"

"How so?" Han Li asked.

"Puppet City is our sworn enemy, so even if we're working together for now, you shouldn't have gone out of your way to save their cultivators. Everyone is going to see you as a traitor now!" Gu Qianxun explained through voice transmission.

Han Li took a glance at the nearby Profound City cultivators upon hearing this, and sure enough, they were all looking at him with hostile expressions, with the exception of Fang Chan, who was smiling at him, seemingly in gratitude for the verbal warning he had issued earlier.

Han Li turned his gaze back to Gu Qianxun as he replied through voice transmission, "Given how dangerous and unpredictable this place is, if we do not work together wholeheartedly, then we may not even make it out of this mountain range alive."

In reality, the true reason why he had decided to save those two women was for Violet Spirit's sake. He hadn't been able to find any information about her in Profound City, and thinking back to the puppet remnants in that cave, he felt like there was a very good chance that she had fallen into the hands of Puppet City.

He had been intending to dig up some information from the Puppet City cultivators, but the cultivators from the two cities were still quite apprehensive of one another, so he never had the chance to speak to any of them.

Hence, he had immediately pounced on that opportunity to appease Puppet City, and he didn't care if that was at the expense of offending those from Profound City.

After that close call, the cultivators from the two cities became even more cautious, constantly surveying the surrounding area for potential hazards, but even so, they were still attacked by several packs of powerful demon beasts, and the going had become very tough.

Thankfully, their efforts ultimately paid off, and after reaching the top of the mountain ridge, they had a much easier downhill journey to a giant canyon deep within the mountain range.

The entrance of the canyon was established as a boundary, with the cultivators of the two cities setting up camp on either side of it.

Inside the valley, one half of the rock face was blue, while the other was red, and they were giving off completely contrasting freezing and scorching auras. Through the valley, it could be seen that the black abyss cut through the entire valley, slicing it into two like a black river.

The area around the black abyss was completely filled with spatial rifts that were clumped together like a ferocious storm.

Chapter 922: Constructing a Star Boat

That night, Han Li and Gu Qianxun emerged from their campsite before making their way to the entrance of the canyon together.

"Have City Lord E and Mistress Liu Hua gone to meet with City Lord Sha Xin?" Han Li suddenly asked.

"That's right, they left together not long after we set up camp," Gu Qianxun replied.

"It looks like this is where they're planning to make a move," Han Li mused.

"The environment here is quite special, and the spatial storm is far weaker here than elsewhere," Gu Qianxun replied with a nod.

As soon as her voice trailed off, a burst of thunderous rumbling suddenly rang out from within the valley.

The two of them cast their eyes into the canyon in unison upon seeing this, and they were greeted by the sight of bursts of crimson flames rising up from the ground alongside gusts of howling blue winds.

The two clashed to create a reaction similar to that of pouring water into bubbling oil, generating gusts of fierce white winds that swept through the air in all directions.

The gusts of white wind were forced upward by the rock faces on either side of the narrow canyon, scattering much of the spatial storm above the canyon.

"With the spatial storm weakened by these winds, there's a chance that we could pass over the canyon, but it's still only a very slim one. In any case, with our physical constitutions, forcing our way through will most likely only lead to death," Han Li said with tightly furrowed brows.

"There's no need to be too concerned. I'm sure City Lord E must've made some preparations prior to bringing us here, so he won't just send us to our deaths. After his meeting with City Lord Sha Xin, we should have a relatively safe way to cross the abyss," Gu Qianxun said with a smile.

"In that case, I'll mind my own business," Han Li replied with a smile of his own.

He cast his gaze through the scattered spatial storm, and he spotted a glowing white landmass on the other side of the black abyss.

Are those the Great Ruins?

The night quickly passed by, and the next morning, Han Li and the others had only just emerged from their tents when they were summoned to a clearing.

"I'm sure all of you have already witnessed the perils presented by the black abyss. It would be far too difficult to try and cross it with our powers alone, and that's why our two cities have decided to work together. Collaboration between our two cities is vital to crossing the abyss, so restrain yourselves and do not get into any conflicts with the Puppet City cultivators until we enter the Great Ruins," E Kuai declared in an authoritative voice.

Everyone was still rather unwilling to work with the Puppet City cultivators, but no one raised any objections.

"May I ask how we're going to be crossing the black abyss, City Lord E?" Sun Tu asked.

Everyone else also turned to E Kuai to hear his answer. Even though much of the spatial storm above the abyss had been scattered, it was still extremely dangerous.

"Rest assured, I've already decided on a course of action with Fellow Daoist Daoist Liu Hua and City Lord Sha Xin," E Kuai replied with a faint smile.

Mistress Liu Hua took that as his cue to step forward, and he said, "As I'm sure all of you have already witnessed, the main sources of danger in the black abyss is the tremendous suction force that it's releasing, and the spatial storm above it.

“Thankfully, the special environment here has significantly weakened the spatial storm, and after some discussion with City Lord E and City Lord Sha Xin, we've designed a Star Falcon Flying Boat that incorporates my expertise in starpower restrictions and Puppet City's puppetry acumen, and that should be enough to get us across the black abyss."

"The body of the Star Falcon Flying Boat will be crafted by the Puppet City cultivators, while we'll be responsible for engraving the restrictions on it. From here onward, all of you are to follow Fellow Daoist Liu Hua's instructions," E Kuai ordered, and all of the Profound City cultivators gave a collective affirmative response.

After that, E Kuai discussed something briefly with Mistress Liu Hua, then gathered the other four city lords together for a separate meeting.

Meanwhile, the Puppet City cultivators had begun their work, clearing out a large area that was going to serve as their workspace for the construction of the flying boat.

At the same time, Mistress Liu Hua began delegating tasks to everyone.

He picked out three or four of the Profound City cultivators as he declared, "A special type of star fluid is required for the inscription of the restrictions. You will be responsible for mixing this star fluid, here are the ingredients and instructions."

Mistress Liu Hua then picked out a few more cultivators before issuing another instruction.

Before long, all but four of the Profound City cultivators had been assigned different tasks, and out of the four that remained, two of them were Han Li and Xuanyuan Xing. They were joined by a tall and thin yellow-haired young man from White Rock City, and a short and stocky man from Profound City.

Han Li wasn't familiar with those two, all he knew were their names from the Five City Martial Gathering. The one from White Rock City was called Lü Gang, while the name of the Profound City cultivator was Liang Fa.

"What should we do, Senior Liu Hua?" Han Li asked.

"I can tell that all of you possess tremendous spiritual sense. Your task will be the most important one of all, and that's to help me engrave the restrictions onto the flying boat," Mistress Liu Hua declared, and Han Li was quite elated to hear this.

He was very curious about this Star Falcon Flying Boat, and with such an important task assigned to him, he would be able to glean much of the intricacies involved in the crafting process.

"With all due respect, Senior Liu Hua, I don't even know the first thing about tool refinement. Restriction inscription is an extremely important task, one that I have no confidence of carrying out successfully. If something goes wrong in this process, the consequences could be catastrophic.

“I know of several of our fellow daoists who are adept in the art of tool refinement, so why don't I get them to help you instead?" Xuanyuan Xing suggested with a hesitant look on his face.

"Only those who possess immense spiritual sense can engrave my restrictions! Do you think this is a task that anybody could carry out? Aside from the four of you, only the four city lords meet the spiritual sense requirements, so if you don't want to do this, then get Chen Yang from your Green Goat City to replace you," Mistress Liu Hua harrumphed in a displeased manner.

"I have no intention of shirking my duties, Senior Liu Hua, I'm just worried that my incompetence will lead to detrimental outcomes," Xuanyuan Xing hurriedly said with a fearful expression.

Mistress Liu Hua was quite pleased by Xuanyuan Xing's panicked reaction, and the discontent on his face eased a little as he said, "Rest assured, I won't make you inscribe any of the most complex patterns, you'll only be responsible for some of the simpler work in the corners. With your spiritual sense and my guidance, all of you will be up to the task."

Xuanyuan Xing raised no further objections upon hearing this.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Mistress Liu Hua continued, "Having said that, your concerns are not completely unfounded. The process of creating restrictions in the Scalptia Spatial Domain is very different from the same process in the outside world, so you do need to master some technique in order to complete this task. Come over here and do some practice."

With that, he handed out a bone pen that was around the same thickness as a human finger and roughly half a foot in length to each of the four cultivators present.

The bone pen was very similar to the pens used for rune inscriptions, with a sharp tip that seemed to have been fashioned out of some type of scaled beast tooth, and a hair thin hole could be seen at the center of the tip.

On the other end of the pen was a transparent sac-like object, which was filled with some type of silver liquid that was giving off faint starpower fluctuations.

"These pens are called Star Wave Pens, and the liquid inside the star fluid that I just mentioned. Immortal spiritual power is inaccessible in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so while engraving the restrictions, you'll need to inject your spiritual sense into the star fluid. These jade slips contain some simple star runes, you can try engraving them on these jade slabs first," Mistress Liu Hua said as he pulled out four jade slips and some white jade slabs for everyone.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly as he injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip, and sure enough, there were some star runes inside, but all of them appeared to be quite complex and were very different from any of the runes that he had ever seen before.

"My star runes are going to be more difficult to engrave than the runes you'll find in the outside world, so listen carefully to my instructions," Mistress Liu Hua said, then began instructing Han Li and the others through voice transmission.

Only after more than two hours had passed did the lesson conclude, and despite the strange and unfamiliar nature of these star runes, Han Li was able to master the concepts quite quickly thanks to his stellar tool refinement foundation.

In contrast, the other three didn't have any tool refinement experience, so they were far slower learners than Han Li, but they were eventually able to get the hang of things as well.

Under Mistress Liu Hua's instructions, the four of them each picked up a jade slab and began practicing their inscriptions.

Han Li injected his spiritual sense into the Star Wave Pen to activate the star fluid inside, then commenced his inscription, and a stream of silver light flowed out of the tip of the pen onto the jade slab.

This was a process that was very taxing on one's spiritual sense, and the Star Wave Pen resembled a tiny vortex that was constantly absorbing his spiritual sense, but this amount of expenditure was still well within his means.

His expression was calm and focused, while the tip of his bone pen was gliding smoothly over the jade slab, and it didn't take long before a complete star rune had taken shape.

As soon as the final stroke was completed, the entire star rune instantly lit up, then dimmed once again. However, one could clearly sense a burst of invisible power coursing through it.

"Oh? That was quick. Looks like you must have some past tool refinement experience," Mistress Liu Hua said with a hint of surprise in his eyes.

"I have dabbled a little in the past," Han Li replied.

"This is quite well done. The distribution of starpower is very even, and there aren't any problems with it. You can begin attempting more complex runes now," Mistress Liu Hua said after assessing the star rune that Han Li had just inscribed.

Han Li nodded in response, then injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip once again to study the more complex runes.

The other three were far slower to pick up the craft then Han Li, and on average, each of them only successfully inscribed their first star rune after four or five attempts.

Mistress Liu Hua was forced to suppress his impatience to provide instructions to the three of them, and they improved very quickly.

As for Han Li, he was already racing along, and aside from some difficult bottlenecks, he required no instructions from Mistress Liu Hua in any other areas.

Chapter 923: Purple Figure

Close to a month flew by in a flash.

The cultivators of Puppet City worked extremely quickly, and the main frame of the Star Falcon Flying Boat was already complete. It was still going to take some time before the boat's construction was fully completed, but at this stage, the restriction inscription process had to commence.

"Here are the blueprints for the Star Falcon Flying Boat. Take a look first, and I'll explain everything to you in detail after. All of you should be extremely honored. Under normal circumstances, you'd never get to see my blueprints," Mistress Liu Hua harrumphed coldly as he flipped a hand over to produce four jade slips.

After taking a jade slip from Mistress Liu Hua, Han Li injected his spiritual sense into it to find the blueprints of a bird-shaped flying boat inside. The design of the boat was accompanied by many annotations and star runes, forming a diagram of an extremely intricate starpower restriction.

Over the past month of learning from Mistress Liu Hua, Han Li had made some brilliant progress, and thanks to his prior experience in arrays and tool refinement, he was able to somewhat understand this starpower restriction.

This starpower restriction seems to be more geared toward summoning than defense, Han Li thought to himself after some observation.

As for the Xuanyuan Xing and the others, they were still not at a stage where they could interpret the function of the restriction.

After giving Han Li and the others roughly fifteen minutes to examine the blueprints, Mistress Liu Hua declared, "Alright, now, I'm going to tell you about all of the important points in this Star Falcon Restriction."

Han Li had already developed a rudimentary understanding of the restriction on his own, and after hearing what Mistress Liu Hua had to say, many of the questions that had stumped him were answered.

In contrast, Xuanyuan Xing and the others were still clearly none the wiser.

For some reason, Mistress Liu Hua displayed far more patience than he normally did on this occasion, answering all of the questions raised by the trio until they finally had a rough understanding of the restriction.

After all of the questions were answered, Mistress Liu Hua's patience was clearly running thin, and he shook his head in a disgruntled fashion before leading Han Li and the others to the flying boat.

The Puppet City cultivators were still busy at work, and a hint of enmity appeared in their eyes at the sight of Han Li's group, but they made no attempt to stop them.

Upon their arrival, they were approached by Zhuo Ge, who smiled as he greeted, "Welcome, fellow daoists. The main frame of the Star Falcon Flying Boat is already complete, so it's all up to you now."

Mistress Liu Hua nodded in response with a cold expression, then began delegating tasks to Han Li and the others.

After all of the tasks had been assigned, Han Li and the others sprang into action.

Despite Mistress Liu Hua's frosty reception, Zhuo Ge remained unbothered, and he turned to Han Li with a smile as he greeted, "We meet again, Fellow Daoist Li."

"Indeed. Looks like we'll be working together quite extensively from now on," Han Li replied with a nod.

"It's a pleasure working with you," Zhuo Ge said as his smile widened a little.

Even though they had only exchanged a few words, their brief conversation had attracted a lot of attention.

Aside from the two women that Han Li had saved earlier, all of the Puppet City cultivators were observing Han Li with cold animosity in their eyes, while Xuanyuan Xing and the others were also looking at him with tightly furrowed brows, and the atmosphere was starting to become a little tense.

"Li Feiyu, hurry up and get to work!" Mistress Liu Hua scolded with a displeased expression.

Han Li excused himself with Zhuo Ge, then began carrying out the tasks assigned to him, and only then was the tension in the air alleviated.

Meanwhile, Zhuo Ge promptly departed, while Han Li watched his departing figure from out of the corner of his eye.

He was planning to strike up a conversation with Zhuo Ge to see if he knew anything about Violet Spirit, but this was clearly not a good time for that.

With that in mind, he snuck a glance at the Puppet City campsite to discover a cluster of tents, all of which were crafted from some type of special material that could keep out spiritual sense, thereby preventing him from seeing what was inside.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he considered his next move.

Han Li and the others worked day and night without rest, and after close to half a month, most of the restrictions on the main frame of the flying boat had finally been completed.

However, this didn't mean that Star Falcon Restriction was nearing completion. The restriction on the main frame was only a part of the overall restriction, and the majority of the work could only be carried out after construction on the body of the flying boat was completed.

On this day, Han Li had just used up the star fluid in his pen, and he was about to get some more when he heard the sound of footsteps ringing out from the Puppet City camp, accompanied by the sound of laughter.

The laughter was coming from E Kuai, and Han Li wasn't surprised to hear this.

Half a day ago, E Kuai had taken the other city lords to visit the Puppet City camp, and it was unclear what had been discussed between them, but judging from the sound of E Kuai's laughter, things had to have gone quite smoothly.

It didn't take long before E Kuai and the city lords appeared in Han Li's field of view, and they were accompanied by Sha Xin, Zhuo Ge, and several other Puppet City cultivators.

All of a sudden, Han Li's expression abruptly stiffened as he began intently scrutinizing a purple figure beside Sha Xin.

The figure was wearing a veiled bamboo hat that concealed their features, but judging from their figure, it appeared to be a woman.

Even though he could see the woman's face, he couldn't help but feel like her figure was rather similar to Violet Spirit's.

He was just about to find an excuse to go and take a closer look when the purple figure said something to Sha Xin, then made her way back into the Puppet City camp.

Han Li reflexively tried to chase after her, only for a golden-robed young man to suddenly appear before him, blocking his path.

"Outsiders are forbidden from entering our Puppet City's campsite!"

Han Li stopped in his tracks as his eyes narrowed slightly, but he then quickly composed himself as he said, "I have something that I need to speak to City Lord Chen Yang about, so I approached him without thinking once I saw that he had come out of the campsite. Please forgive me for..."

All of a sudden, his voice trailed off as he caught a clear glimpse of the golden-robed young man standing before him.

The man was identical in appearance to a normal human, but he was a lifeless puppet.

"Please step back," the golden-robed puppet said.

Han Li nodded in response, then returned to the Profound City campsite to retrieve a vial of star fluid, then made his way back toward the flying boat.

All of a sudden, Mistress Liu Hua appeared in his path with a displeased expression as he scolded, "Li Feiyu, stop getting distracted and focus on your duties! Don't make me have to speak to you again!"

"Rest assured, Senior Liu Hua, my part is almost done," Han Li replied in a respectful manner.

Mistress Liu Hua gave Han Li a parting glare before turning to depart.

Han Li had only just gotten back to work when Mistress Liu Hua's voice suddenly rang out in his mind through voice transmission.

"I can tell that you're trying to get closer to the people from Puppet City, but don't make it look so obvious! If you keep this, you're going to be labeled a traitor!"

Han Li raised his head slightly to take a glance at Mistress Liu Hua's departing figure, then returned to work.

Thanks to the tireless efforts of Han Li and the others, all of the inscriptions on the main frame were finally completed before nightfall on the third day.

However, the past half-month of work had been extremely taxing on everyone's spiritual sense, so they were all looking rather pale.

After all of the work was done, Mistress Liu Hua's attitude toward Xuanyuan Xing's trio warmed up significantly, and he said, "You've done well. Construction on the Star Falcon Flying Boat must be completed first before we can continue, so take a good rest in the interim."

Han Li and the others bade farewell to Mistress Liu Hua before departing, but Mistress Liu Hua instructed Han Li to stay behind.

"Why are you trying to get close to the people from Puppet City?" Mistress Liu Hua asked with a serious look in his eyes.

"I require a type of material that I've heard can only be found in Puppet City, so I'm hoping to get closer to them to see if I can exchange for that material. Rest assured, I won't let it get in the way of my work," Han Li replied, making up a reason on the spot.

"You think I'm stupid enough to believe something like that? Regardless of what your intentions are, the two cities are still sworn enemies, and the conflict between them cannot be resolved.

“Once access is gained to the Great Ruins, the two cities will instantly turn on each other again, so if you know what's good for you, then you'll stay far away from the Puppet City cultivators! Otherwise, you run the risk of having both cities turn on you!" Mistress Liu Hua harrumphed coldly.

Despite Mistress Liu Hua's cold tone, it was clear that his words came from a place of concern, and a surge of warmth flowed through Han Li's heart upon hearing this.

"Thank you for looking out for me, Mistress Liu Hua. I'll be sure to keep that in mind," Han Li replied in a grateful manner, and Mistress Liu Hua gave another cold harrumph before departing.

Han Li took a glance at the Puppet City campsite, then also returned to his own residence.

As the night deepened, a blurry humanoid figure snuck out of a tent before concealing themselves in the shadow cast by a nearby mountain. From there, they slowly left the Profound City campsite before approaching the Puppet City campsite.

Not only was the figure almost completely invisible, they also weren't giving off any aura at all.

It didn't take long before the figure arrived before the Puppet City campsite, following which they emerged from behind a large rock, revealing themselves to be none other than Han Li.

He had carefully weighed up his options after seeing that purple figure three days ago, and in the end, he was unable to suppress the urge to come here, despite the risks involved.

Chapter 924: Visit from Daoist Xie

Han Li began inspecting his surroundings while thinking of a way to sneak into the Puppet City campsite.

The campsite was patrolled by a series of puppets, and there were also two Puppet City cultivators standing on a pair of watchtowers, surveying the entire campsite from their vantage point.

Right at this moment, someone suddenly patted him on the shoulder, giving him a massive fright.

He immediately swung around with an alarmed expression while rushing back in retreat, but upon catching sight of the figure that had tapped him on the shoulder, he stopped in his tracks, and the apprehension on his face also eased slightly.

The figure that had appeared behind Han Li without any warning was none other than Daoist Xie.

"Come with me, and don't make a sound," Daoist Xie said, then turned and began making his way into the mountain range in the distance.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he took a glance at the Puppet City campsite, but ultimately still followed along after Daoist Xie.

The two of them only stopped once they were far away from the Profound City campsite, and Daoist Xie turned to Han Li and asked, "Are you planning to search for Violet Spirit in the Puppet City campsite?"

"That's right. A few days ago, I saw someone in the Puppet City campsite that looked rather similar to Violet Spirit. I don't know if it actually is her, but I need to get to the bottom of this," Han Li replied.

"You're a fool! Immortal spiritual power is inaccessible in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so aura concealment is extremely difficult. You're going to get yourself killed if you venture into the Puppet City campsite under these circumstances!" Daoist Xie harrumphed coldly.

A look of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

In this moment, Daoist Xie's demeanor was no different from that of a normal person.

"I'm aware of the risks involved, but I can't just do nothing," Han Li said with tightly furrowed brows.

"Even so, you have to take into account the current circumstances. Sneaking into the Puppet City campsite now is far too reckless. You'll just have to leave this for later. If that person really is Violet Spirit, she's not going to suddenly run away, so there's no need for you to be in such a hurry,"Daoist Xie said.

"That's true, I was indeed too reckless," Han Li sighed as he nodded in response.

Daoist Xie took a glance at Han Li, then asked, "What aura concealment method are you using? It must be a very advanced one, considering even I almost wasn't able to see through it. No wonder you dared to try and venture into the Puppet City campsite like this."

"If it really was that advanced, then you wouldn't have caught me," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

At the moment, he was using the Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique, a concealment secret technique included in the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

The secret technique allowed one to seal all of their profound acupoints, but the downside was that no profound acupoints could be used while this secret technique was in effect.

After that, a long silence ensued, and Daoist Xie stared expressionlessly at Han Li without saying a word.

"I'm assuming you didn't come to me so late at night just to tell me this, right, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked.

"I do indeed have some other matters to discuss with you. Barring any mishaps, the Star Falcon Flying Boat should be ready in another half a month. The entrance found by E Kuai and Sha Xin is a decent one, so all of you should be able to enter the Great Ruins with no problems. When that time comes, I'm going to need your help," Daoist Xie said.

"It seems like you know a lot about the Great Ruins, Brother Xie. Could it be that you've regained more memories? It feels like you're very different from before," Han Li said.

Daoist Xie offered no reply to Han Li's question as he turned to look in the direction of the Great Ruins with some mixed emotions in his eyes.

Shortly thereafter, he turned his gaze back to Han Li as he sighed, "I have indeed recovered a lot of my memories, but I'm afraid I still can't tell you about them right now."

"In that case, just tell me when the time is right," Han Li replied with a nod.

"I don't have much time left. I can't be absent for too long. Otherwise, Chen Yang could notice. This jade slip contains what I need you to do for me," Daoist Xie said, then opened his mouth to release a white jade slip.

Han Li caught the jade slip and was just about to say something when Daoist Xie raised a hand to interrupt him.

"Make sure to do as the jade slip says. I promise you that it'll only be beneficial to you, and there could perhaps even be a massive opportunity waiting for you."

After that, Daoist Xie promptly slipped away into the night, rushing back toward the Profound City campsite as a black shadow.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

At this moment, the speed displayed by Daoist Xie wasn't inferior by much compared to his own.

He took a glance at Daoist Xie's departing figure, then turned his gaze back to the white jade slip before injecting a wisp of his spiritual sense into it.

In the next instant, a stunned look appeared in his eyes, followed by a look of indecision.

After a long period of contemplation, he seemed to have finally made u his mind, and he crushed the jade slip into powder before making his way back to the Profound City campsite.

With the Puppet City cultivators working on the construction of the Star Falcon Flying Boat, Han Li and the others had nothing to do, so they stayed in their tents to rest, and they were occasionally summoned by Mistress Liu Hua for lessons on Star Falcon Restriction.

Around half a month flew by in a flash, and the construction of the Star Falcon Flying Boat was finally complete.

A silver flying boat was resting on the ground, giving off a metallic gleam that gave it an indestructible appearance.

The entire boat was extremely streamlined in form, with two silver wings that were angled upward, giving it the appearance of a silver bird that was about to take flight.

The interior of the flying boat was hollow, allowing people to stay inside, and there was a row of windows on each side that was sealed by a type of transparent material that allowed one to see outside.

At this moment, all of the Profound City cultivators were gathered in front of the flying boat, and E Kuai patted it with his hand a few times, but there was no reverberation, as if the flying boat were solid all the way through.

"The fellow daoists of your Puppet City must be truly exceptional craftsmen to have created such a sturdy and intricate flying boat in just a month," E Kuai praised.

Sha Xin was also present with seven or eight Puppet City cultivators by her side, and she smiled as she replied, "You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist E. In a normal setting, this boat would be able to fly on its own, but suction force from the black abyss will be too much for it to bear, so we'll have to count on Fellow Daoist Liu Hua."

Han Li swept his gaze over the Puppet City cultivators, following which a hint of disappointment flashed through his eyes at the absence of the purple-robed woman.

"We'll be counting on you to apply the finishing touches, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua," E Kuai said as he turned to Mistress Liu Hua, who was observing the flying boat with his brows slightly furrowed.

He strode over to the boat, then laid a hand onto its surface in silence.

"Is there something wrong, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua?" E Kuai asked.

"Has Silver Gilded Fluid been injected into the walls of the boat, Fellow Daoist Sha Xin?" Mistress Liu Hua asked.

"That's right. Silver Gilded Fluid is a secret concoction of our Puppet City, so I didn't think you'd be aware of its existence. The injection of Silver Gilded Fluid allows the different materials in the ship's walls to come together more cohesively, thereby strengthening its defenses," Sha Xin explained, and Mistress Liu Hua fell silent upon hearing this.

"Is there something wrong, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua?" E Kuai repeated.

"No, it's just that the primary material used to make Silver Gilded Fluid is Silver Gilded Stone, which conflicts a little with the star fluid that I've prepared, so that's going to make the restriction inscription process a more difficult, but it shouldn't be a problem," Mistress Liu Hua replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he opened his mouth to say something, only for Mistress Liu Hua to stop him with a stern look.

"In that case, please begin right away, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua. We don't know how long the spatial storm will remain weak for, so the longer we delay, the greater the chance that something could go wrong," E Kuai said.

Mistress Liu Hua nodded in response, then led Han Li and the others into the boat, while the other cultivators from the two cities departed.

It was unclear whether this was due to the materials used to craft the Star Falcon Flying Boat, or if the boat itself possessed this innate property, but as soon as they entered it, all of the sounds from outside were cut out.

"Is this really not going to have a negative impact, Senior Liu Hua?" Han Li asked with a grim expression.

Unlike the earlier preparatory work that they had completed on the main frame of the flying boat, they were going to truly commence the process of setting up the Star Falcon Restriction now, and this required both the inscription of runes and the addition of many tools and materials, thereby making for a far more difficult process.

With the Silver Gilded Fluid posing an additional obstacle, the process was only going to be made even more difficult.

Han Li was relatively confident that he would be able to deal with these difficulties, but the same couldn't be said for the other three.

Xuanyuan Xing's trio had clearly also realized this, and uneasy looks appeared on their faces.

"How could it possibly not have a negative impact? This is where we'll begin truly constructing the array. If any mistakes are made in the process, not only will the array fail, the materials and tools used will also be ruined. What a massive pain in the backside!" Mistress Liu Hua grumbled with a furious expression.

"Could it be that you haven't brought much materials with you, Senior Liu Hua?" Han Li asked.

"I brought two batches of materials, and I thought that would definitely be enough, but that may not be the case now," Mistress Liu Hua harrumphed coldly as he glared at Xuanyuan Xing's trio, and the three of them lowered their heads with embarrassed expressions.

"In that case, why didn't you inform City Lord E Kuai of this, Senior Liu Hua? If we all combine our efforts, I'm sure we can think of a solution," Han Li said.

A peculiar look flashed through Mistress Liu Hua's eyes upon hearing this, and his attitude suddenly took a turn as he said, "It's just a minor hiccup, there's no need to inform City Lord E. Don't worry, just do your best, and I'll make sure everything goes smoothly in the end."

Chapter 925: Remedial Action

"How about you and I work on the Star Falcon Restriction by ourselves, Senior Liu Hua? That way, we'll be a little behind schedule, but it'll be a much safer route to take, and I'm sure City Lord E and the others won't mind," Han Li suggested.

"That won't work. The Star Falcon Restriction was designed with five people in mind, so all five of us need to work on it at once. Otherwise, the restriction will be thrown into a state of imbalance and completely collapse. Alright, that's enough talking, let's get started," Mistress Liu Hua said.

After that, Mistress Liu Hua gave Han Li and the others another detailed rundown of the Star Falcon Restriction before work commenced.

Just like in their prior arrangement, Mistress Liu Hua was responsible for the central area of the boat, while Han Li and the others worked around him.

Han Li began inscribing runes onto the flying boat with his Star Wave Pen, but the Silver Gilded Fluid in the walls of the ship was constantly conflicting against the star fluid in his pen, making the process several times more difficult.

Han Li took a deep breath, then increased his spiritual sense to stabilize the star fluid in response.

Given his current level of spiritual sense and his understanding of the Star Falcon Restriction, he was able to acclimate himself very quickly, and it didn't take long before things began to fall into place for him.

In contrast, Xuanyuan Xing's trio was having a much rougher time. In particular, Xuanyuan Xing had failed four or five times in a row within the span of less than half a day, wasting a lot of materials in the process.

Mistress Liu Hua was getting very disgruntled by these repeated failures, and he had no choice but to stop what he was doing and provide more instruction to Xuanyuan Xing's trio.

Some time later, the majority of the Star Falcon Flying Boat's interior was riddled with glowing silver patterns, while Mistress Liu Hua and the others were standing at the center of the boat.

Xuanyuan Xing's trio were hanging their heads in shame, while Han Li stood beside them in silence.

Mistress Liu Hua was standing in front of them with a grim expression, seemingly contemplating something.

At this point, most of the array had already been completed, but due to the fact that Xuanyuan Xing's trio had wasted too much materials in the process, they had finally run out.

"What do we do now, Senior Liu Hua?" Han Li asked after a long silence.

"I still have some array tools left, and the used up materials aren't all completely ruined, so they can be reused after some repair. The main problem right now is that we're missing Sea Condensed Jade, Blush Crystals, and Earth Tide Stones," Mistress Liu Hua replied in a calm manner.

"Could it be that you already have a way to source more of those three materials, Senior Liu Hua?" Han Li asked after seeing Mistress Liu Hua's calm expression.

"There's a type of scaled beast called the Ice Scaled Armadillo in the Bipolar Extreme Mountain Range, and the horn on its head is very similar to Sea Condensing Crystal, so that can be used as a substitute. I recall spotting some Ice Scaled Armadillo tracks on the way here, and I presume it'll only take us about two days to go and hunt a few.

“As for Blush Crystals, according to my knowledge, City Lord Fu Jian has some, so I can just go ask for a few from him. The only problem right now is that I don't know where we're going to procure more Earth Tide Stones from," Mistress Liu Hua said.

Right at this moment, a voice rang out from outside the flying boat.

"There's a type of Puppet City puppet that has parts made from Earth Tide Stones, so I assume Fellow Daoist Sha Xin should have some. I'll go borrow some from her."

Immediately thereafter, E Kuai and Chen Yang made their way into the boat.

"City Lord E!" Mistress Liu Hua hurriedly rose to his feet as an awkward look flashed through his eyes.

"You're still just as prideful as ever, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua. Even though you promised me that you would take care of the Star Falcon Flying Boat's construction, you should've spoken to me upon encountering difficulties, rather than try to tackle everything on your own," E Kuai said with a faint smile.

Upon hearing this, Han Li finally understood why Mistress Liu Hua was unwilling to bring up this matter to E Kuai.

An embarrassed look appeared on Mistress Liu Hua's face as he sighed, "I was too ashamed to turn to you for help after screwing everything up, but seeing as you've already been made aware of this, then we'll do as you say, City Lord E."

E Kuai nodded in response, then turned to Chen Yang as he said, "I'll get you to hunt the Ice Scaled Armadillos. I also recall seeing some tracks on the way here, and if I recall correctly, it was roughly in this location."

He pulled out a jade slip as he spoke, then drew out a rough map of the Bipolar Extreme Mountain Range onto it before marking out a spot on the map and handing it to Chen Yang.

"Leave it to me," Chen Yang said as he took the jade slip before turning to depart, only to be stopped by E Kuai.

"Hold on a second. The Bipolar Extreme Mountain Range is fraught with peril, so it wouldn't be wise for you to go on your own. I'll get Li Feiyu to come with you. He just so happens to be familiar with Sea Condensing Crystals, so he'll be able to help you out."

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response.

"City Lord E, I was the one who wasted the most materials, so please let me go and help them as well. That way, I can at least somewhat atone for my mistakes," Xuanyuan Xing suddenly implored as he stepped forward.

"Alright, then you can go as well," E Kuai replied with a nod.

The three of them made some brief preparations, then left the campsite to hunt for Ice Scaled Armadillos.

Due to the fact that they were going back the same way that they had come from, they were able to make very fast progress, closing in the marked spot on the map after only a day.

At night, the glacial aura in the air suddenly became more pronounced, and gusts of freezing winds were blowing through the area without pause.

The winds were truly freezing, to the point that even with their tremendous physical constitutions, the three of them were beginning to feel numb in their extremities.

"These weather conditions are a little abnormal, so let's find a place to seek shelter in for now," Chen Yang said.

Xuanyuan Xing seemed to be struggling quite a bit, and he eagerly nodded in agreement with this proposal.

Han Li was still able to go on, but he didn't raise any objections, either.

After searching around nearby for a while, they quickly found a relatively obscure cave to enter.

The temperatures in the cave were slightly less unforgiving, and the three of them were all quite relieved as they sat down inside.

Xuanyuan Xing seemed to be the one struggling the most with the frigid temperatures, and he found a place to sit in the deepest part of the cave.

After that, he pulled out a small brazier and a bamboo container from the cloth pouch on his back, and he poured out some oily black substance into the brazier.

A small spark landed in the brazier, and the oily black substance instantly erupted into flames.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Even though the cave was quite obscure, a bright flame could still attract the attention of scaled beasts outside.

He took a glance at Chen Yang, who didn't raise any objections, so he didn't say anything, either.

"City Lord Chen, Fellow Daoist Li, come and join me by the fire. I can see that the two of you are far more resistant to the cold than I am, but it's still a good idea to keep yourselves warm," Xuanyuan Xing said.

"Sure," Chen Yang said as he strode over to the brazier, followed closely by Han Li.

The fire generated by the combusting black oil in the brazier was extremely hot, and even in these freezing conditions, Han Li felt as if he were basking in the light of the noon sun.

"This is quite a remarkable substance!" Han Li exclaimed as he looked into the brazier.

"It's just a type of scaled beast fat," Xuanyuan Xing replied with a smile.

Han Li nodded in response and didn't ask any further questions.

"Why are the winds so strong tonight?" Xuanyuan Xing murmured in a perplexed voice.

"Due to its close proximity to the black abyss, the Bipolar Extreme Mountain has always been prone to drastic changes in weather, so this is not a strange occurrence," Chen Yang said.

The howling of the wind outside was growing louder and louder, but despite this, the interior of the cave remained as warm as ever, resembling a safe haven in a cold and bleak world.

Thanks to the fire, their stiff and frozen bodies gradually loosened up, the task that they had been assigned wasn't particularly difficult, so the three of them were feeling quite relaxed and began chatting with one another.

However, as the night deepened, the conversation quickly petered out.

Xuanyuan Xing leaned against the wall of the cave and fell asleep first, while Chen Yang also sat down with his legs crossed before closing his eyes to rest.

Han Li didn't feel like sleeping, nor was he in the mood to cultivate, and he stared into the flame in the brazier with a contemplative look on his face.

At some point, Chen Yang opened his eyes, and he asked through voice transmission, "It's already quite late, Fellow Daoist Li, why are you not resting? The task assigned to us isn't overly difficult, but it's still a good idea to rest up."

Han Li took a glance at Xuanyuan Xing, then replied through voice transmission, "This cave is quite obscure, but we're still in the Bipolar Extreme Mountain Range, so there's no guarantee that we won't be attacked at night. Hence, it's best to have someone stay up through the night."

"With your exceptional powers and cautious nature, I'm sure you'll be able to accomplish great things in the Great Ruins," Chen Yang chuckled.

"I don't know about that, I'm only accompanying everyone into the Great Ruins on this occasion in order to broaden my own horizons," Han Li replied with a smile.

"There are countless precious treasures in the Great Ruins, is there nothing that appeals to you?" Chen Yang asked with a meaningful expression.

"Oh? What do you mean by that, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Han Li asked.

"I heard that you paid a visit to Fellow Daoist Liu Hua prior to the Five City Martial Gathering, and there seemed to have been some mention of Heavenly Qilin Crystals during that visit," Chen Yang mused.

Chapter 926: Hunting Armadillos

"That's right, I visited Senior Liu Hua to find a way to remove the Black Tribulation Centipede in my body. You have some very good sources, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li replied.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Li. I wasn't tracking you or anything like that, I only happened to learn of this by chance. Heavenly Qilin Crystals can be found in the Great Ruins, so if you need my help, then I'll be sure to do everything in my power to assist you," Chen Yang promised with a wide smile.

"Thank you for looking out for me, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li replied.

"You haven't been in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so you haven't had a chance to explore the Great Ruins yet, but I've already been in there on several occasions. In the face of truly alluring treasures, so-called friendships and even the differences between the two cities can be completely disregarded. You're a smart man, so I'm sure you don't need me to tell you that, Fellow Daoist Li," Chen Yang said as a peculiar tone crept into his voice.

Han Li took a glance at Chen Yang, but didn't say anything.

"In my eyes, the power of the individual is far too insignificant in the Great Ruins. I've always admired you greatly, and if you agree to work with me, I can guarantee you that I'll find you a Heavenly Qilin Crystal, so please consider my offer carefully," Chen Yang continued, then closed his eyes and spoke no further.

Han Li remained silent as his eyes narrowed slightly.

As the date of entry into the Great Ruins drew closer, not only was the collaboration between Puppet City and Profound City about to come to an end, all of the city lords were also hatching their own plans. Even though Han Li was technically Chen Yang's subordinate, he didn't necessarily have to obey him under these special circumstances.

What Chen Yang was proposing was quite clear, but Han Li didn't know what his objectives were, and under these circumstances, he didn't want to rush into any agreements.

The night quickly passed by, and by the time night transitioned into day, the howling wind outside the cave had already subsided. It was still extremely cold outside, but far better than it had been the night before.

"Let's go, we still have some way to go until we reach our destination," Chen Yang said before departing.

Han Li inhaled a lungful of cold air as his brows furrowed slightly.

Perhaps it was because he had stayed up the entire night to keep watch, but at this moment, he was feeling rather weary, and he felt like he couldn't muster up much strength.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Li?" Xuanyuan Xing asked. "You don't look very energetic."

"It's nothing, I guess I'm still just not accustomed to the environment here," Han Li replied, then took another deep breath as channeled his own bloodline powers, and to his relief, the weariness in his body quickly faded away.

"In that case, let's set off," Xuanyuan Xing said.

Han Li nodded in response, and he was just about to leave the cave when his expression suddenly changed slightly as he cast his gaze toward the left, where there were currently two figures racing along in a distant mountain range.

One of them was Zhuo Ge of Puppet City, while the other was the dwarf-like man who was no more than four feet in height.

"Hide!" Chen Yang hurriedly urged at the sight of the two men, then immediately concealed himself behind a giant rock, and Han Li and Xuanyuan Xing also ducked behind some cover.

Zhuo Ge and his companion didn't notice Han Li's trio, and they continued onward, quickly vanishing into the distance.

Only then did Han Li's trio slowly emerge from their hiding spots.

"What are those two doing here?" Xuanyuan Xing asked.

"There are many treasures and unique scaled beasts to be found in the Bipolar Extreme Mountain Range, so it's no surprise to see Puppet City cultivators scouring the mountain range. We still have a mission to complete, so let's not get entangled in any other matters," Chen Yang said.

"Do you know those two, Fellow Daoist Chen? Do they pose a threat to us?" Han Li asked.

"The taller one of the two is called Zhuo Ge, while the shorter one is called Wu Yun, and both of them are top-tier cultivators of Puppet City. It's very difficult to gauge the power level of Puppet City cultivators as combat prowess is a culmination of their own powers and the puppets that they use.

“With a powerful puppet at their disposal, even an ordinary Puppet City cultivator could have their powers enhanced by tenfold, so do not take any Puppet City cultivator lightly," Chen Yang warned.

Han Li and Xuanyuan Xing nodded in response.

After waiting for a while longer, Chen Yang said, "They should be far away now, so let's go."

Thus, the three of them promptly departed, and after close to half a day, they had reached a basin that was nestled in between some mountains.

The basin was filled with scattered rocks, and freezing winds were blowing through the basin to produce a rustling sound akin to that produced by countless crawling insects.

At the bottom of the basin was a layer of faint blue mist that, for some reason, refused to dissipate in the wind, and after consulting the jade slip momentarily, Chen Yang declared, "This should be the spot."

Han Li cast his gaze toward the basin up ahead to find that it was circular in shape and so massive that he couldn't see the other side.

Chen Yang led the way forward, followed closely by Han Li and Xuanyuan Xing.

Due to the enormous size of the basin, the three of them decided to split up.

Han Li was going to search through the left side of the basin, Chen Yang was going to venture into the middle, while Xuanyuan Xing was sent to the right side, and they had agreed to reunite at the entrance of the basin a day later.

Half a day later.

A fist came crashing down with tremendous power, slamming down onto the head of a snow wolf scaled beast.

The snow wolf's head exploded like a watermelon, and its massive body crashed to the ground and spasmed a few times before quickly falling still.

Han Li dug a beast core out of the snow wolf's head and stowed it away before looking around with tightly furrowed brows.

The spatial pressure in the Bipolar Extreme Mountain Range was even heavier than that of Profound City, so his spiritual sensory range had been limited to only around twenty kilometers. After half a day of searching, he hadn't found a single Ice Scaled Armadillo, but he had encountered many other scaled beasts.

He cast his gaze forward to discover that the rocks up ahead were only becoming more massive. Some of them were hundreds of feet tall, resembling small mountains, and the blue mist on the ground was also denser than before.

This isn't going to work...

After some contemplation, Han Li leaped onto a large rock, then sprang onto another one, and he began jumping from rock to rock while releasing his spiritual sense to examine the surrounding area.

There were many scaled beasts in the basin, some of which even Han Li found to be rather dangerous, so he was taking some risk by jumping around like this and making himself a target, but that was a risk that he was just going to have to accept if he wanted to find an Ice Scaled Armadillo as soon as possible.

After warding off two scaled beast attacks, Han Li's eyes finally lit up as he cast his gaze toward the right before rushing away in that direction.

A few moments later, he arrived in a dense quarry of rocks, all of which were a translucent white color. Unlike the rocks that Han Li had encountered thus far, these seemed to be some type of special ore that was giving a bone-chilling glacial aura.

At this moment, there was a scaled beast that was taller than the average adult human munching on these pieces of white ore.

The creature had a translucent blue and white horn on its forehead, and its entire body was covered in blue scales, while a long tail was dragging along behind it.

It was an Ice Scaled Armadillo!

Alerted by the sound of Han Li's approach, the Ice Scaled Armadillo looked up to find Han Li swooping down upon it like a hunting hawk, and it immediately let loose a sharp cry akin to the crying of an infant before darting away as a blue shadow, traveling at an extraordinary speed.

"You're not getting away!" Han Li yelled as the profound acupoints on his legs lit up, releasing rays of white light that formed a starry white cloud, which lifted him up into the air.

At the same time, he stomped heavily down onto the space beneath him, causing it to ripple violently as he propelled himself through the air, instantly reaching the Ice Scaled Armadillo before reaching down to make a grab for it.

The Ice Scaled Armadillo screeched once again as it slapped the ground with its long tail, allowing it to change directions in an instant and just barely evade Han Li's grab.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he twisted around in mid-air before stomping down onto the space underfoot again.

A dull thump rang out as he also changed directions to continue pursuing the Ice Scaled Armadillo, and at the same time, he raised his right hand before flicking his middle and index fingers through the air, sending two finger projections flying into the Ice Scaled Armadillo.

The armadillo was instantly sent flying, somersaulting through the air a few times before crashing into a large rock.

It seemed to have been enraged, and it clambered to its feet before pouncing at Han Li in retaliation.

It let loose a low roar as the horn on its head began glowing brightly, and a series of white stripes instantly appeared over its blue body. At the same time, it swelled up like a balloon, expanding to several times its original size in the blink of an eye, and its front claws also elongated about twofold as it lashed out at Han Li.

Simultaneously, its blue tail whipped through the air as a blue shadow, hurtling toward Han Li's face like a speeding harrow.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as he thrust a palm forward, and the flurry of claw projections unleashed by the Ice Scaled Armadillo instantly stopped cold in their tracks before shattering as if they had crashed into an invisible wall.

As for its tail, that also drew to a screeching halt around half a foot away from Han Li's hand before shattering into pieces.

In the next instant, a dull thump rang out as the Ice Scaled Armadillo was sent flying back even faster than it had come, and it crashed heavily into the ground with a gruesome crunch as countless bones in its body were shattered upon impact.

Its body also reverted back to its original size, and blue blood came gushing out of its mouth as the light began to fade from its eyes.

Han Li landed beside the Ice Scaled Armadillo and carefully examined its horn momentarily before nodding to himself and severing the horn.

According to Mistress Liu Hua, they were going to require at least five or six of these horns, and he didn't know if Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing had managed to gather any.

After stowing the horn away, Han Li cast his gaze toward the quarry of white rocks with a contemplative look in his eyes.

So this is what Ice Scaled Armadillos like to feed on...

After a brief pause, he continued deeper into the basin.

Chapter 927: Private Meeting

Half a day later, a loud explosion rang out near another quarry of crystalline white rocks, followed by a despairing wail.

A large hole had been pierced into an Ice Scaled Armadillo's abdomen by a sharp rock, and it tried in futility to crawl away, only to ultimately fall to the ground.

Han Li arrived beside the Ice Scaled Armadillo before quickly harvesting its horn.

After discovering their food source, Han Li's encounter rate with these Ice Scaled Armadillos had increased significantly, and after only half a day, he had already found four.

At this point, it was already very close to the rendezvous with Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing, so it was time to head back.

However, over the past half a day, he had been focused solely on searching for clusters of this white ore, so he had strayed away from his designated area, and he didn't really know where he currently was.

After jumping onto a rock and inspecting his surroundings momentarily, he quickly cast his gaze in a certain direction.

The rendezvous point should be in that direction...

The environment in the basin was very monotonous, so he couldn't be sure.

Even so, he still decided to depart in that direction while releasing his spiritual sense to search for the tracks that he had made on the way here.

The sky was quickly beginning to turn dark, and the freezing winds were picking up once again.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he sped up a little, but shortly thereafter, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he stopped in his tracks.

Two figures had appeared in his spiritual sensory range, but instead of Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing, they were Zhuo Ge and Wu Yun.

Why are they here? Could it be that they actually already noticed us earlier, but pretended to be oblivious, only to follow us here with sinister intentions?

Han Li immediately withdrew his spiritual sense upon detecting the two Puppet City cultivators.

At the same time, he also unleashed his Myriad Acupoint Technique, and all of a sudden, his aura completely vanished.

After that, he began to travel in the direction of the two Puppet City cultivators, and upon getting close, he hid behind a large rock.

Zhuo Ge and Wu Yun were standing near a giant rock several thousand feet away, and both of them were looking around with tightly furrowed brows.

Han Li immediately ducked behind his rock once again to remain unseen.

It doesn't look like they were planning to attack us.

A perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face as he began to wait. He wanted to see just what these two were up to.

Over two hours flew by in a flash.

All of a sudden, a pair of black figures appeared in the distance, and they sped onto the scene, reaching Zhuo Ge and Wu Yun in the blink of an eye.

Both figures were dressed in cloaks with their hoods up, making it impossible to see their faces.

A hint of relief appeared on Zhuo Ge's face at the sight of the two figures, following which he harrumphed coldly, "Could you two have come any later?"

The two figures offered no response, and one of them began to inspect their surroundings.

Han Li hurriedly ducked back down again upon seeing this.

"Rest assured, we've already carefully examined the nearby area several times to ensure that there's no one eavesdropping in hiding," Zhuo Ge said.

One of the cloaked figures lowered their hood and smiled as they said, "My apologies. E Kuai has been keeping us on a very tight leash, so it wasn't easy for me to manufacture this opportunity to bring Fellow Daoist Chen out here."

The figure was none other than Xuanyuan Xing.

At this moment, he was displaying none of his usual timidity. Instead, he was looking extremely confident and self-assured, and it was as if he had turned into a different person.

The other figure also lowered their hood, revealing them to be Chen Yang.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Judging from what Xuanyuan Xing had said, it seemed that they had already agreed to meet here well in advance.

On top of that, Xuanyuan Xing had just said that he had manufactured this opportunity, so could it be that he had intentionally failed in his array inscriptions, thereby wasting all those materials just so he could come here with Chen Yang?

If that were the case, then Xuanyuan Xing really had done a very good job of fooling everyone.

"I've heard many great things about you, City Lord Chen," Zhuo Ge said with a smile.

"Cut the chit-chat. Show me the proof," Chen Yang replied with a cold expression.

Zhuo Ge remained unbothered by Chen Yang's frosty attitude, pulling out a crimson jade slab before handing it to Chen Yang.

Han Li was just about to take a closer look when the jade slab was transferred into Chen Yang's hand, thereby obscuring it from view.

Even though it was only a fleeting glance, Han Li was still able to see some of the things on the jade slab. It seemed to have been riddled with tiny text, and there was also what appeared to have been an array diagram engraved upon it.

Chen Yang examined the jade slab closely, and a series of emotions flashed over his face, including shock, anger, and indignation.

Moments later, Chen Yang took a deep breath to compose himself, then stowed the jade slab away without Zhuo Ge's permission, but Zhuo Ge didn't seem to mind.

Chen Yang was silent for a moment, then said, "I agree to your proposal. However..."

Whatever he said next was delivered through voice transmission, and from there, the four men began conversing in secret through voice transmission.

After a brief discussion, all of them nodded in unison, seemingly having arrived at some type of agreement.

"Alright, everything that needs to be said has already been said, so let's end things here," Chen Yang said before turning to depart.

Xuanyuan Xing nodded at Zhuo Ge and Wu Yun, then also departed after Chen Yang.

Following their departure, Wu Yun asked in a tender, childlike voice, "Zhuo Ge, do you think Chen Yang will actually do what we agreed upon?"

"He has no other choice," Zhuo Ge replied in an indifferent manner.

"I suppose so," Wu Yun replied with a nod.

After that, the two of them promptly departed as well.

Only after waiting for a long while did Han Li emerge from hiding with a contemplative look on his face, following which he also departed from the scene.

The night quickly passed by.

At the entrance of the basin, Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing stood side by side, seemingly waiting for something.

Before long, they were approached by a figure from afar, and it was none other than Han Li.

At this moment, he was looking a little worse for wear. His clothes were torn and stained with blood in many places, and he was also looking quite weary.

"My apologies. I ventured too deep into the basin in search for Ice Scaled Armadillos yesterday, and I was also attacked by several powerful scaled beasts. I lost my way while escaping from them, so I wasn't able to return here in a timely fashion," Han Li said with a wry smile.

"You have nothing to apologize for, Fellow Daoist Li. Thank you for your tireless efforts," Chen Yang replied with a smile, and there was nothing unnatural about his expression.

"How did things go on your end, Fellow Daoist Li?" Chen Yang asked.

"I was able to kill four Ice Scaled Armadillos," Han Li replied as he pulled out four translucent horns.

"I killed three, while Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan killed one, so we have more than enough," Chen Yang said as he pulled out his own three horns.

"I came here to make amends, but it seems like all I did was drag everyone down again," Xuanyuan Xing said with an embarrassed expression as he pulled out a single horn.

Han Li sneered internally at the act that Xuanyuan Xing was putting on, but on the surface, he maintained an amicable smile as he said, "Don't say that, Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan. It was a team effort, and ultimately, we managed to reach our target, did we not?"

"Alright, now that we've gathered enough horns, let's go back right away so we don't keep Fellow Daoist Liu Hua waiting any longer. You don't look so good at the moment, Fellow Daoist Li, will you be alright to make the return journey?" Chen Yang asked.

"I'm fine, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li replied with a smile.

With that, the three of them set off in the opposite direction that they had come from.

Having already made this trip twice, they had become very familiar with the route, and it only took them a day to return to the campsite.

The Blush Crystals and Earth Tide Stones had already been prepared, and with the Ice Scaled Armadillo horns ready as well, work was able to resume.

……

Around a month passed by in a flash.

On this night, the sky was filled with stars, brightly illuminating the area in front of the canyon.

A giant, black flying boat was hovering around three feet above the ground with its wings extended outward on either side, looking like a giant bird that was about to take flight.

The entire boat was riddled with densely packed white runes, and even though they weren't glowing at the moment, they still appeared to be quite remarkable.

The two campsites were still standing, but the cultivators of the two cities were already prepared to set off, and they were arranged in a pair of orderly lines on either side of the flying boat.

Han Li was standing within the crowd on the left, and his gaze was constantly roaming over the collection of Puppet City cultivators.

There were far more Puppet City cultivators than last time, even more so than the number of Profound City cultivators.

Zhuo Ge met Han Li's gaze and gave him a slight nod, to which Han Li responded with a smile and a nod of his own.

The two women that he had saved were also looking at him with smiles on their faces under the veils of their conical bamboo hats, but they didn't dare to nod at Han Li as Zhuo Ge had.

In contrast, the other Puppet City cultivators were regarding Han Li in a far less friendly manner, but Han Li didn't care about that at all.

Instead, his attention was focused solely on searching for that purple-robed woman that he had caught a brief glance of last time, but unfortunately, she wasn't present.

Chapter 928: Setting Off

The other Profound City cultivators clearly weren't very happy to see Han Li initiating eye contact with the Puppet City cultivators, and someone murmured in a disdainful voice, "Shameless scoundrel! He must be a Puppet City spy!"

"You're already dying to return to your true allies, aren't you? A slave will always be a slave!" Feng Wuchen scoffed in a cold voice.

He wasn't being excessively loud, but he made sure to be just loud enough for everyone present to hear him.

Han Li had ignored all of the unflattering words directed at him up to this point, but upon hearing what Feng Wuchen had to say, he chuckled, "You must be itching for another beating."

"What did you say?" Feng Wuchen snapped as he clenched his fists tightly and took a step toward Han Li, followed by the other two Profound End City cultivators.

Han Li spread his hands open with an unfazed grin, challenging all three of them to come at him at once.

The three of them were furious to see this, and the profound acupoints on their bodies lit up as they prepared to attack.

Gu Qianxun's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and after a brief hesitation, she arrived by Han Li's side.

The three Excess Passage City cultivators also stepped up with hostile expressions, but Duan Tong's gaze was focused on Gu Qianxun.

Xuanyuan Xing was looking on with tightly furrowed brows, and after some hesitation, he remained still on the spot as he cast an inquisitive gaze toward Chen Yang.

Chen Yang could see that Qin Yuan had no intention of stepping in, and he was just about to get involved when another figure suddenly appeared beside Han Li.

To Han Li's surprise, it was none other than Fang Chan, who was still holding a greasy roasted beast leg.

Even in this tense setting, he was still munching on his beast leg with a completely unfazed look on his face.

With Gu Qianxun and Fang Chan backing up Han Li, even if all of the Excess Passage City and Profound End City cultivators were to join forces, they would have to think twice about making any aggressive moves.

With Fang Chan entering the picture, Sun Tu immediately stood up to mediate, putting on a stern expression as he yelled, "What do you all think you're doing? You're making fools out of yourselves!"

Han Li took a glance at the Puppet City camp, and sure enough, all of them were watching the proceedings with mocking sneers on their faces.

Gu Qianxun was eager to defuse the conflict, and she immediately said, "My apologies, City Lord Sun. Let's all calm down and take a step back."

Only then did Qin Yuan and the others arrive onto the scene, and they pretended to scold the cultivators under their command briefly, thereby bringing this farce to a conclusion.

After the conflict was defused, Gu Qianxun asked through voice transmission, "Fellow Daoist Li, were you actually planning to fight them here?"

"How about you? Were you planning to stand with me to oppose them?" Han Li asked.

"I... You and I are from the same city, so I had to stand up for you," Gu Qianxun replied after a brief hesitation.

"There's no need to worry, City Lord E Kuai wouldn't allow a conflict to break out here," Han Li assured with a smile.

"In that case, were you intentionally provoking them?" Gu Qianxun asked as she raised an eyebrow.

"That's not true, he was the one who started the conflict. Come to think of it, I wonder why Fang Chan chose to stand with me just now," Han Li said as he turned a perplexed gaze toward Fang Chan.

"Maybe it's because you called out to him last time during the scaled python attack? He may not be very bright, but he's very loyal and knows better than others the importance of repaying kindness," Gu Qianxun replied with a smile.

"That seems to be the only plausible reason," Han Li said with a nod.

"Honestly, I don't blame them for what they did. Why do you keep looking at the Puppet City cultivators? What are you looking at?" Gu Qianxun asked.

"Nothing, I was just... looking around," Han Li replied with an awkward smile.

"Has one of the women caught your eye? The women of Puppet City are indeed quite beautiful, but all of them are adept in both the arts of puppetry and seduction, so if you're not careful, you could end up being lured in and refined into a puppet by one of them," Gu Qianxun jibed.

"Did Senior Liu Hua tell you some things? Is that why you're making fun of me?" Han Li asked with a resigned smile.

An amused smile appeared on Gu Qianxun's face, following which she said through voice transmission, "My father... Mistress Liu Hua really does think very highly of you, and he's very sincere about accepting you as his disciple. All you have to do is remain by his side for ten thousand years. This is an opportunity that countless people would kill for! Perhaps you should reconsider."

Even though she had already acknowledged Mistress Liu Hua as her birth father, she still wasn't used to calling him that.

"I also think this is a brilliant opportunity, but I have more important matters to attend to, so I can't afford to stay here for so long," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

Gu Qianxun heaved a faint sigh upon hearing this.

"In any case, given Mistress Liu Hua's personality, even if you're unwilling to become his disciple, I'm sure he'll still remove the Black Tribulation Centipede from your body once we return from the Great Ruins."

"I wouldn't count on it. Having said that, I think the Blood Plasma Wine that I'm brewing in Profound City should almost be ready," Han Li replied with a smile.

"I bet you're not going to bring out your Blood Plasma Wine until Mistress Liu Hua agrees to remove the Black Tribulation Centipede from your body, isn't that right?" Gu Qianxun asked with an amused smile.

"I wouldn't dare to do that," Han Li chuckled.

As the two of them were conversing with each other, five figures suddenly emerged from the Star Falcon Flying Boat, and they were led by the trio of Mistress Liu Hua, E Kuai, and Sha Xin.

Standing behind E Kuai and Sha Xin were Shi Chuankong and the mysterious woman in purple, respectively.

Han Li's expression instantly stiffened slightly at the sight of those two.

His gaze lingered momentarily on Shi Chuankong before he turned his attention to the woman in purple.

Her bamboo hat already had a black veil, and she also seemed to be wearing a veil over her face, making it impossible to make out her facial features, but her gorgeous figure was clearly highlighted by her dress.

The more Han Li looked at her, the more she reminded him of Violet Spirit.

"Fellow daoists, the Star Falcon Flying Boat is ready, so today is the day that we enter the Great Ruins. The spatial storm is much weaker in this canyon than elsewhere, but it's still not to be underestimated, so we'll still all have to work together and combine our efforts to power the Star Falcon Restriction on the boat," E Kuai declared.

His voice was as loud as the striking of a gong, and it reverberated deep within everyone's hearts.

After E Kuai's voice trailed off, Sha Xin continued, "We've had to endure many hardships on this journey thus far, and this is where all of our efforts come into fruition. I hope all of you can set aside your personal differences just a little longer to work together for one final collective effort."

In stark contrast with E Kuai's voice, Sha Xin's voice was extremely delicate and alluring, filling everyone with a sense of motivation.

All of the cultivators from the two cities were raring to go.

Mistress Liu Hua stepped forward as he declared, "I'm going to bestow upon all of you the method to power the Star Falcon Restriction. Once you board the boat, I expect all of you to pull your own weight."

Everyone began to listen carefully as Mistress Liu Hua delivered a detailed rundown of all of the information that had to be learned.

Even after everyone had declared that they remembered everything, Mistress Liu Hua still repeated everything a second time, just to make sure.

After all of the preparatory work was complete, E Kuai ordered, "Board the boat!"

The cultivators from the two cities immediately began boarding the Star Falcon Flying Boat.

At the very center of the flying boat was a tall ridge that divided the boat into two halves, and the sides of the interior of the boat were lined with seats that, upon each of which was engraved a circle of runes.

Han Li and the Profound City cultivators were instructed to sit down on the left side of the cabin by Mistress Liu Hua, while the Puppet City cultivators sat down on the right side, and E Kuai and the others remained at the front of the boat.

After everyone had taken their seats, E Kuai gave the order to set off, and Mistress Liu Hua made his way into a circular array at the front of the Star Falcon Flying Boat before sitting down in it with his legs crossed.

E Kuai and the others also followed suit, sitting down onto the circular arrays beside him, upon which the arrays beneath them immediately began to glow brightly, while a string of specks of starry light appeared along the ridge at the center of the boat.

The entire Star Falcon Flying Boat shuddered violently before slowly rising up into the air, and by the time it had risen to an altitude of over a thousand feet, Mistress Liu Hua ordered, "Activate the restriction!"

The cultivators from the two cities immediately sprang into action upon hearing this, and dozens of profound acupoints lit up over each of their bodies, while the circles of runes beneath them also began to glow brightly.

The runes on the boat also lit up one after another, extending from the belly of the boat all the way onto its two wings, making the entire flying boat resemble a white falcon that was spreading its wings to take flight.

Han Li could feel his own profound acupoints resonating with the restriction on the flying boat, and not only did he not feel like his power was being sucked out of his body, it was as if he were basking in a nourishing pool of starlight, and it was a very comfortable sensation.

Right at this moment, Mistress Liu Hua pressed his palms onto the deck of the flying boat several times in succession, and the two largest runes on the boat's wings glowed even brighter while emitting a buzzing sound.

Han Li looked up to discover that all of the stars in the sky were suddenly glowing brighter, and two incredibly thick pillars of white starlight descended out of the heavens before crashing down onto the wings of the Star Falcon Flying Boat, causing the entire boat to shudder violently.

All of the people on the boat hurriedly channeled more of their power into the flying boat upon seeing this.

Chapter 929: Tumultuous

"There's no need to be alarmed. The power of the flying boat alone is not enough to withstand the spatial storm, so only by drawing upon the power of the stars in the sky can we ensure safe passage," Mistress Liu Hua said in a calm manner, and everyone felt much more reassured upon hearing this.

Sure enough, after the initial jolt and a fall in altitude of several dozen feet, the Star Falcon Flying Boat returned to its original altitude in a stable fashion.

Immediately thereafter, bursts of starpower began to surge out of the countless runes engraved all over the entire flying boat, and they connected together with one another to form a white starlight barrier.

A few moments later, the wings on either side of the boat began to flap up and down, and the boat slowly advanced into the canyon.

Han Li could feel a glacial aura coming from his left, and a scorching sensation from his right, and began to focus his attention on observing his surroundings.

There was no sound to be heard aside from the sounds produced by the restriction on the ship, and everyone was silently focused on the task at hand.

No one, including Mistress Liu Hua, dared to proclaim that they would definitely be able to make it across the abyss safely.

As the flying boat entered the canyon, gusts of freezing blue winds swept forth from the left, slicing against the Star Falcon Flying Boat like a series of sharp, glacial knives.

However, the starlight barrier around the boat was very flexible, and even though indentations were appearing on its surface from the glacial winds, it remained resilient, displaying no signs of breaking.

On the other side of the canyon, scorching hot waves of heat were surging through the air, giving that half of the sky a fiery red complexion, but it was also unable to burn through the starlight barrier.

However, the starlight barrier was unable to keep out the freezing cold and the intense heat, so all of the people on the flying boat were feeling extremely uncomfortable.

After traveling onward for several thousand more kilometers, they were approaching the point in the canyon where the glacial blue winds and the scorching flames met, and the two temperature extremes were generating gusts of ferocious wind.

Even before the gusts of wind had reached the flying boat, the violent howling that they produced was already grating on everyone's eardrums.

Right at this moment, a particularly powerful gust of wind struck the flying boat head-on, and the boat shuddered violently before veering away to one side, crashing toward the wall of blue ice on the left.

The front and left side of the boat were crashing toward the mountain face in unison, and if a collision were to occur, then that side of the boat would be sure to suffer severe damage, perhaps even causing it to fall apart entirely.

Without the flying boat's protection, everyone would be exposed to the glacial winds and scorching flames, and the gusts of wind that they produced together would also sweep them straight into the spatial storm up above, leading to certain death.

Right as everyone was about to erupt into a panic, a figure suddenly rushed over to the left side of the flying boat, and it was none other than E Kuai.

He spread his fingers open on both hands, then thrust both palms toward the blue mountain face. Dense clusters of profound acupoints appeared over his hands and arms like stars in the night sky, releasing a burst of incredibly formidable power.

Han Li was also stunned by the sight of E Kuai's arms. There were over two hundred profound acupoints on his arms alone, and that was already more than what most of the cultivators on the boat possessed on their entire body.

It seemed that Chen Yang hadn't been exaggerating when he proclaimed that E Kuai had opened a total of more than a thousand profound acupoints.

All of the profound acupoints on E Kuai's arms and hands were glowing radiantly, and beams of bright light shot out of the palms of his hands and the tips of his fingers before fusing into the starlight barrier upon contact.

Waves of massive circular ripples immediately began to spread over the surface of the starlight barrier, following which pillars of white light that were as thick as wooden rafters emerged from the light barrier, extending toward the blue mountain face on the left.

A burst of loud rumbling rang out as the blue mountain face was shattered, causing a huge avalanche, and the twelve thick pillars of light acted as oars, forcibly restoring the enormous Star Falcon Flying Boat back to its original orientation.

The boat slowly began to return to its original trajectory, and everyone heaved a collective sigh of relief upon seeing this.

E Kuai withdrew his hands, and the pillars of white light surging out of the starlight barrier were also slowly withdrawn, while Han Li looked on with astonishment in his eyes.

It wasn't very difficult to release a tremendous amount of starpower to cause widespread damage, but it was extremely difficult to control one's own power as meticulously as E Kuai had just done.

Even though that crisis had been successfully averted, everyone was still very tense and on-edge, powering the Star Falcon Flying Boat with all their might to spur it onward.

Meanwhile, Mistress Liu Hua was constantly adjusting the direction of the flying boat, and he was becoming more and more skilled at the task, avoiding one whirlwind after another before finally arriving at the point where the hot and cold mountain faces met.

At this point, the wind outside had become almost unbearably loud, and the light barrier around the Star Falcon Flying Boat was also constantly warping and twisting from the tremendous wind pressure.

Han Li was sitting in the cabin with close to a hundred profound acupoints shining on his body, and he had also conjured up his True Extreme Film.

Most of the other Profound City cultivators had also revealed close to a hundred profound acupoints each, but this was not under instructions from E Kuai. Instead, it was because the temperatures were becoming more and more extreme as they advanced onward, and the starlight barrier could only shelter them to a certain extent.

Many of the Profound City cultivators on the boat were already developing signs of frostbite, and their lips had also become dry and cracked from the glacial winds.

In stark contrast, the Puppet City cultivators felt as if they had been sent down into the fiery pits of hell. Their skin had turned bright red, and the sweat pouring out of their pores didn't even have a chance to linger on their bodies before being evaporated into nothingness.

Their lips were also dried and cracked, except it was from the intense heat, rather than the cold.

Right at this moment, Mistress Liu Hua's voice suddenly rang out from the front of the boat.

"Attention, everyone! We are reaching the most critical point of our flight, so make sure to stabilize the flying boat with all your might."

Everyone immediately redoubled their focus upon hearing this.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the left side of the boat to discover that the depths of the canyon had already descended into complete chaos, with countless spatial rifts littered throughout the surrounding area. A gust of freezing wind was clashing against a wave of fire down below, sending gusts of fierce wind rising up into the spatial storm above.

Bursts of rumbling were ringing out incessantly, and the Star Falcon Flying Boat began trembling as it ventured into the ferocious winds up ahead.

Right at this moment, the front of the Star Falcon Flying Boat suddenly twisted to the side, and the entire boat abruptly accelerated as it was instantly wrenched into the storm.

The entire world instantly began spinning, and everyone was also thrown up into the air and out of the cabin.

Han Li hurriedly channeled his cultivation arts to plant himself firmly in his seat, while Mistress Liu Hua yelled, "Fortify the array! Things won't be as tumultuous once we reach the center of the storm!"

A string of loud thumps rang out incessantly on the flying boat and more and more profound acupoints lit up over the bodies of the Profound City cultivators, and the entire boat began glowing so brightly that the canyon was illuminated to be as bright as day.

Prior to this, it had felt as if the flying boat had been nourishing their bodies this entire time, and only now did everyone begin to feel their starpower being sucked out of their bodies to support the Star Falcon Restriction.

At the same time, the radiant stars in the sky also began to resonate with the flying boat from afar, and the two pillars of starlight descending from the heavens became brighter than ever. As a result, the starlight barrier around the entire boat became even denser, and specks of bright bright light also appeared over its surface, as if it were mirroring the starry night sky.

Simultaneously, the runes engraved onto the wings of the boat were also increasing in brightness, releasing two bursts of white light that formed a pair of massive starry wings.

With the emergence of those wings, the violently swaying Star Falcon Flying Boat was finally somewhat stabilized, and it plunged headfirst into the fierce winds ahead to reach the eye of the storm in one fell swoop.

The eye of the storm was massive, and it appeared to be quite tranquil inside, but in reality, it was also fraught with peril.

All of a sudden, a burst of tremendous suction force began acting upon the Star Falcon Flying Boat, causing it plummet rapidly downward.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he looked down to discover a chaotic scene several thousand feet below, where a burst of blue light had fused together with a vast expanse of crimson flames.

Beneath this swirling mass of fire and ice was a black vortex that resembled the eye of a giant demon, and that was the source of the immense suction force.

In the blink of an eye, the Star Falcon Flying Boat had already descended over a thousand feet.

A bone-chilling glacial aura rose from below alongside a burst of scorching heat, and everyone instantly felt as if they had been cast into a hellish storm of fire and ice.

Right at this moment, a delicate cry rang out from the front of the Star Falcon Flying Boat, immediately following which four golden puppets sprang out of the right side of the cabin before leaping straight down into the abyss below.

Four loud thumps rang out in unison, and the flying boat shuddered violently, following which the speed of its descent began to decrease, as if it were being supported by something from down below.

Han Li peered over the side of the boat to see one of the golden puppets at the tail end of the boat, supporting it on his shoulder. Around a dozen specks of white light had emerged over the puppet's body, embedded within each of which was a beast core.

On top of that, its legs had transformed into something that resembled a lotus flower platform, and bursts of starpower were surging out of it like flames, generating tremendous propulsion force that slowed the flying boat's descent.

Chapter 930: Crisis Averted

Right at this moment, a faint crack rang out, and Han Li could see that the shoulder of the golden puppet had already caved in significantly, indicating that it wasn't going to be able to last much longer.

Right at this moment, five pillars of white light erupted the night sky above the canyon from the front of the boat.

Countless rays of starlight instantly began to cascade down from the stars in the sky, connecting together with the starlight barrier around the flying boat to generate bursts of powerful upward tugging force.

The Star Falcon Flying Boat shuddered violently, following which it completely ceased in its descent, then began to slowly elevate again.

After the boat had been elevated by about two hundred to three hundred feet, the tugging force from the stars seemed to have finally been exhausted, and it was only just barely able to keep up with the suction force coming from the abyss below. With its altitude stabilized, the boat flapped its wings and began to slowly advance onward.

The four golden puppets beneath the boat seemed to have also been sapped of all of their strength, and the beast cores all over their bodies dimmed as they plunged straight down into the depths.

The two puppets on the left were instantly frozen solid after falling into the glacial winds, while the two on the red were melted into molten fluid by the crimson flames, following which all of them vanished into the black vortex below.

Thanks to the combined efforts of the golden puppets and the stars above, the Star Falcon Flying Boat was able to safely cross the eye of the storm to the other side.

Thanks to the prior experience, everyone did a much better job stabilizing the boat upon re-entry into the storm.

Even after the entire boat had entered the storm, there were no significant tremors or deviations, and all they had to do was make it through the storm to reach the glowing white continent on the other side.

However, the boat had only flown onward for a short distance when a burst of violent spatial fluctuations erupted up ahead.

Han Li looked up to discover that a fragmented spatial rift had been caught up in the storm, yet instead of dissipating, it was moving toward the left side of the flying boat.

Before he had a chance to raise the alarm, Mistress Liu Hua had also noticed this, and he hurriedly diverted the boat away to the right, but to compound their woes even further, a thunderous roar suddenly rang out, following which a burst of tremendous force crashed into the flying boat from behind.

The starlight barrier around the boat was almost shattered upon impact, while the boat itself also involuntarily accelerated forward, crashing toward the dense mass of spatial rifts up ahead.

Han Li sprang to his feet and grabbed tightly onto the side of the boat while reaching out with his other hand to support Gu Qianxun, who had been sent stumbling toward him.

He then turned around to discover a gargantuan dragon-like head that was covered in spikes, glowering at the flying boat from afar with a pair of pitch-black eyes.

Attached to the head was an incredibly powerful serpentine body that was covered in rhomboid scales. The body was thousands of feet in length, and it was extending out of the black vortex in the abyss.

Somehow, the creature seemed to be completely unaffected by the tremendous suction force released by the vortex, and it was swaying its body from side to side as it prepared to ram its head into the flying boat again.

In the next instant, the boat was dealt another heavy blow, and the starlight barrier around it almost completely fizzled out, while everyone was staring at the gargantuan creature behind the boat with horrified expressions.

Right at this moment, a loud voice rang out from the front of the boat.

"All of you, focus on guiding the boat, Fellow Daoist Sha Xin and I will take care of this imbecile!"

As soon as the voice trailed off, both E Kuai and Sha Xin vanished from the spot, then reappeared in unison behind the flying boat.

E Kuai clenched his fists tightly and adopted a peculiar fist stance as he swayed his body from side to side while swinging his arms through the air in a series of rather strange-looking gestures.

At the same time, the profound acupoints on his body lit up one after another, giving off a tremendous aura, and all of a sudden, his fist stance wasn't looking so comical anymore.

Even though E Kuai's movements were quite slow, his robes were billowing around him as if there were strong winds blowing through them.

Meanwhile, Sha Xin reached a hand into her own sleeve, then casually swept her sleeve through the air to release a streak of black light, which contained a fist-sized ball.

The ball was clicking incessantly as it flew through the air, as if there were countless gears rapidly revolving within it.

Before long, a series of cracks had appeared on the ball, and it transformed into a four-armed ape-like puppet that was close to a thousand feet tall.

As soon as the giant ape puppet appeared, it almost began to plummet out of the sky under the suction force from the vortex below.

However, the puppet then reached out with one hand, and it detached itself from its body at the wrist before flying through the air. The hand was still connected to its arm by a thick, black chain, which wrapped itself around one of the spikes on the gargantuan creature's head.

The ape puppet then tugged violently on the chain, sending its own enormous body flying up into the air, following which it came crashing down onto the creature's head with mountainous force.

At the same time, each of its other three hands was holding a pillar-like giant iron pestle, and it swung the three pestles down onto the dragon-like creature's head as well.

The creature let loose a thunderous roar as its body was forced down by the puppet's formidable blows.

At this point, countless profound acupoints had already lit up over E Kuai's body, and starlight was pouring out of the profound acupoints on his arm, forming a thin mist of starlight around him.

With all of the preparations complete, he focused all of his power into his fist before launching it forward, with the timing of his punch perfectly corresponding with the lowering of the dragon-like creature's head.

All of the starlight radiating from his fist converged toward a single spot before exploding with devastating power, shattering layers upon layers of space up ahead to forcibly create a black hole that encompassed the entirety of the creature's head.

After the starlight faded, the black hole also disappeared, having already claimed the creature's head. Its headless body was still writhing from side to side, while vast volumes of blood gushed out of the wound on its neck.

All of this had taken place within a span of less than twenty seconds, and in the meantime, the Star Falcon Flying Boat was already about to crash into the mass of spatial rifts up ahead.

Veins were bulging on Mistress Liu Hua's forehead as he pressed his hands tightly against the array on the deck of the boat, and he was tilting his body to the right with all his might, but despite his best efforts, the turn radius of the boat simply wasn't small enough for it to avoid the hazard up ahead.

The front of the boat was able to just barely avoid the mass of spatial rifts, but the side of the boat was not so fortunate.

The wing on the left side of the boat was the first to crash into the spatial rifts, and it was instantly torn to shreds. As a result, the giant boat was immediately tipped off balance and began tilting to the right.

"Qianxun!" Mistress Liu Hua called out in alarm as he sprang to his feet, abandoning the flying boat to rush to Gu Qianxun's aid, but it was already too late.

With the flying boat completely careening out of control, Han Li and Gu Qianxun were sent flying toward the cluster of spatial rifts without any time to react.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly let loose a loud roar, and a series of profound acupoints lit up over his right arm, releasing a layer of hazy starlight that was a little reminiscent of the cloud of misty starlight that E Kuai had created earlier.

Having said that, there was naturally still a vast disparity in their auras.

Even so, Han Li didn't hesitate in the slightest as he lashed out with his fist, and the starlight radiating from the profound acupoints on his arm and fist formed a huge white fist projection that crashed into the mass of spatial rifts with tremendous power.

The white fist projection instantly exploded upon contact with the spatial rifts, sending formidable shockwaves sweeping through the air in all directions, and as a result, the Star Falcon Flying Boat was pushed slightly further to the right.

Taking advantage of this opportunity, Han Li activated all of the profound acupoints on his legs and instantly rushed over to Gu Qianxun's side, then wound an arm around her slender waist before vanishing from the spot, only to reappear a moment later near the front of the boat.

Ultimately, the flying boat wasn't able to completely avoid the spatial rifts, and a string of loud cracks rang out as the midsection of the left side of the boat crumbled away like a piece of rotten wood.

However, it was only thanks to that punch from Han Li that the boat didn't crash straight into the mass of spatial rifts. Instead, it only grazed its way past the spatial rifts, and even though a part of the boat had been destroyed, the damage wasn't all that severe.

Mistress Liu Hua heaved a long sigh of relief upon seeing this, and at this point, E Kuai and Sha Xin had also returned.

"What was that thing just now?" Mistress Liu Hua asked.

"I've never seen a creature like that before, but it seems to be a scaled beast that's unique to this black abyss. It wasn't all that powerful, but it almost sent all of us to our deaths," E Kuai replied with a shake of his head.

"Thankfully, the crisis has been averted, and we're not that far away from the other side of the abyss," Sha Xin said, but right as her voice trailed off, a chorus of beastly roars suddenly rang out across the surrounding area as one gargantuan head after another emerged, surrounding the Star Falcon Flying Boat from all directions.

All of the heads were completely identical to that of the creature that E Kuai and Sha Xin had just slain!

Chapter 931: Sudden Calamity

"We've just killed one, and now there's eight! Is there no end to them?"

"All of them must have a death wish!"

"With City Lord E and City Lord Sha on our side, it doesn't matter how many of them come after us!"

"Hold on, this thing looks a little familiar..."

All of the people on the flying boat erupted into chatter at the sight of the eight giant heads.

However, given how easily E Kuai and Sha Xin had dealt with that earlier scaled beast, there wasn't much panic, and some of the cultivators on the boat were looking to E Kuai for instructions.

However, neither E Kuai nor Sha Xin were saying anything, and it didn't seem like they intended to take any action, either.

At the same time, the four subsidiary city lords of Profound City and Zhuo Ge and the others were also looking on with grim expressions, and a sense of foreboding immediately welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this.

Right at this moment a thunderous roar rang out as another head emerged from behind the flying boat.

However, this head was far smaller than the other eight, and there was a layer of white coloration over its surface, as if it had only recently sprouted. On top of that, there was also a clear dark red mark on its neck.

This was the very same head that E Kuai had just decapitated!

"Those aren't individual creatures, it's a Nine-headed Wyrm!" E Kuai exclaimed, and Han Li's expression instantly changed slightly upon seeing this.

He had heard of this name before, but most mentions were from unsubstantiated legends, and he had never actually seen the creature before.

It was said that his creature had a gargantuan, elephant-like body, with necks that were long as pythons, as well as nine heads and one mouth. It was capable of devouring all things, and it was extremely aggressive. The only way to kill it was to decapitate all nine of its heads at once. Otherwise, any lost heads would simply be regrown indefinitely.

As for this "one mouth", that didn't mean that all nine of its heads shared a single mouth. Instead, that was referring to an enormous, all-devouring mouth on its back, which was rather similar to Xiao Bai's abilities.

Right at this moment, the Nine-headed Wyrm raised all nine of its heads at once before ramming them against the Star Falcon Flying Boat from all directions.

Its nine gargantuan heads filled the entire sky, and even the starlight shining down from above was kept out.

The Star Falcon Flying Boat shuddered as the starlight barrier around it began to thin out even further, and everyone was looking up at the sky with despair in their eyes.

E Kuai and Sha Xin naturally weren't just going to resign themselves to their fates, and they exchanged a glance with each other, then launched themselves up from the flying boat in unison.

The surrounding space was trembling violently as if it were on the verge of shattering.

The black veil on Sha Xin's face was flapping audibly in the ferocious wind, revealing her stunningly beautiful features, but at this moment, there was a grim look on her face as she swept both hands through the air to release a pair of balls.

One of them released radiant white light and transformed into a giant figure that was over a thousand feet tall amid a burst of formidable starpower fluctuations.

The giant figure was wearing a regal purplish-golden crown and a suit of rainbow scaled armor. Its entire body was giving off a metallic gleam, as if it were forged out of metal, and as soon as the transformation was complete, it reached out with one hand, upon which the other ball transformed into a giant, silver umbrella before falling into its grasp.

Even from the flying boat, Han Li could sense the tremendous aura of the armorclad giant, and he was stunned to discover that its aura wasn't inferior in the slightest compared with E Kuai's.

Sha Xin twisted around in mid-air before flicking her fingers through the air in rapid succession, and the armorclad giant held the shaft of the umbrella in one hand before raising it upward.

The umbrella released a burst of radiant white light that formed an enormous light barrier up above.

The surface of the light barrier was riddled with countless specks of starlight, as if it were reflecting the starry night sky.

All of the stars on the umbrella seemed to be connected to the stars in the sky, and they were able to draw upon boundless starpower from the heavens.

A string of devastating blows were dealt upon the light barrier by the Nine-headed Wyrm's heads, causing the light barrier to tremble violently, while the star designs on its surface dissipated one after another.

The armorclad giant began to tremble under the tremendous pressure, but it was still supporting the umbrella with all its might.

"Allow me, Fellow Daoist Sha Xin!" E Kuai yelled as all of his profound acupoints lit up, and a layer of hazy starlight appeared over his body as he threw a punch at the bottom of the umbrella's shaft.

Right at this moment, the body of the Nine-headed Wyrm began to rise up from the black vortex down below.

Its back was so incredibly massive that it filled up virtually the entire eye of the storm, and it was covered in scales, with a thin mark running down its center.

Mistress Liu Hua looked down with a grim expression, while Gu Qianxun asked with tightly furrowed brows, "What do we do, Father?"

"No matter what happens, do not leave my side!" Mistress Liu Hua instructed in a serious manner.

Before Gu Qianxun had a chance to reply, an earth-shattering roar rang out from down below.

It was like the sound of a volcanic eruption, instantly striking everyone with a rush of dizziness.

Han Li was able to regain his mental faculties after channeling the Spirit Refinement Technique, but as he looked around, he discovered that everyone aside from Mistress Liu Hua and himself were swaying in an unsteady fashion.

Mistress Liu Hua pressed a hand down onto Gu Qianxun's shoulder to help her stabilize her soul, and a surprised look appeared in his eyes at the sight of Han Li as he praised, "The stability of your soul is quite remarkable!"

"I don't think this is the time to be discussing something like this, Senior Liu Hua," Han Li replied as he cast his gaze toward the front of the boat, where Shi Chuankong and the woman in purple had both fallen to one knee, and they were only faring slightly better than everyone else.

Right as he was about to approach them, he suddenly felt the ground give way beneath his feet, causing him to plummet involuntarily out of the sky.

Without anyone to man the Star Falcon Flying Boat, it was rapidly falling out of the air.

A gargantuan mouth had already opened up on the back of the Nine-headed Wyrm down below, and black light was churning incessantly within it.

An urgent look appeared on Han Li's face as all of the profound acupoints on his legs lit up, and he was able to stomp down onto the space below to send himself flying up several feet, but it was all in futility as he was immediately sucked back down again.

Cries of panic were ringing out from all directions as everyone made futile attempts to escape.

E Kuai and Sha Xin had already noticed what was happening down below, but it was too late for them to do anything.

A resounding boom rang out as the tail end of the Star Falcon Flying Boat fell into the giant mouth on the back of the Nine-headed Wyrm, and it was instantly destroyed by the strange power inside.

Cries of despair rang out as Han Li looked on with tightly furrowed brows, but in this moment, he was extremely calm.

He rummaged around in the chest of his robe for a moment before pulling out the leaf-shaped jade pendant given to him by Shi Pokong, then began scouring the surrounding area for Shi Chuankong and the woman in purple.

As long as he had the jade pendant, he would be able to take the two of them back with him to the Devil Realm.

After a quick search, he failed to spot Shi Chuankong, but he did see Daoist Xie about a thousand feet away.

"Come over here, Brother Xie," he hurriedly called out through voice transmission.

Right at this moment, he spotted the purple-robed woman from Puppet City, who wasn't all that far away, so he hurriedly channeled his Wingform Ascension Arts to rush toward her.

As Han Li approached the woman, he couldn't help but wonder if she actually was Violet Spirit.

Right as he was about to grab onto her arm, Mistress Liu Hua's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"I'm going to set off an explosion that'll create some spatial rifts, go into the largest one. Make sure you don't die!"

Han Li immediately turned around to discover Mistress Liu Hua standing outside the giant mouth of the Nine-headed Wyrm roughly thousand feet away, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a palm-sized white disc, which fell into the center of the mouth before exploding violently.

A string of incredibly violent explosions rang out as the space within the Nine-headed Wyrm's mouth shattered like a mirror, creating massive spatial rifts that extended outward in all directions.

Bursts of formidable suction force erupted out of these newly opened spatial rifts, and many of the cultivators of the two cities were sucked in before they even had a chance to react.

Some were fortunate enough to have entered a spatial rift with their bodies intact, while others were not so fortunate and were instantly torn to shreds.

Han Li immediately sprang forward to make a grab for the purple-robed woman, but a spatial rift just so happened to have appeared between them, and Han Li was sucked in before he had a chance to dodge.

Upon entering the spatial rift, Han Li arrived in a pitch-black space, and he could feel immense tearing force sweeping at him from all directions, while the entire world spun around him.

All of the lights and sounds instantly faded away, and he was struck by a splitting headache, while his consciousness also began to blur.

In his final moments of consciousness, his thoughts continued to linger on the purple-robed woman, and even though there was a veil over her face, he was convinced that she was Violet Spirit.

Chapter 932: Initial Foray Into the Great Ruins

Han Li's ears were buzzing erratically, and he felt as if there were countless strange voices ringing out in his head. The entire world was spinning around him as if he were drunk, and not only had he been stripped of all five of his senses, he wasn't even able to formulate any thoughts.

After what seemed like an eternity, his body finally drew to a halt, then came crashing down heavily down onto the cold, hard ground in a very painful landing.

Thankfully, given his immense physical constitution, he didn't suffer any injuries, and the impact allowed him to recover his senses and his consciousness.

He looked around in a daze to discover a dim, yellow landscape, and the ground was riddled with countless yellowish-black rocks of different sizes. There was nothing but barren plains stretching as far as the eyes could see in all directions, and it appeared that he had landed on a boundless desert.

The sky up above was also a strange, yellowish-brown color, as if there was a dense layer of yellow clouds overhead, and occasionally, what appeared to be flashes of white lightning could be seen peeking through the clouds.

There was a churning vortex within the yellow clouds, and it was rapidly fading away. That seemed to have been what he had just fallen out of.

Han Li slowly clambered to his feet before inspecting his surroundings to discover that there was no else in the entire area aside from himself.

Are these the Great Ruins? It doesn't seem much different from outside. I wonder where everyone else is.

Right as he was about to depart, a hint of surprise suddenly appeared on his face, and he began inspecting the surrounding space again.

There were some rather pronounced energy fluctuations in the air, these energy fluctuations were different from both spiritual qi and devilish qi, but it was very similar to starpower.

Perhaps it was due to the nourishment of this starpower, but some white moss-like plant life could be seen growing between the rocks on the ground, so the area wasn't as barren as it had appeared at first glance.

A hint of curiosity flashed through Han Li's eyes, and a thought suddenly occurred to him as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

All of the nearby starpower instantly converged toward him before surging into his body, and it was quite a large volume of starpower, creating the same effect as cultivating while refining beast cores.

A hint of elation appeared on Han Li's face upon sensing this, and he was even more convinced that he was in the Great Ruins. Only in a secret area like the Great Ruins could there be such abundant starpower, and only in an environment like this could treasures like Heavenly Qilin Crystals and Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds arise naturally.

Even though he wasn't injured, he was feeling a little feeble, and there didn't appear to be any hazards present in the area, so instead of setting off right away, he sat down with his legs crossed to absorb starpower and rest.

Close to half a day flew by in a flash, and by the time he reopened his eyes, he had made a full recovery.

On top of that, a profound acupoint that he had already been chipping away at for a long time was beginning to display signs of opening.

The starpower in this place seemed to be particularly effective for opening new profound acupoints, and he could sense that it was only a matter of time before this one was completely opened.

However, he didn't intend to continue cultivating here, and after looking around briefly, his gaze quickly settled on a certain direction to his right.

The entire surrounding area appeared to be completely the same, but he could see a shadow or two flashing past in that direction. However, they were too far away for him to see them clearly.

The spatial pressure in the Great Ruins was even more overbearing than that of the Extreme Bipolar Mountain Range, and his spiritual sensory range was restricted to only several kilometers, which was even worse than his eyesight.

He didn't know what was in that direction, but at the very least, it appeared to be something different.

With that in mind, he promptly set off, and it didn't take long before the shadows up ahead began to gradually come into focus.

As it turned out, it was a cluster of mountains that were each hundreds of feet tall, and they were connected together to form a winding mountain range that stretched as far as the eyes could see.

These mountains were black and giving off a faint sheen, indicating that they were no ordinary mountains, and the ground had also gradually transitioned from desert to hard rock.

There was much more of the white moss-like plants growing here, making the environment appear less monotonous.

Han Li arrived in front of the black mountain range, then drew to a halt, and instead of immediately entering the mountain range, he released his spiritual sense to scour the nearby area.

Everything in the Great Ruins was completely unknown to him, so he didn't dare to make any reckless moves.

Only after verifying that there were no detectable hazards in the mountain range up ahead did he continue onward, and he walked for half a day without encountering any danger.

However, the nearby mountains were becoming taller and taller, reaching thousands of feet in height, and the gaps between the mountains were also becoming wider and wider.

After walking onward for a while longer, an intrigued look suddenly appeared in Han Li's eyes as he sped up a little, making his way over to a particularly tall mountain.

This mountain stretched all the way up into the clouds like a heavenly black pillar, and its peak was concealed within the clouds, making it impossible to see the summit.

At the foot of the mountain was a cluster of gray palaces that stretched as far as the eyes could see, but most of them had already collapsed.

Even so, one could get an idea of just how majestic and stunning these palaces would've been from the intricate craftsmanship present in the ruins.

After briefly examining the cluster of palaces, Han Li channeled his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique to conceal his own aura, then carefully stepped inside while releasing his spiritual sense to monitor his surroundings.

After advancing onward for a while, he suddenly raised an eyebrow, then ducked behind a long palace wall before carefully making his way to the end of the wall and peeking forward.

The sound of heavy footsteps rang out up ahead as a yellow puppet that was several dozen feet tall slowly trudged along while occasionally turning its head from side to side, seemingly patrolling the area.

The puppet resembled a giant gibbon, and it was clad in a suit of heavy armor, most of which was missing. The body of the puppet beneath the suit of armor was also riddled with signs of decay, and it was holding a saber that was in a state of disrepair, seemingly having already been patrolling this area for countless years.

Despite the signs of erosion displayed by its armor and saber, they were still giving off a faint, white gleam and traces of starpower fluctuations.

Are those star artifacts?

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li sprang out of his hiding spot and withdrew his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique as he pounced at the giant ape puppet from behind.

The puppet immediately swung around and let loose a low roar while swinging its saber at Han Li's head, but before its attack had a chance to land, its head was decapitated by a flash of white light, and its headless body fell completely still before crashing to the ground.

Han Li drifted down from mid-air before landing beside the puppet.

The fact that the puppet was still able to detect Han Li's attack and react indicated that its powers would've been very formidable during its heyday.

Han Li picked up the puppet's saber to discover that it had been crafted out of a glowing white material, and even though there was severe erosion on display, some faintly flashing runes could still be made out on the blade, and these runes were very similar to the star runes that Mistress Liu Hua had taught him to inscribe.

Aren't Mistress Liu Hua's starpower restrictions supposed to be original creations? Could this be a coincidence?

Han LI then turned his gaze to the suit of armor worn by the puppet, and he quickly caught sight of another star rune, one that was completely identical to one of the star runes taught to him by Mistress Liu Hua, even down to the finest of details.

Han Li couldn't help but be amused upon seeing this. This puppet had clearly existed for far longer than Mistress Liu Hua's star runes had been around, so it seemed that Mistress Liu Hua's star runes weren't an original creation of his own, after all.

Even though the saber was still giving off faint starpower fluctuations, it was already completely unusable, so Han Li tossed it aside before continuing onward, and it didn't take long before he had ventured deep into the cluster of palaces.

The palaces here were relatively more well preserved, but unfortunately, there were no precious treasures to be found, and it seemed that this place had already been completely looted.

After an extensive search, Han Li was only able to find a few pieces of ordinary ore, and he was attacked by many puppets along the way.

He tried to engage with the puppets as little as possible, running away where he could and dismantling the ones that he couldn't avoid. All of the puppets were severely eroded, so they were quite easy to deal with.

After advancing onward for a while longer, Han Li suddenly drew to a halt.

The field of view up ahead had suddenly broadened significantly, and a massive gray structure had appeared up ahead. It appeared to be an altar, and it was surrounded by many other structures like a moon among stars.

The altar had been constructed using a type of crude and massive gray stone blocks that appeared extremely resilient, and in contrast with many of the nearby collapsed structures, the altar was almost perfectly intact.

The doors of the altar were wide open, and its interior was shrouded in darkness, restricting visibility to only several dozen feet. Its entrance resembled a massive mouth capable of devouring all those that entered.

Star runes could be seen etched onto the walls inside the altar, forming a restriction that kept out all spiritual sense.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this.

Given how well-preserved this altar and the restrictions inside were, there surely had to be some valuable things inside.

After carefully scouring the surrounding area with his spiritual sense, he failed to detect anything amiss, and he made his way to the entrance of the altar.

Gusts of cold wind blew out of the entrance, and even though they weren't very strong, they struck him with a bone-chilling sensation as they swept over his body.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon sensing this, but he didn't back down as he stepped into the altar.

Chapter 933: Destined for Conflict

In the instant that Han Li set foot into the altar, a resounding explosion rang out as a massive hole was blown into the ground beneath his feet.

Countless shattered rocks screeched through the air as they converged toward him, and at the same time, a sharp blade shot out of the hole, sweeping rapidly toward his feet.

Despite the abrupt nature of this turn of events, Han Li reacted extremely quickly, drifting back as soon as the ground exploded beneath him to evade the shattered rocks, and the blade that was sweeping toward him didn't even manage to graze his robes.

In the next instant, a black shadow shot out of the hole, revealing itself to be a black ape that was around ten feet tall.

The ape was clad in a suit of bright, silver armor that also appeared to be a star artifact, but unfortunately, most of it was already ruined, and it was wielding a white scimitar that was around seven feet in length.

Is this a scaled beast? No, it's another puppet.

The ape's entire body was covered in black fur, and not only was there a cold gleam in its eyes, there was also viscous saliva dripping down from its fangs, making it no different in appearance from an actual living creature, but Han Li was still able to instantly identify it as a puppet.

The ape gave him a similar feeling to back when he first encountered Daoist Xie.

Han Li's gaze fell upon the white scimitar, and he discovered that it was displaying no signs of decay at all, and the star designs on its surface were still flashing incessantly while giving off bursts of formidable saber qi that caused the surrounding air to tremble incessantly.

Before Han Li had a chance to take a closer look, the black ape launched itself at him, and at the same time, the star designs on its white scimitar lit up, releasing a saber projection that was several dozen feet in length that came sweeping directly at Han Li's neck.

Han Li paid no heed to the oncoming attack as he began swaying from side to side, conjuring up four or five identical afterimages that sprang at the black ape from different directions.

The ape puppet let loose a low roar as it swept its scimitar through the air in a circle, aiming to cut down all of the oncoming Han Lis, only for all of them to instantly vanish upon making contact with its scimitar projection.

The black ape was momentarily rooted to the spot upon seeing this, and right at this moment, Han Li appeared before it in a wraith-like manner, then chopped down onto its wrist like lightning with his left hand, severing its hand at the wrist like a hot knife through butter.

The black ape let loose an agonized howl before lashing out with its other arm, throwing a punch at Han Li's head.

However, Han Li was far faster, and he grabbed onto the white scimitar with one hand, then slashed it through the air to slice the black ape's body into two from head to toe before its fist even had a chance to reach him.

The two halves of its body tumbled to the ground and spasmed momentarily before falling still.

Silver liquid that resembled blood poured out of the black ape's body, and on top of that, it had a full set of organs, making it appear no different from an actual living creature. However, these organs were crafted out of some type of crimson jade material, presenting an intriguing sight to behold.

Han Li took a glance at the two halves of the black ape's body, then turned his gaze to the white scimitar in his hand with an elated look in his eyes.

He channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts as he tightened his grip slightly around the hilt of the scimitar, and a bright saber projection instantly emerged over its blade, causing the nearby space to tremble and buzz incessantly.

As he swept the scimitar through the air, a series of saber projections instantly began to revolve around him like a nest of white spirit snakes.

The saber projections swept over the nearby walls, easily leaving deep marks onto theirs surfaces as if they were made from tofu.

However, a disappointed look quickly flashed through Han Li's eyes.

Even though this scimitar appeared to be quite powerful, it wasn't actually a star artifact, and it couldn't enhance one's physical prowess like a true star artifact could, so it could only be considered a pseudo-star artifact.

Even so, this was still a very valuable weapon under the current circumstances.

Han Li strapped the scimitar to his back, then concealed his aura once again and continued onward.

Beyond the entrance of the altar was a long passageway, and the walls on either side were constructed from gray stone bricks that were giving off a cold aura.

The passageway was quite wide at thirty to forty feet, but it was only around twenty to thirty feet tall, and for some reason, it was extremely dim here, restricting visibility to only less than two hundred feet, thereby striking one with a sense of tension and unease.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he continued onward, but he was walking along extremely carefully, constantly preparing for another puppet or something else to jump out of the walls or the ground below to attack him.

Thankfully, there were no further attacks, and after a long and meticulous walk, an exit that was giving off a faint white glow appeared up ahead.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly as he immediately sped up and made his way into the exit, upon which he arrived in a square hall.

The hall was several thousand feet in area, with a series of glowing white stones embedded onto the ceiling to brightly illuminate the entire area, which was riddled with a series of stone statues of different sizes.

These statues depicted figures in all types of different postures with a wide range of expressions on their faces, and all of them were extremely lifelike, presenting a rather unsettling sight to behold.

Right at this moment, a speck of white light appeared in Han Li's field of view, and it was rapidly expanding at an extraordinary speed. It was as if a star were plummeting from the heavens toward his face with unstoppable might.

An alarmed look instantly appeared on Han Li's face as he rushed back in retreat while drawing the scimitar from his back, raising it in front of his head to just barely parry the oncoming burst of white light.

A resounding boom rang out as the burst of white light clashed against the blade of the scimitar.

Han Li's scimitar-wielding arm trembled violently as he was sent flying back even faster, and he stumbled back close to twenty steps before finally managing to steady himself.

The burst of white light had also been repelled, and it was flying back end over end through the air.

Only then was Han Li able to catch a clear glimpse of it, and he discovered that it was a thin white sword that resembled a spirit snake. The specks of starlight on its surface indicated that it was a star artifact of a high caliber.

Immediately thereafter, a figure emerged from behind one of the stone statues to catch the sword, and it was none other than Feng Wuchen.

"I wanted to grant you a swift and painless death by punching a hole straight through your head, but it looks like you're going to have to suffer now," Feng Wuchen harrumphed coldly with undisguised killing intent in his eyes.

"It seems like we were destined to clash, Feng Wuchen," Han Li said as his eyes narrowed slightly.

That attack was far more formidable than the attacks that Feng Wuchen had displayed during their previous battle, so it appeared that he had stumbled upon some type of opportunity in the Great Ruins.

"Indeed! There were too many people in the Asura Arena, so I didn't go all out, and you managed to defeat me thanks to my complacency. Now that there's no one else around, I'm going to make you wish you had never been born!" Feng Wuchen declared with a vicious and confident gleam in his eyes.

"We've had our differences in the past, but it's nothing personal. Right now, we should be uniting against the cultivators of Puppet City instead of fighting among ourselves," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Are you begging for mercy now? It's too late! You humiliated me in front of everyone in the Asura Arena, so no matter how much you beg, you're not going to leave this place alive!" Feng Wuchen roared as a look of intense resentment appeared in his eyes, and second identical sword appeared in his other hand.

"So you insist on fighting me here then," Han Li sighed.

A cold sneer appeared on Feng Wuchen's face, and he offered no response as he sprang forward, instantly covering a distance of several hundred to appear in front of Han Li in the blink of an eye.

The two swords in his hands had been raised, and both of them were aimed at Han Li's chest.

The speed that Feng Wuchen was displaying here was almost twice as fast as what he had shown during the arena battle, and Han Li remained rooted to the spot, seemingly having completely failed to react.

Feng Wuchen had been feeling a little uneasy, but he instantly felt much more assured upon seeing this, and he cast his gaze toward Han Li's face, hoping to see the panic and horror in his eyes during his dying moments.

However, he was only greeted by the sight of a pair of eyes that were calm to the extreme.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Feng Wuchen's heart upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to do anything, the swords in his hands had already been knocked aside by a burst of tremendous force that almost wrenched them out of his grasp altogether.

A stunned look appeared on Feng Wuchen's face as he darted back as a blurry shadow, instantly retreating to over a thousand feet away.

"I failed to kill you last time, but it looks like I've been given a second chance to finish the job here," Han Li said in a cold voice, immediately following which all 237 of the profound acupoints on his body lit up one after another in rapid succession.

A loud explosion rang out in the air around Han Li as an unimaginably formidable aura erupted out of his body before sweeping forth in all directions.

The entire hall trembled violently, as did all of the stone statues, and an incredulous look appeared on Feng Wuchen's face as he exclaimed, "Impossible! How could you have opened so many profound acupoints?!"

Chapter 934: Brother Against Brother

In the face of the power that Han Li had suddenly displayed, Feng Wuchen was momentarily rooted to the spot, immediately following which he turned and fled deeper into the hall, where there was an entrance clearly leading to somewhere else.

Han Li immediately set off in pursuit, vanishing from the spot in the blink of an eye as the ground exploded beneath his feet, sending countless loose rocks flying in all directions.

Feng Wuchen had only fled to less than two hundred feet away when a blurry white shadow caught up to him like lightning, reaching him in a flash.

An arm that was riddled with radiant profound acupoints then came swinging at him from behind with its fist clenched, and large sections of the nearby space became twisted and warped in the face of the fist's tremendous power.

Feng Wuchen felt bursts of immense spatial pressure converging toward him from all directions, causing him to slow down drastically.

He knew that he wouldn't be able to get away, and a desperate look appeared in his eyes as he let loose a wild roar and swung around to face Han Li, then crossed his two swords above his head before injecting all of his power into them.

Radiant starlight erupted out of the pair of swords as close to twenty star acupoints emerged on their blades, forming a pair of massive starry swords that were each several dozen feet in size to oppose Han Li's almighty punch.

Han Li's fist struck the pair of swords, and a loud crack rang out as the giant starry swords instantly shattered into countless specks of starlight, while the two swords themselves were also destroyed.

Feng Wuchen's body was like a wooden pillar that was smashed into the ground by Han Li's fist, instantly burying him up to his knees.

Han Li's fist then continued onward without pause en route to Feng Wuchen's head, and with the lower half of his legs embedded into the ground, it was impossible for him to take any evasive measures.

Hence, he could only look on helplessly as a wave of dazzling white light washed over his body from Han Li's fist, tearing him to pieces just like his two shattered swords.

Only after Feng Wuchen's body had been completely obliterated did Han Li withdraw his fist with a calm expression.

Even if Feng Wuchen had stumbled upon some type of opportunity in the Great Ruins, there was no way that he could've enhanced his powers to a sufficient degree to pose a threat in such a short time. He had no intention of killing Feng Wuchen, but the latter insisted on being killed, so he had no one else to blame.

Han Li was just about to depart when an intrigued look suddenly appeared in his eyes, and he turned to the spot where Feng Wuchen had been standing just a moment ago, then extended his hand into the hole in the ground before pulling out a pair of white boots.

The boots seemed to have been made from some type of special beast hide that was soft, yet extremely resilient, and there were a series of star runes and a crescent moon design etched onto each of the boots.

It was clear that these were no ordinary boots, and Han Li immediately took off his own shoes before putting them on, then took a step forward.

As soon as he did so, he immediately vanished from the spot, only to reappear over a thousand feet away.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, and he looked down to discover that a total of sixty-four star acupoints had appeared on the boots, glowing just as radiantly as his profound acupoints.

An ecstatic look appeared on his face, and he began whizzing around the hall in a wraith-like fashion, filling the entire hall with his afterimages.

In the next instant, all of the afterimages abruptly disappeared, leaving Han Li to stand alone at the center of the hall with an elated look on his face.

These boots were a star artifact that could both enhance his physical prowess and his speed. Speed was his forte to begin with, and with the assistance of these boots, his speed was elevated by over 50%.

On top of that, this was before he had even begun refining the boots. Once he completed the refinement process, their enhancement effect would only improve even further.

These boots were definitely a star artifact of a superior caliber to his Star Shield, and it was no wonder that Feng Wuchen had been so confident after obtaining them. Unfortunately for him, even these boots weren't enough to bridge the power gap between him and Han Li.

The more Han Li looked at the boots, the fonder of them he became.

He took a glance at the crescent moon insignias on the boots, then murmured to himself, "I'll call you Star Moon Boots."

After putting on the Star Moon Boots, Han Li's speed was greatly enhanced even without channeling his Wingform Ascension Arts, and even though they didn't allow him to fly, they were certainly taking him from one place to another far faster than before.

Han Li continued deeper into the altar through a passageway at the back of the hall, and the path ahead suddenly began to slope downward.

He continued down the passageway, and after traveling for around fifteen minutes, he was greeted by the sight of an even larger white exit. After passing through the exit, he arrived in front of a massive underground plaza that was riddled with buildings, stretching as far as the eyes could see.

It was quite a surprise to Han Li that there was such a massive area beneath the altar, and he took a moment to compose himself, then began to make his way through the clusters of buildings.

After traveling for some time, the buildings on the plaza gradually became denser and denser, and there was no lack of intricately constructed palaces among them.

Han Li checked through these buildings one by one, but didn't find any star artifacts or treasures inside. However, he did encounter some puppets that were still intact, and he was attacked by such puppets on several occasions, but he was able to deal with them easily.

After searching for a while, he lost interest and began to accelerate onward.

Upon arriving above a circular, black stone palace, he suddenly raised an eyebrow, then gently descended onto the palace.

Immediately thereafter, he descended onto the ground and began rushing along the stone slab path toward a seven-story stone pagoda.

The doors of the pagoda had already been destroyed, and Han Li entered the building without any hesitation. From there, he quickly made his way onto the top floor before casting his gaze into the distance through a window to his left.

At this moment, there were four figures flashing back and forth on a white stone plaza over ten thousand feet away, and they seemed to be locked in a battle.

They were all moving quite quickly, so Han Li initially wasn't able to catch a clear glimpse of them from afar. All he could tell was that three of them were dressed in Puppet City attire, while the final figure was clad in a suit of white bone armor and looked slightly familiar.

A resounding boom rang out as the armorclad man was sent flying by a collective blow from the three Puppet City cultivators, and he crashed violently into a black wall that was over a hundred feet tall.

The wall immediately exploded into pieces, sending loose rocks flying in all directions, while the armorclad man fell to the ground. Now that he had come to a rest, Han Li was finally able to catch a clear glimpse of his features, and he was stunned to discover that it was none other than Shi Chuankong!

Right as he was planning to set off for the white stone plaza himself, one of the three Puppet City cultivators opened their mouth to speak.

"I never thought I'd run into you in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, Chuankong. You delivered yourself right to my doorstep, so you can't blame me..."

The figure removed the black veil over their face as they spoke, revealing themselves to be Shi Zhanfeng.

This was certainly very much an unexpected sight of Han Li, and only then did he recall that he had previously spotted three figures among the Puppet City cultivators that he had felt to be a little strange.

However, he didn't know why Shi Zhanfeng had appeared in the Scalptia Spatial Domain. Judging from what he had just said, he didn't seem to have come here specifically to hunt down Shi Chuankong, so what exactly was his objective?

"Cut the chit-chat! If you want to kill me, then come and get me!" Shi Chuankong said in a cold voice as he rose to his feet.

At this point, his suit of armor was already broken in many places, indicating that the battle had clearly already been unfolding for a while prior to Han Li's arrival, and it was clear that he was being outmatched by his three opponents.

"Still as cocky as ever, eh?" Shi Zhanfeng chuckled coldly, then swept a sleeve through the air, and other two figures with him also removed their Puppet City attire to reveal their true appearance.

One of them was a tall and broad man clad in a suit of black devilish armor, and it was none other than Du Yuan.

Du Yuan was the one that Shi Zhanfeng had entrusted to investigate the Scalptia Spatial Domain, and the fact that he was still by Shi Zhanfeng's side clearly indicated that he was a very trusted subordinate.

The other figure was a petite and extremely beautiful woman whose looks weren't inferior in the slightest compared with the twin sisters that had been sent to kill Shi Chuankong in the past, and she was clearly also one of Shi Zhanfeng's close subordinates.

The two of them rushed forward in unison with starpower surging out of their bodies, and each of them had exactly 156 profound acupoints.

The woman was small, but extremely fast, and even though she and Du Yuan had sprung into action at the same time, she was able to reach Shi Chuankong several seconds ahead of him, following which a bone whip shot out of her sleeve before pouncing at Shi Chuankong's glabella like a spirit snake.

Shi Chuankong let loose a loud roar as he retaliated with his bone saber, and dozens of star acupoints lit up over its blade, forming a radiant, white saber projection that swept through the air with tremendous power.

The bone whip was longer and slightly faster than his bone saber, so it should've been able to reach him before his blade could strike the woman, but thanks to the additional length contributed by the saber projection, the blade of the saber was able to reach the woman's chest before her whip could strike him.

The woman's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and with a flick of her wrist, the bone whip in her hand swung back to wrap itself around the blade of Shi Chuankong's saber, locking it into place.

At the same time, Du Yuan also arrived on the scene, and he threw a punch at Shi Chuankong's ribs from the right.

Shi Chuankong tugged back violently on his saber upon seeing this, using the bottom of its hilt to meet Du Yuan's fist.

A resounding boom rang out as Du Yuan's fist struck the hilt of the saber, sending violent shockwaves erupting in all directions, and the saber was almost wrenched out of Shi Chuankong's grasp.

He immediately let loose a loud roar, and over 160 profound acupoints lit up over his body, and he was releasing an aura superior to that of his two assailants.

Chapter 935: The Truth?

"You think you can take on all three of us with your pitiful powers? What a joke?" Shi Zhanfeng scoffed.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he launched himself forward, raising a hand as he did so before swinging it down in a chopping motion upon Shi Chuankong's head.

A string of profound acupoints lit up over his arm, and it was as if his hand had truly been transformed into a radiant white blade that was giving off formidable energy fluctuations.

Shi Chuankong seemed to have detected the threat posed by the attack, and he was desperately trying to free his saber to defend himself, but he was unable to do so with both Du Yuan and the woman restricting his movements.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he was just about to rush out of the pagoda when a burst of black light suddenly appeared in front of Shi Chuankong's chest, following which a pendant-like object slipped down before shattering into pieces.

Immediately thereafter, a vortex of black erupted out of the pendant's shattered fragments, and an ape-like scaled beast with countless spikes over its body rushed out from within before crashing into Shi Zhanfeng.

A sharp screech akin to the sound of metal grating on metal rang out as Shi Zhanfeng's arm struck the scaled beast on the head, only for him to be sent flying back by the force of the clash.

The devilish ape was identical in appearance to the creature confined within the black cage pendant that Shi Pokong had given to Shi Chuankong.

After knocking back Shi Zhanfeng, the devilish ape turned around and swung an arm at the woman.

The latter withdrew her bone whip, then jumped up in an agile fashion to evade the attack, while Du Yuan rushed over to the devilish ape's side before throwing an almighty punch.

Despite its massive frame, the devilish ape wasn't slow at all, and it twisted around before retaliating with a punch of its own.

The two fists clashed violently, sending gusts of fierce wind sweeping through the air in all directions.

Shi Chuankong took advantage of this opportunity to fly back in retreat, attempting to escape, yet he had only just leaped up into the air when a burst of white light appeared above his head, and Shi Zhanfeng descended upon him once again.

Shi Zhanfeng's attack was too fast for Shi Chuankong to parry with his saber, so he could only reflexively lean back, and a streak of white flashed past his cheek before sliding down his chest.

A lock of his silver hair drifted up into the air as a long gash was sliced into his cheek. The breastplate of his suit of bone armor was also shattered, while a gash that was deep enough to expose bone was inflicted onto his chest.

Shi Chuankong was sent plummeting to the ground by the force of the blow, but Shi Zhanfeng refused to give him any respite, racing after him in hot pursuit before stomping a foot down onto his chest.

A resounding boom rang out as violent tremors ran through the ground.

Shi Chuankong's body was embedded into the earth below, and a series of massive cracks appeared over the ground as blood came gushing out of his mouth.

His saber star artifact was kicked out of his grasp by Shi Zhanfeng, who then picked it and claimed it for himself.

As Shi Zhanfeng looked down at Shi Chuankong, a look of melancholy appeared in his eyes as he mused, "Compared with Shi Pokong, I don't harbor much resentment toward you. It's just that... Forget it, you can only blame yourself for putting your eggs in the wrong basket."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he raised his saber before swinging it down at Shi Chuankong's head.

Shi Chuankong seemed to have already given up on resisting, and there was a resigned smile on his face. All of a sudden, he loosened his own left fist, spreading his hand open to reveal a bloodstained, leaf-shaped jade pendant, the very same one that had been given to him by Shi Pokong!

The pendant was stained with his blood essence, seemingly having already been activated, and the thin veins on its surface began to glow radiantly.

An alarmed look appeared on Shi Zhanfeng's face upon seeing this, and he hurriedly shot back in retreat.

Immediately thereafter, the air around Shi Chuankong seemed to suddenly contract and converge around him, following which a radiant white sun rose up.

A resounding explosion rang out as the white sun imploded, sending waves of blinding white light washing over the entire white stone plaza.

Powerful shockwaves also swept through the air in all directions, peeling layers of earth up from the ground.

Even from his vantage point up in the pagoda over ten thousand feet away, Han Li felt a wave of heat sweeping toward him, almost forcing him to close his eyes, and the stone pagoda was also trembling violently, as if it could collapse at any moment.

The tremors lasted close to twenty seconds before finally slowly subsiding.

The outermost layer of the pagoda was already very fragile from wind erosion, and with much of it stripped away by the explosion, there was barely anything left of the pagoda standing.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he looked out at the white stone plaza.

The entire plaza had already been wiped out of existence, leaving only a crater that was over a hundred feet deep and over a thousand feet in diameter in its wake, and all of the nearby buildings had also been destroyed.

At the center of the crater laid Shi Chuankong's charred and bloodied body, and it was unclear whether he was dead or alive.

Right at this moment, his chest suddenly began to heave violently as he erupted into a violent coughing fit.

For some reason, not only had the jade pendant not teleported him back to the Devil Realm, it had set off an explosion that had almost killed him instead.

Shi Chuankong wanted to struggle up into a seated position, but as soon as he tried to move, a burst of excruciating pain instantly coursed through his entire body, causing him to let loose an involuntary cry of pain.

"It's extremely impressive that you were able to survive an explosion from an Explosive Space Realm Talisman from point blank," Shi Zhanfeng praised as he strode over to the edge of the crater with his two subordinates.

Half of his robe had been torn away, and even the suit of armor beneath it had also been severely ravaged. On top of that, his right arm and shoulder had been reduced to a grotesque mass of flesh and blood, with bone exposed in many parts.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing the words "Explosive Space Realm Talisman", and he pulled out his own leaf-shaped jade pendant with a grim look on his face.

If he had gone through with using the talisman while traversing through the spatial storm en route to entering the Great Ruins, then all of the cultivators from Puppet City and Profound City would've most likely already been dead by now.

At the bottom of the crater, Shi Chuankong was still trying to struggle into a seated position, but he was in such terrible condition that he was only able to make small, spasming motions.

Some of the charred ashes on his body began to slip off, revealing an extremely thin white garment that was giving off a white glow.

"Is that a Star Fox Robe? No wonder you were able to survive such a violent explosion. I thought that your mother would've left this treasure to Shi Pokong, considering how he was always her favorite son, but it seems like you inherited it instead," Shi Zhanfeng sneered.

Shi Chuankong paid no heed to Shi Zhanfeng's mockery as he closed eyes, and a tear slowly slid down his cheek.

Even during their mother's dying moments, she hadn't expressed any resentment toward those around her. Her final wish was that her two sons would continue to protect and look out for each other in this perilous world, yet it seemed that this final wish of hers was ultimately not able to come into fruition.

Pokong, why would you do this?

Right at this moment, a beastly roar suddenly rang out, and the devilish ape scaled beast erupted out of the crater, somehow completely unscathed, before charging at Shi Zhanfeng's trio.

"Get rid of that thing!" Shi Zhanfeng ordered with a hint of disdain in his eyes.

Du Yuan and the petite woman immediately launched themselves at the devilish ape in unison, and their battle resumed.

Meanwhile, Shi Zhanfeng slowly made his way to the bottom of the crater, then crouched down beside Shi Chuankong.

With a casual tug, the Star Fox Robe was removed from Shi Chuankong's body, only for it to immediately dissipate into nothingness.

"It's been ruined... What a pity..." Shi Zhanfeng sighed.

He then turned to Shi Chuankong with a look of sorrow in his eyes as he rested the tip of the saber in his hand onto Shi Chuankong's chest.

All of a sudden, Shi Chuankong's eyes sprang open, and he seemed to have composed himself as he asked, "Zhanfeng, what type of person do you think Pokong is?"

Shi Zhanfeng's brows furrowed slightly as he considered the question momentarily, then replied, "I've never been able to quite see through him."

"It's always said that the one who knows you best will always be your enemy. If even you can't see through Pokong, then I was a fool for thinking that I knew him well," Shi Chuankong sighed.

Shi Zhanfeng didn't understand what Shi Chuankong was alluding to, and he declared, "Alright, it's time for me to send you on your way."

Shi Chuankong merely smiled and closed his eyes once again, ready to accept his fate.

The melancholy in Shi Zhanfeng's eyes faded as he plunged the saber down toward Shi Chuankong's heart.

Chapter 936: Allies to Enemies

Right as Shi Zhanfeng's saber was about to fall, Han Li rushed out of the stone pagoda through the window, hurtling rapidly toward Shi Chuankong with his Star Moon Boots glowing radiantly.

However, after flying for several thousand feet, he suddenly spotted a white figure out of his peripheral vision, and they were also racing onto the scene from a different direction.

Han Li immediately stopped in his tracks upon seeing, then descended onto the roof of a relatively well-preserved palace.

Right as Shi Zhanfeng was about to plunge his saber through Shi Chuankong's heart, a blood-curdling howl suddenly rang out, and he immediately swung around with an alarmed expression to discover that a white flower had bloomed in front of Du Yuan's chest, and the flower was drenched in his blood.

Before he had a chance to figure out what had happened, the petals of the flower suddenly closed, forming a flower bud that was as sharp as a spear tip before being pulled out of Du Yuan's body.

A hole was left where his heart had once been, and a torrent of blood was gushing out from within.

Immediately thereafter, a slender figure clad in a suit of white bone armor emerged from behind Du Yuan, holding what appeared to be a bone spear in her hand as she smiled and waved at Shi Zhanfeng.

A stunned look appeared on Shi Zhanfeng's face, and his expression was mirrored by Han Li as he looked on from afar.

The armorclad figure was none other than Gu Qianxun!

She plunged her spear forward once again, this time driving it through Du Yuan's dantian to destroy the nascent soul inside.

The petite woman immediately began to dart back to Shi Zhanfeng's side upon seeing this, but the devilish ape refused to let her go, and she found herself entangled in a battle against it once again.

"I don't recall there being any bad blood between us, so why have you killed my companion?" Shi Zhanfeng asked with tightly furrowed brows.

Shi Chuankong had also opened his eyes and was looking at Gu Qianxun with a perplexed expression.

Gu Qianxun took a cold glance at Shi Chuankong, and she displayed no intention of answering the question posed to her as she darted straight toward Shi Zhanfeng.

"Are you trying to save him? I'm afraid I can't let you do that," Shi Zhanfeng chuckled as he swung his saber down toward Shi Chuankong's head.

It appeared that he was entirely focused on the task of decapitating Shi Chuankong, but in reality, he was simultaneously keeping a constant eye on the approaching Gu Qianxun out of his peripheral vision.

The skin and flesh on his arm was slowly regenerating, and he was secretly holding a white bone dagger that was as thin as a willow leaf. There were around a dozen star acupoints glowing on the dagger, and he was waiting to land a lethal blow upon Gu Qianxun as she swooped in to save Shi Chuankong.

However, as Gu Qianxun drew closer, Shi Zhanfeng noticed that her spear was aimed directly at his head, rather than at the saber in his hand.

She was here to kill, not to save anyone!

Shi Zhanfeng immediately swung around upon seeing this, the dagger in his hand flew out of his grasp, piercing directly toward Gu Qianxun's glabella.

All of the dozen or so star acupoints on the dagger were glowing radiantly, conjuring up hundreds of dagger projections that sped toward Gu Qianxun all at once.

Gu Qianxun's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but she continued charging onward, seemingly without any regard for self-preservation.

However, at the same time, the tip of her spear had veered away from its original trajectory to point at the willow leaf dagger instead, and a burst of white light erupted out of it like a blooming flower to encompass all of the oncoming dagger projections.

The petals of the flower then closed once again, reverting the spear tip to its original form. The dagger had been caught within the tip of the spear, and it was now also aimed at Shi Zhanfeng.

In response, Shi Zhanfeng darted back in retreat to the edge of the crater.

He took a glance at the petite woman, who was still struggling to shake off the devilish ape, then at his own arm, which was still yet to fully regenerate, and he heaved a forlorn sigh before ordering, "Run!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he turned and fled the scene, and the petite woman followed along after him without any hesitation.

The devilish ape chased after her for a while in futility, and after losing its target, it suddenly turned around before rushing at Gu Qianxun.

Gu Qianxun harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a small badge that hovered in mid-air in front of the devilish ape.

In the face of the badge, the devilish ape rapidly shrank back down into a miniature figure before being stowed away by Gu Qianxun along with the badge.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he observed the unfolding scene from afar.

"Are you here to save me or kill me?" Shi Chuankong asked with a calm expression.

Gu Qianxun offered no response, but a hint of melancholy had appeared in her eyes as she raised her spear before plunging it down at his glabella without any hesitation.

Right at this moment, a streak of white light raced through the air before striking the tip of her spear with a loud clang.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li arrived onto the scene, descending beside Shi Chuankong like the wind before catching the white scimitar that he had just hurled through the air.

"What is the meaning of this, Fellow Daoist Gu?" Han Li asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"I should be the one asking you that, Fellow Daoist Li. Why are you getting in my way?" Gu Qianxun asked in an indifferent manner.

"Fellow Daoist Shi is a friend of mine, so I'm not going to let you hurt him," Han Li declared.

"And what if I insist on killing him?" Gu Qianxun asked as a cold tone crept into her voice.

"In that case, you'll have to get past me," Han Li replied without any hesitation.

A cold gleam flashed through Gu Qianxun's eyes upon hearing this, and she abandoned Shi Chuankong to charge at Han Li without any hesitation.

Over thirty star acupoints lit up over her white bone spear, releasing radiant white light and over a hundred identical white spear projections that hurtled toward Han Li in unison.

Han Li remained completely unfazed as he swept his white scimitar through the air, and its blade sliced into the mass of oncoming spear projections.

All of the spear projections instantly dissipated as the blade of the scimitar struck the tip of the bone spear with unerring accuracy, stopping it cold in its tracks.

However, this seemed to have played right into Gu Qianxun's hands, and her eyes immediately lit up as the tip of her spear opened up once again, then immediately closed around the scimitar, catching its blade like a four-pronged mouth.

At the same time, an arrow of white light shot out of the tip of the spear directly toward Han Li's chest.

Simultaneously, Gu Qianxun swept a hand through the air to release a streak of black light, which contained the pendant that Shi Chuankong had been wearing earlier.

A dull thump rang out as the pendant exploded to form a vortex of black light, and the devilish ape re-emerged, albeit a little smaller than before, then rushed directly at Han Li.

As the devilish ape charged at Han Li, all of the countless spikes on its body shot forth as countless streaks of black light, which converged toward Han Li from all directions.

Meanwhile, Gu Qianxun had tossed her bone spear aside, and she swept her hands through the air to send eight white daggers flying out of her sleeves, all of which were aimed at Shi Chuankong, who had been her target this entire time.

Shi Chuankong was currently still completely unable to move, so he could only look on helplessly at the approaching daggers.

However, in the next instant, an earth-shattering boom rang out from Han Li's body, and his profound acupoints were glowing radiantly, releasing bursts of tremendous force in all directions.

The arrow of light released by the bone spear and the black spikes that had shot out of the devilish ape's body were all stopped cold in their tracks before shattering into countless pieces, while the devilish ape itself was also sent flying before crashing into a nearby building.

The building immediately collapsed, burying the devilish ape under a pile of rubble.

At the same time, Han Li vanished from the spot, then reappeared in front of Shi Chuankong an instant later as if by instantaneous teleportation before reaching out with his right hand to catch the eight oncoming daggers.

A stunned look appeared in Gu Qianxun's eyes upon seeing this, while Han Li took a glance at the eight daggers that he had caught before hurling them back at Gu Qianxun.

The daggers were sent flying back several times faster than when they were hurled by Gu Qianxun, and an alarmed look appeared on her face as he hurriedly grabbed onto her bone spear before sending the white scimitar that was still caught in its tip flying through the air.

The scimitar and the spear combined to keep the oncoming daggers at bay, but there was such tremendous force behind the daggers that Gu Qianxun was sent stumbling back seven or eight steps.

A fearful look flashed through her eyes as she turned and fled without any hesitation, but she wasn't able to get very far at all before Han Li appeared in her path in a wraith-like manner.

"Who exactly are you, Fellow Daoist Gu?" Han Li asked as Gu Qianxun drew to a shuddering halt.

"Why do you want to know so much, Fellow Daoist Li? If you want to save Shi Chuankong, then you can have him," Gu Qianxun replied as she composed herself before putting on a faint smile.

"Tell me who you are! Don't make me kill you!" Han Li threatened as a cold gleam flashed through his eyes.

Chapter 937: Holy Remains

"Sometimes, knowledge can be a burden, Fellow Daoist Li. It won't benefit you at all to ask too many questions here," Gu Qianxun replied.

Han Li raised an arm in silence, and a tremendous aura erupted out of his body, one that was filled with violence and brutality, much like the aura of a fearsome beast that had just awakened from a long slumber.

"Fine, I'll tell you everything," Gu Qianxun sighed.

Han Li stopped what he was doing upon hearing this, but his arm remained held aloft as he waited for Gu Qianxun to continue.

Gu Qianxun opened her mouth as if to speak, but all of a sudden, the bone spear in her hand shot forth without any warning, springing at Han Li like a vicious viper.

Han Li seemed to have already anticipated this, and he casually caught the bone spear, but right as he was about to retaliate, the bone spear suddenly began to tremble violently as all of its star acupoints began to release dazzling white light.

The bone spear exploded with a resounding boom into close to twenty fragments, all of which hurtled toward Han Li like pieces of lethal shrapnel.

At the same time, the tip of the spear split open once again to form a four-petaled white flower, and the petals flew directly at Han Li's chest at a far faster speed than the other fragments of the bone spear.

In the blink of an eye, they were no more than half a foot away from Han Li's chest, and this time, Han Li was caught off guard as he immediately shot back in retreat while throwing a punch forward.

The space ahead of him instantly solidified into an invisible wall that stopped the four white petals cold in their tracks, but they immediately began to struggle and writhe like living creatures, attempting to pierce through the invisible wall.

Ultimately, the four petals ran out of power and clattered to the ground along with the fragments of the bone spear.

"Farewell, Fellow Daoist Li."

Gu Qianxun had already fled into the distance in the same instant that the bone spear was detonated, and Han Li was just about to set off in pursuit when the devilish ape erupted out of the pile of rubble that it had been buried under before pouncing at Shi Chuankong.

The devilish ape let loose a thunderous roar as it swung its massive fist at Shi Chuankong's head, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he was forced to turn his attention away from Gu Qianxun.

A resounding boom rang out as the devilish ape's fist drew to a shuddering halt around half a foot above Shi Chuankong's head. It had been stopped by a hand, which stood in front of it like an immovable mountain.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li swung his other arm through the air, and the devilish ape was sent flying like a rag doll before exploding in mid-air into a cloud of black mist.

At this point, Gu Qianxun had already vanished into the distance.

Han Li took a glance in the direction that she had fled in, and by his estimates, he would have a roughly 50% chance of chasing her down if he were to go after her now, but he refrained from doing so.

Even though Gu Qianxun had refused to talk, he already had a decent idea of why she was aiming to kill Shi Chuankong.

Han Li turned his gaze to Shi Chuankong, and he was just about to say something when Shi Chuankong raised a hand with great difficulty, then reached into the front of his ruined robes to pull out a white jade vial.

He then tipped out a crimson pill from the vial before devouring it, immediately following which a hint of color instantly returned to his cheeks, while all of the wounds on his body also began to glow red.

The wounds were rapidly healing within the red light, and in just a few seconds, all of his external injuries had been healed.

All of a sudden, a serious look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as he began to chant an incantation while tapping his fingers all over his own body, and a burst of translucent crimson light appeared over his chest.

A hint of elation appeared on Shi Chuankong's face at the sight of the speck of crimson light, and he began to speed up in his chanting and his finger movements.

A faint splashing sound could be heard ringing out within his body, as if there were a river flowing inside, and the speck of crimson light began to flicker before slowly moving from his chest to his left arm.

He immediately raised his right hand and chopped it down viciously upon his own left shoulder without any hesitation, amputating the entire arm.

As soon as his left arm was detached from his body, the speck of crimson light on it immediately erupted into a crimson flame that set the entire arm alight.

Han Li hurriedly grabbed onto Shi Chuankong and dragged him to the side upon seeing this.

The effects of the pill that Shi Chuankong had just taken hadn't run its course yet, and the wound on his left shoulder was instantly sealed, thereby stopping the bleeding.

At this point, Shi Chuankong's left arm had already been incinerated into ashes, and the crimson flames had also faded away, leaving only a crimson jade-like bead behind.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

"Don't move!" Shi Chuankong warned, and Han Li did as he was told, remaining perfectly still on the spot.

The crimson bead was trembling slightly as if it were scouring the surrounding environment, only to ultimately give up on its search and vanish into the ground.

Only then did a look of relief appear on Shi Chuankong's face as he reached into the front of his own robe to pull out another crimson pill that he promptly devoured.

The wound on his left shoulder instantly began to glow with radiant crimson light, and a new arm was rapidly emerging.

In less than twenty seconds, a brand new arm had appeared to replace Shi Chuankong's amputated one.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this. In the outside world, regrowing a limb wasn't a difficult task thanks to the world's origin qi present in the environment, but it was not so simple in the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

Even though Shi Chuankong had regrown a new arm, he was still looking extremely pale, and he sat down with his legs crossed to digest the two pills that he had just taken.

Han Li strode over to his side and also sat down before closing his eyes to rest.

Three days and three nights flew by in a flash.

By the time Shi Chuankong opened his eyes again, his complexion was looking much better, and he took a deep breath as he rose to his feet.

"Are you feeling alright, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked as he also stood up.

"You really are my lucky star, Fellow Daoist Li. Without you, I would be long dead by now," Shi Chuankong said with a wry smile.

"It's fine. What are friends for? By the way, what was that crimson bead that came out of your body?" Han Li asked.

"That was a drop of blood essence that E Kuai planted into my body using a blood tracking secret technique, and it can allow him to monitor someone within a certain range. Even though I was severely wounded by the Explosive Space Realm Talisman, its power also destroyed part of the blood tracking secret technique by a stroke of luck, thereby allowing me to expel it from my body," Shi Chuankong explained.

"I see. The Scalptia Spatial Domain may be devoid of spiritual and devilish qi, but there's still no lack of these unorthodox techniques," Han Li remarked.

"It was also because of this blood tracking secret technique that I acted so cold and detached to you in the past. Please forgive me, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong said in an apologetic manner.

"There's no need to apologize, I would've done the same thing under those circumstances. Having said that, what I want to know is why E Kuai planted this blood tracking secret technique in your body," Han Li said.

Shi Chuankong's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, following which a sullen look appeared in his eyes.

Han Li made no attempt to rush him, merely patiently waiting for him to respond.

"If you hadn't saved me just now, I would already be dead, so I won't keep any secrets from you. Truth be told, I entered the Scalptia Spatial Domain with you not just to help you search for Violet Spirit. Instead, I have another objective, and that's actually my main objective for entering the Scalptia Spatial Domain," Shi Chuankong said after a long silence.

From the conversation that had taken place between Shi Chuankong and Shi Zhanfeng, Han Li had already guessed that Shi Chuankong had an alternate motive for entering the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so he wasn't surprised to hear this, and he asked, "What is it?"

"I came here to search for the Scalptia Holy Remains," Shi Chuankong replied.

"What's that?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not sure of the exact details myself. All I've heard is that it's an exceptional treasure that's extremely helpful for breaking through the Great Encompassment Stage bottleneck, and that there's a very good chance that it's in the Great Ruins. I initially came into the Scalptia Spatial Domain for Pokong's sake, but from now on, I'm going to live for myself.

“I have some information on the Great Ruins given to me by Pokong, and one of the main reasons E Kuai decided to imprison me is because he wanted to get his hands on this information. Would you be interested in coming with me to search for the Scalptia Holy Remains? I'm sure it'll be extremely helpful to you as well," Shi Chuankong replied.

"In that case, E Kuai has also entered the Great Ruins to obtain these holy remains, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's most likely the case. However, he's a man who's harboring many secrets, and I think he has some other objectives as well," Shi Chuankong replied as his brows furrowed slightly.

"If E Kuai is also searching for these holy remains, then we'll be pitting ourselves against him by also searching for it. This is a very significant decision to make, so please allow me some time to think," Han Li said.

"Of course, take all the time you need," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

In any case, they weren't going to be able to set off anytime soon. Even though Shi Chuankong appeared to have already made a full recovery, his internal injuries were still quite severe, so he was going to require an extended period of rest and recuperation.

After resting for three more days, Shi Chuankong had only made a halfway recovery, and the two of them began making their way deeper into the plaza.

Chapter 938: Abnormal Occurrence

Within a certain palace in the Great Ruins.

The palace was several thousand feet in area, and the ground was paved with green tiles, while the walls were also the same color, giving the entire place a rather cold and eerie appearance.

At the center of the palace was a square elevated altar, upon which stood three figures.

At the center of the trio was E Kuai, and he was accompanied by Mistress Liu Hua and the black-robed man.

The area near the altar was severely ravaged, with many deep craters in the ground, as well as countless puppet fragments everywhere, clearly indicating that an intense battle had just taken place.

E Kuai paid no heed to his surroundings as he observed the top of the altar, which was circular in shape and very flat and smooth.

Its surface was also riddled with countless star runes to form a complex star array, at the center of which was a crimson object, most of which was embedded into the altar, so it was impossible to tell exactly what it was.

Dazzling white light was radiating from the star array, forming a pillar of white light that protected the crimson object from all directions.

E Kuai turned his gaze to Mistress Liu Hua, and the latter immediately sprang into action, placing a series of array tools onto the altar while also pulling out a Star Wave Pen to begin making inscriptions.

Only after close to two hours of work did he finally step back, and at that point, a new array had taken shape around the existing star array on the altar.

From there, Mistress Liu Hua chanted an incantation before flicking a finger through the air, releasing a burst of white light out of his fingertip.

The array that he had just created instantly began operating, releasing rays of white light that fused into the pillar of white light on the altar.

The rays of white light weren't particularly bright, but as soon as they entered the pillar of white light, the latter immediately began to rapidly fade away, revealing the crimson object inside.

"Impressive as always, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua. I don't think anyone else in the Scalptia Spatial Domain could've broken this Heavenly Starlight Array so easily," E Kuai praised with a pleased smile.

"You're far too kind, City Lord E. Please make haste, the array that I just set down isn't going to last long," Mistress Liu Hua replied.

E Kuai nodded in response, then stepped onto the altar and began making his way toward the crimson object.

The array on the altar hadn't been deactivated, and as soon as E Kuai set foot onto the array patterns, they immediately lit up and sent countless arrows of light hurtling directly toward him.

However, these arrows of light immediately faded away as soon as they reached within a certain distance of him, so he was able to continue onward unobstructed.

It didn't take long for E Kuai to reach the crimson object, and he grabbed onto it before forcefully tugging it upward.

The object began to radiate crimson light as it slowly rose upward, and the entire altar began trembling violently along with the surrounding palace.

E Kuai paid no heed to this as he continued to pull on the crimson object, and a series of profound acupoints had lit up over his arm, indicating that this was not an easy task for him.

The crimson object was gradually being pulled out of an altar, and it appeared to be around half a foot in length, but it wasn't clear exactly what it was as if it was concealed within the radiant crimson light around it.

After the object was completely pulled out of the altar, a faint crack rang out, and the white light radiating from the altar completely faded, while all of the array patterns also turned gray.

The crimson light emanating from the crimson object also faded, revealing it to be an antiquated key that seemed to have been crafted from some type of jade material.

The key was riddled with countless tiny runes, and E Kuai was inspecting it with a pleased expression as he murmured to himself, "That's the second one."

"Congratulations, City Lord E," the black-robed man said, while Mistress Liu Hua remained silent.

……

Meanwhile, in a certain underground cave somewhere within the Great Ruins.

The roof of the cave was riddled with crimson patterns that formed an enormous array, which was giving off faint crimson light that illuminated the darkness slightly, and a series of figures could be seen standing on the ground beneath the array.

There were countless figures present, stretching as far as the eyes could see, and right at this moment, the crimson array above them flashed erratically a few times before turning completely dark, plunging the entire underground cave into absolute darkness.

However, right at this moment, the eyes of one of the figures standing on the ground suddenly began to glow white as they raised their heads.

This seemed like some type of catalyst, and the eyes of all of the figures in the underground cave lit up one after another. In the blink of an eye, countless specks of white light had appeared in the cave, resembling a starry night sky.

……

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were naturally oblivious to what was happening underground.

At this moment, they were still exploring the plaza beneath the altar.

The plaza was enormous, and the two of them searched for almost an entire day before finally discovering a secluded palace.

The palace was less than a thousand feet tall, and it was entirely constructed from giant black stone blocks. There weren't any decorative engravings on its surface, but there was an image of a starry night sky engraved onto its tightly shut stone gates.

"Brother Li, I'm willing to bet that there must be puppets inside far more powerful than the ones we've faced thus far. What do you think?" Shi Chuankong asked with a smile.

"I'm not going to bet against you. I don't get anything for winning, and losing is a sign of bad luck, so it's a lose-lose situation for me," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

The two of them had encountered many ruined buildings on the way here, most of which had been completely devoid of spoils. They had also encountered some puppets along the way, but none of them were very powerful and had been easily dismantled.

For some reason, Han Li couldn't help but feel as if there were something different about Shi Chuankong. The change wasn't in his appearance, cultivation base, or aura. Instead, the change was in some type of unquantifiable quality.

Han Li was well aware of the reason for this change. Even though neither of them had mentioned Shi Pokong's betrayal on the way here, it was clear that the betrayal had had a profound effect on Shi Chuankong.

"Let's go," Han Li said, then strode forward and pressed a palm against the heavy stone gate before pushing on it.

A resounding grating noise rang out as the gate swung back, creating an opening that was wide enough for the two of them to fit through. It was pitch-black inside, and the entire place smelled like decay.

Han Li took a brief glance at his surroundings, then made his way inside with the white scimitar in his hand, followed closely by Shi Chuankong.

As soon as they entered the palace, a flame instantly lit up on the nearby wall. The flame then quickly spread over the entire perimeter of the palace along the slots on the walls, illuminating the entire area.

A slightly, sickly sweet odor began to waft through the air, seemingly from some type of burning fat.

Thanks to the light of the fire, Han Li was able to see a moderate-sized rectangular pond on the ground not far up ahead. The pond was already completely dry, and there was a white stone arch bridge.

The surrounding stone walls were riddled with floral engravings that had soft, yet extremely clear and vivid linework. Interspersed throughout these floral designs were some engravings of different beasts, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

At the end of the palace stood seven or eight black stone statues, and the two directly facing across from Han Li and Shi Chuankong were both in a standing posture.

The one on the left depicted a tall and imposing devilish man with a head of short hair that was spiked up at the heavens. He had a set of ape-like facial features with fangs that were protruding out of his mouth, and he was clad in a suit of black devilish armor, while a long staff was held in his grasp.

The staff was only around the same thickness as an infant's arm, but it was riddled with storm cloud designs, and it appeared to be a different material from the rest of the statue.

The statue on the right depicted a slender human woman who was extremely beautiful, with a pair of bright and exuberant eyes. There were silken streamers draped over her body, and they were dancing in the wind, giving her the appearance of a celestial maiden who was soaring through the heavens.

Her hands were cupped together in front of her chest, and cradled over her palms was a crimson key that appeared to have been made from some type of jade-like material.

Beside each of them were three halberd-wielding guards that were half-knelt onto the ground, and they were identical in appearance. Their upper bodies were bared to reveal bulging muscles that seemed to be brimming with explosive power.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with each other, then strode over the edge of the pond. After inspecting the pond momentarily, they made their way onto the stone arch bridge leading to the other side.

Upon making it to the center point of the bridges, the ground beneath them suddenly began to tremble, and they hurriedly stopped in their tracks before looking around, but didn't discover anything amiss.

Right at this moment, the faint sound of trickling water suddenly began to ring out from under the bridge.

Han Li looked down to discover that there seemed to be a hole at the bottom of the pond, and water was pouring out from within.

"What's going on?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"I'm not sure, but let's get to the other side first," Han Li replied with slightly furrowed brows.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the sound of flowing water suddenly grew louder, and the rate of water outflow drastically increased, with most of the pond quickly filled up.

At the same time, plumes of white mist began to rise up from the surface of the water, and Han Li looked up to discover that an image of a glowing starry sky had appeared on the ceiling of the palace above.

His brows furrowed slightly as he and Shi Chuankong took a step forward in unison, and all of a sudden, they found themselves in a resplendent palace, as if they had been teleported into a completely different setting.

The sound of musical instruments rang out as a group of beautiful women in colorful dresses swayed their hips from side to side while playing different musical instruments, performing a well-rehearsed dance.

Chapter 939: One Obstacle After Another

"I didn't think that I would encounter an illusion here," Han Li remarked with a calm smile.

"Don't underestimate this illusion, Brother Li. I just tried to use a spiritual sense secret technique to break it, but to no avail. If you have a way to break this illusory array, then I suggest you do it before the illusion takes a more dangerous turn," Shi Chuankong said with a wry smile.

Han Li nodded in response as he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique.

As he turned to inspect his surroundings once again, he discovered that all of the beautiful dancing women had taken on an extremely harrowing appearance, with rotting flesh clinging to withered bones.

Han Li couldn't help but grimace slightly at this jarring sight.

"Are you also unable to break the illusion, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"This is quite an interesting illusory array, but it shouldn't be too difficult to break it," Han Li replied with a confident smile.

Right as his voice trailed off, the hideous, decomposing women seemed to have discovered that Han Li was attempting to break the array, and they threw down their musical instruments before pouncing at him with their fingers extended into sinister claws.

Han Li channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might as he let loose a loud roar, and it was as if a thunderclap had rung out within the palace.

Even Shi Chuankong shuddered involuntarily, and the bodies of all of the decomposing women instantly exploded before dissipating into specks of dark red flames.

However, even after all of the decomposing women had been eradicated, the two of them remained in the illusion of the opulent palace.

"It looks like we'll only be able to make it out of this array by breaking its core. Hold on tight, Brother Shi," Han Li said as he grabbed onto Shi Chuankong's shoulder before stomping a foot heavily down onto the ground.

The ground in the entire palace collapsed to form a bottomless pit, which Han Li and Shi Chuankong plummeted into.

Only after close to twenty seconds did the sensation of falling fade away, and as they inspected their surroundings once again, they discovered that they had returned to the same palace from before.

At this moment, the two of them were standing at the center of the dried pond, and the stone arch bridge had already been shattered by the force of Han Li's stomp.

"Looks like this bridge was the core of that illusory array," Shi Chuankong remarked.

Han Li nodded in response, and he was just about to say something when he suddenly turned and cast his gaze toward the rear of the palace.

A string of faint cracks rang out from the statues of the halberd-wielding guards that were half-knelt on the stone platform, and a series of cracks began to spread over their bodies.

Immediately thereafter, a glimmer of red light appeared in their eyes, and all of them seemed to have sprung to life as they turned to Han Li and Shi Chuankong in unison.

"Here we go again," Han Li sighed with a shake of his head.

The cracking sounds ringing out from the bodies of the six statues grew louder, and chunks of stone began to peel off their bodies as they rose to their feet.

After rising to their feet, the six puppets flexed their necks from side to side in a very humanized manner, then gripped onto their halberd and pounced at Han Li's duo.

They split up into two groups while in mid-air, with three of them pouncing at Han Li, while the other three launched themselves at Shi Chuankong.

Han Li darted back to evade a piercing attack from one of the puppets, then pushed off with both feet against the ground, and thanks to the speed boost provided by his Star Moon Boots, he was able to almost instantly reach the puppet.

From there, he slashed his scimitar toward the puppet's head, yet before his attack had a chance to land, the other two guards were already upon him, with their halberd aimed at his throat and his dantian.

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this, and he stopped in his tracks before spinning around on the spot, parrying the halberd aimed at his throat with his scimitar while also kicking aside the halberd that was aimed at his dantian.

Right at this moment, he felt a gust of wind sweep over the back of his head as the first puppet thrust its halberd at the back of his head.

Han Li was able to dodge the attack by swaying his head to the side, but internally, he was astonished by just how seamless the teamwork between the three puppets was.

Thankfully, they weren't all that fast. Otherwise, there was a good chance that Han Li would've already been struck by one of their attacks.

After swaying to the side to evade the oncoming halberd, Han Li reached out to grab onto its shaft, then forced it downward in a powerful motion to catapult its wielder up into the air.

Before the puppet had a chance to land, Han Li sprang up into the air to pursue it, then sliced it into two with a sweep of his scimitar.

Meanwhile, Shi Chuankong had already been forced into a corner of the pond by his three puppet assailants.

Two of the puppets had thrust their halberds at his chest, and even though he was able to keep their attacks at bay, the puppets were able to push him all the way back with their halberds until he was trapped in the corner.

The third puppet sprang up from the ruined stone arch bridge, holding onto the shaft of its halberd with both hands as it thrust it down upon Shi Chuankong's chest.

Shi Chuankong was still yet to fully recover from his injuries, so he was in no condition to be fighting, and all he could do was look on helplessly as the halberd sped toward his chest.

Right at this moment, Han Li swiveled around in mid-air, and his scimitar flew out of his grasp, revolving end over end as it was hurled at the puppet from afar.

The puppet was able to detect the scimitar that was flying toward it from behind, and it withdrew its halberd to deflect the scimitar away.

That split second of delay was all that Han Li needed to arrive on the scene, and he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts as a string of profound acupoints lit up over his arm in rapid succession.

The puppet only had the chance to turn around halfway before it was struck on the head by Han Li's fist, and its head instantly exploded like a ripe watermelon.

Right at this moment, Shi Chuankong suddenly yelled in an alarmed voice, "Look out!"

Han Li immediately ducked down upon hearing this, but before he had a chance to move away, he was dealt a tremendous blow to the shoulder, and he crashed heavily down onto hte ground with a resounding boom.

The entire pond was instantly shattered, while he plunged into the ground like a steel nail.

Instead of taking any time to see what it was that he had just been attacked by, Han Li burrowed deeper into the ground, quickly vanishing out of sight.

Immediately thereafter, the ground elsewhere in the palace suddenly began to bulge before splitting open, and Han Li re-emerged.

His brows were tightly furrowed as he cast his gaze toward the stone platform in the palace, only to find that the statue of the staff-wielding devilish man was nowhere to be seen.

All of a sudden, Han Li sprang forward with all his might, and in the next instant, a purple staff came crashing down into the ground, only just barely glancing past his back.

The ground exploded violently as sparks and shattered stone shards erupted in all directions, and Han Li swung around to discover the statue of the devilish man hovering in mid-air with its staff in its hand.

There was a pair of black wings on its back that were flapping steadily, and it seemed to possess some degree of intelligence as a frustrated look had appeared on its face after its attack failed to land.

With a violent flap of its wings, a fierce whirlwind was swept up around it, and it flew directly at Han Li at an extraordinary speed.

On this occasion, Han Li raised his scimitar and swung it at the puppet's face instead of taking any evasive measures.

A humanized gleeful gleam flashed through the puppet's eyes upon seeing this, and it grabbed onto its staff with both hands, upon which a layer of faint white light emerged over its surface, indicating that it was a star artifact.

It swung its staff through the air to clash against Han Li's white scimitar, and Han Li felt a burst of tremendous force shoot through his arm upon impact, forcing him to raise his other arm so that he could support the scimitar with both hands.

At the same time, his legs had already sunk around half a foot into the ground, and he couldn't help but be astonished by the puppet's incredible combination of speed and power.

Before he had a chance to retaliate, a series of star acupoints lit up over the purple staff, immediately following which a thick arc of white lightning shot out from within before striking Han Li on the glabella.

Han Li felt a burning sensation on his forehead, and his consciousness also shuddered violently. As a result, the strength in his arms seeped away, and the purple staff was able to overwhelm his scimitar before striking him on the shoulder.

Han Li's legs buckled beneath him as his body began to fall back, and a cold look appeared on the puppet's face upon seeing this as it prepared to swing its staff down onto Han Li's head.

In the instant that Han Li was struck by the arc of white lightning, he had already channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, so he was able to quickly regain lucidity.

In this dire situation, he hurriedly pulled out a small white shield from the front of his robe before injecting his starpower into it with all his might.

Radiant white starlight surged into the shield, and it conjured up a white light barrier that was just barely large enough to encompass his entire body.

Chapter 940: Crimson Key

Right as the white light barrier was conjured up, the puppet's purple staff had already come crashing down with tremendous power.

A resounding boom rang out as the white light barrier trembled violently, and a vast expanse of white lightning erupted out of the staff.

Countless arcs of lightning sprang through the air in all directions, striking the nearby ground to raise large flurries of sparks.

The lightning raged for several seconds before beginning to fade, and at that point, the light barrier released by the shield had been whittled down to the extent that it was only just barely able to encompass Han Li's body.

Right at this moment, the winged puppet knocked Han Li's Star Shield aside with its staff, then stepped forward and threw a kick right into Han Li's midsection.

Han Li felt as if an entire mountain had crashed into him, and all of his internal organs churned violently as he was sent flying back through the air, smashing through the broken stone arch bridge before being embedded deeply into the wall of the pond.

However, immediately thereafter, he thrust his palms against the wall behind him and shot forward through the air, right as the wing puppet was flying rapidly in his direction.

In the instant before the two of them were about to clash, a series of profound acupoints lit up over Han Li's legs, and he stomped down onto the air below to elevate himself by several feet, passing over the puppet's head before stomping down with all his might.

At the same time, all of the profound acupoints on his body also lit up, releasing a formidable wave of white light that came crashing down upon the winged puppet.

Two of the halberd-wielding puppets were pouncing at Han Li from different directions, only to be instantly dismantled by this wave of white light.

The winged puppet was far more powerful than its halberd-wielding counterparts, and it didn't even lower its head in the face of the tremendous pressure being exerted upon it by Han Li. However, its wings seemed to be a weak point, and they were torn to shreds by the wave of white light.

Han Li's almighty stomp landed heavily upon the winged puppet's shoulders, instantly causing it to sink into the ground, while a series of massive cracks appeared beneath its feet.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, and numerous profound acupoints lit up over his arms in unison as he swung his fists down upon the puppet's head.

A vast expanse of starpower erupted out of his arms, and the puppet's head was completely flattened like a pancake upon impact, following which the light faded from its eyes, and its body went completely limp.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh of relief upon seeing this, then jumped down from the puppet's shoulders before casting his gaze toward Shi Chuankong.

At this point, only one of the halberd-wielding puppets was still left standing, and it had already been pursued by Shi Chuankong to the entrance of the palace, so it was no longer a threat.

Han Li then turned his gaze to the statue of the woman that remained on the stone platform, and he murmured to himself, "At least one of them decided to stay put..."

His gaze then fell upon the crimson key in the statue's hands, and after a brief hesitation, he began to make his way toward the stone platform.

However, before he had a chance to step onto it, a white light restriction abruptly appeared before him, separating him from the statue of the woman.

Han Li immediately stopped in his tracks before descending out of mid-air, and after some close examination, he discovered that a pillar of white light had risen up around the statue from the stone platform.

"Interesting," Han Li mused to himself.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out from behind him as the final halberd-wielding puppet was destroyed by Shi Chuankong.

Shortly thereafter, Shi Chuankong joined Han Li by the stone platform, picking up Han Li's white scimitar and the purple staff along the way.

"What's going on here, Brother Li?" he asked.

"Take a look at the array patterns down below. Do they look familiar to you?" Han Li asked.

Shi Chuankong did as he was told, and he looked down to discover a set of extremely complex array patterns below the pillar of light, some areas of which did indeed appear somewhat familiar.

"These appear to be runes that were on the Star Falcon Flying Boat," Shi Chuankong said.

"That's right. These array patterns appear to be very complex, but there are some sections that are not entirely alien to me," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Does that mean you can breach this array?" Shi Chuankong asked as a hint of elation flashed through his eyes.

"I'm not fully confident, but I can give it a try," Han Li replied with a smile, following which he pulled out the Star Wave Pen that Mistress Liu Hua had given to him before commencing the process of inscribing a separate array outside of the existing one.

He did so quite slowly, stopping every once in a while to examine his own work, and only after over an hour did he finally complete the array.

"Is it done?" Shi Chuankong asked.

Han Li offered no response. Instead, he stowed the Star Wave Pen away, then began to chant an incantation.

Moments later, he channeled the starpower within his own body before flicking a finger through the air, and a burst of white light shot out of his fingertip and into the array on the ground.

Immediately thereafter, the array that he had engraved onto the ground began to buzz and function, releasing rays of white light that fused into the pillar of white light on the stone platform.

The pillar of white light immediately began to melt away rapidly, and a faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he strode over to the statue of the woman before plucking the crimson key out of her hands.

To his surprise, the key was slightly warm to the touch, as if he had just taken it out of a pair of actual, human hands, but aside from that, there was nothing remarkable about it.

"So we did all that just for a single key, and we don't even know what it's used for," Shi Chuankong said with a wry smile.

"Given how tightly guarded this key is, I'm sure it's very important. I wonder if it has anything to do with the holy remains that you mentioned," Han Li said as he handed the key to Shi Chuankong.

"It doesn't seem to be special in any way. I think it'll be safer if you keep it in your possession," Shi Chuankong said as he handed the key back to Han Li after a brief examination.

Han Li accepted the key from him before placing it down the front of his own robe, but as soon as he did this, he felt a change in the crimson key.

Rays of faint crimson light had emerged over its surface, and it was beginning to pulse gently like the beating of a heart.

At the same time, a burst of heat surged out of the key before entering his body, striking him with a comforting sensation, like bathing in hot springs.

All of the pores on his body had opened, and his circulation had sped up significantly.

On top of that, he could sense that the latest profound acupoint that he had been working on had opened up just a little further.

"Are you alright, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked upon spotting the change in Han Li's expression.

"I'm fine," Han Li replied, and he was just about to say something else when the entire palace suddenly began to tremble violently.

The tremors were quickly becoming more and more violent, and it was as if an earthquake had suddenly struck.

"What's going on?"

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were both very alarmed by this abrupt turn of events.

Widening cracks were beginning to appear on the surrounding walls, and loose rocks were already tumbling down from above.

"This place is about to collapse! We have to get out of here!" Han Li exclaimed as he grabbed onto Shi Chuankong's arm.

Immediately thereafter, all of the profound acupoints on his body lit up, with the ones on his legs glowing particularly radiantly, resonating with the many star acupoints on his Star Moon Boots.

Han Li pushed off against the ground with both feet, launching himself up into the air with Shi Chuankong.

In the instant that he rose up from the ground, he suddenly noticed that there were rays of blue light emanating from the large cracks on the ground, indicating that there seemed to be something underground.

However, this wasn't the time to be focusing on what was underground, and Han Li quickly turned his attention back to the task at hand, darting back and forth through the air in an agile fashion to evade the falling rubble.

Shi Chuankong was also doing his part, swinging the purple staff to deflect or shatter some of the falling rocks.

On the ground below, an area with a radius of close to ten kilometers around the black altar had begun trembling, and a series of massive rifts appeared over the ground, following which that entire area collapsed violently to form a massive crater.

In the instant that the ground collapsed, two figures flew out before landing on a building that hadn't been affected.

Both of them were covered in dust and looking rather disheveled, but neither of them paid any heed to their own physical appearance as they looked into the giant crater with surprised expressions.

"Why did the ground suddenly collapse?" Shi Chuankong asked with tightly furrowed brows.

Han Li offered no response.

He was still thinking about the rays of blue light that he had spotted underground.

"Could it be that you already have a rough idea of what happened, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"That disturbance was most likely caused by us taking that crimson key. Otherwise, it would be far too much of a coincidence," Han Li said.

"If that's the case, then there must be far more to this key than meets the eye," Shi Chuankong mused.

"I think we should get out of this place as soon as possible. For some reason, I have a bad feeling," Han Li said in a grim voice.

"You're right, we should..."

All of a sudden, Shi Chuankong's voice cut off mid-sentence as Han Li grabbed onto him once again before darting away into the distance.

Chapter 941: Endless Trouble

Not long after Han Li and Shi Chuankong rose up into the air, the sound of insistent rustling began to ring out from beneath the wreckage of the palace.

The layer of earth on top of the wreckage site began to move, and one arm after another emerged, followed by a series of strange-looking heads.

There were countless puppets crawling out from underground one after another.

These puppets weren't particularly large, each standing at only around twenty feet tall, and they possessed humanoid lower bodies, but their upper bodies and heads weren't humanoid in appearance and could be roughly split up into three types.

One type of puppet had wolf heads and slim bodies, wielding a pair of blue longswords in their hands.

The second type of puppet had tiger heads and a more muscular build, each wielding a giant mountain-splitting saber.

The final type of puppet had snake heads and thin layers of fine scales on their bodies, as well as glowing blue bows strapped to their backs.

All of the swords, sabers, and bows wielded by these puppets were giving off starpower fluctuations, and there was an enormous number of these puppets burrowing their way out of the earth in all directions.

These puppets weren't all that remarkable in appearance, but it was clear that they were nothing to be scoffed at, and with such ridiculously large numbers on their side, getting caught among them would surely spell certain death, even for a cultivator of Han Li's caliber.

With that in mind, Han Li hurriedly sped away into the distance as quickly as he could, treading on air to ensure that he remained high above the ground.

However, even though he was able to fly thanks to his Wingform Ascension Arts and Star Moon Boots, his speed was ultimately limited, and he was dragging Shi Chuankong along as well, thereby further slowing him down.

As soon as these puppets emerged from the ground, they immediately looked up at Han Li's duo with humanized looks of resentment in their eyes.

A particularly large snake-headed puppet let loose a wild roar, and all of the other snake-headed puppets on the ground raised their bows before nocking arrows upon them.

Immediately thereafter, a volley of blue arrows was sent flying toward Han Li and Shi Chuankong from all directions, cutting off all avenues of evasion.

A grim look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he conjured up his True Extreme Film over his own body, and at the same time, he swung his white scimitar through the air to defect as many of the oncoming arrows as he could.

Shi Chuankong also conjured up his own True Extreme Film while swinging his newly acquired purple staff through the air as well.

A string of loud clang rang out in rapid succession as Han Li knocked away all of the blue arrows flying at him with his scimitar.

However, these arrows had been fired with tremendous power, and it didn't take long before his arm began to feel numb from the repeated impacts.

Shi Chuankong was also able to keep the oncoming arrows at bay with his purple staff, but his arms were trembling from the strain.

In the face of such a formidable wave of attacks, the two of them had drawn to a screeching halt.

Right at this moment, dozens of the nearby wolf and tiger-headed puppets sprang up into the air, jumping up several hundred feet with ease before lashing out at Han Li and Shi Chuankong from all directions with their swords and sabers.

The three types of puppets were working together seamlessly, as if they had already rehearsed this sequence countless times, and they were giving Han Li and Shi Chuankong no opportunity for respite.

A string of metallic clangs rang out, and all of the dozens of wolf and tiger-headed puppets were dismantled before falling out of the sky.

Before Han Li and Shi Chuankong had a chance to do anything else, countless more arrows came flying at them.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he deflected the arrows away with his white scimitar while simultaneously rising up even further into the sky.

At this point, they were already close to reaching the layer of dense, yellow clouds up above, yet they still hadn't made it out of the firing range of the snake-headed puppets.

Han Li took a glance at the yellow clouds overhead with a hesitant expression, and he was just about to rise up even further when Shi Chuankong's urgent voice suddenly rang out beside his ears.

"Don't go up any higher, those yellow clouds are extremely dangerous! I'll ward off all the attacks, you focus on getting us out of here."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a string of star acupoints lit up over the purple staff in his hand, and he swung it rapidly through the air, creating a purple whirlwind that swept up all of the oncoming blue arrows before destroying them with ease.

Han Li wanted to ask Shi Chuankong what exactly was so dangerous about these yellow clouds, but the latter was entirely focused on warding off the enemy attacks, so Han Li could only continue to tread over the air in an attempt to escape.

Right at this moment, another batch of wolf and tiger-headed puppets sprang up into the air at Han Li's duo, and the puppets from elsewhere were quickly converging as well.

Shi Chuankong let loose a loud roar as he dismantled this next wave of puppets with his staff, but these wolf and tiger-headed puppets weren't as easy to deal with as the volleys of arrows, and it was clear that warding off their attacks had placed quite a physical strain upon him.

Before he even had a chance to catch his breath, another volley of arrows arrived.

While racing through the air, Han Li took a glance at Shi Chuankong's pale complexion, and a grim look surfaced in his eyes.

Shi Chuankong was still yet to fully recover from his injuries, so he most likely wasn't going to be able to last long at this rate. However, at the moment, Han Li saw no better strategy than to continue running away.

In the blink of an eye, the two of them were forced to withstand dozens of waves of attacks from the puppets down below. Shi Chuankong was doing most of the work, while Han Li helped out occasionally, but most of his attention was focused on getting away.

However, there were still more puppets burrowing their way out of the ground in all directions, forming what appeared to be a boundless sea of puppets that stretched as far as the eyes could see in all directions.

A low roar rang out as close to a hundred wolf and tiger-headed puppets sprang up into the air once again.

At this point, Shi Chuankong was already looking as pale as a sheet, and the staff in his hand transformed into another purple whirlwind that swept toward the oncoming puppets.

A string of loud thumps rang out as all of the puppets were sent flying, but Shi Chuankong also threw up a large mouthful of blood.

The True Extreme Film around his body was flickering incessantly and had become far dimmer than before, and the purple staff almost slipped out of his limp grasp.

"You're going to die if you keep this up, Fellow Daoist Shi!" Han Li said in an urgent voice.

"I'll be fined," Shi Chuankong replied in a strained voice.

Right at this moment, another volley of arrows arrived, this one containing far more arrows than previous ones.

"Take some time to recover, I'll take care of everything from now on," Han Li said as he tucked Shi Chuankong under his left arm.

At the same time, he swung his scimitar through the air with his right arm, deflecting all of the blue arrows that were flying at him from the front, the left, and the right, but ignored the ones that were coming at him from behind.

Around a dozen blue arrows struck Han Li on the back with immense power, but were kept out by his True Extreme Film, which shuddered violently before quickly stabilizing again.

Thanks to the force of the arrows, Han Li sped up drastically, allowing him to cover a large distance in the blink of an eye.

Shi Chuankong couldn't help but be impressed with Han Li's courage and powers upon seeing this, and he hurriedly took a pill before closing his eyes to rest.

Following the volley of arrows, several hundred puppets sprang up into the air before pouncing at Han Li's duo, and there were so many of them that they obscured virtually the entire sky.

A burst of white starlight flashed over Han Li's legs as he sprang forward, diving headfirst into the throngs of puppets as he slashed his scimitar horizontally through the air.

The dozens of puppets directly in front of him were instantly sliced into two at the waist, and at the same time, he kicked out with his legs, unleashing a wave of leg projections that forced back the puppets pouncing at him from the left and the right.

Once again, his back was left completely unguarded with the exception of his True Extreme Film, and a string of loud thumps rang out as Han Li was sent flying forward by the attacks aimed at his back.

His True Extreme Film shuddered violently, and his complexion paled ever so slightly.

He gave a muffled groan as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and continued onward without pause, crashing his way through several more dozen puppets to finally burst his way out of the encirclement.

However, he had only managed to travel several thousand feet before the next volley of arrows arrived.

Once again, he employed the same tactic, swatting away the arrows in three directions while leaving his back unguarded.

Close to half a day flew by in a flash.

At this point, Han Li had already withstood countless attacks with his True Extreme Film, and even with his immense powers, he was beginning to feel the strain. His complexion had turned rather pale, and his True Extreme Film had also become far dimmer than before.

Shi Chuankong had recovered somewhat after taking some pills, but he was still in no condition to fight, so he could look on with an urgent expression.

The area of the wreckage down below was far more massive than they imagined, and even now, there was still no end in sight as tens of thousands of puppets converged toward them from all directions.

In addition to three original types of puppets, a mace-wielding giant ape puppet had also been thrown into the mix. There weren't that many of them, but they were extraordinarily strong and fast and also seemed to possess higher intelligence than their counterparts, thereby making them far more difficult to deal with.

Right at this moment, another volley of arrows was fired from down below, and this time, it was interspersed with black rocks that had been hurled by the giant ape puppets.

Han Li swung his scimitar through the air to deflect the arrows and rocks while also darting from side to side to take evasive measures.

At this point, his True Extreme Film was far weaker than before, so he didn't dare to withstand any more attacks, and as a result, his speed was significantly hampered.

Right at this moment, a massive blue shadow came rising up rapidly from down below, and it was none other than one of the giant ape puppets, which was at least twice the size of the other puppets.

The giant ape puppet paid no heed to the countless arrows flying through the air around it as it swung its mace viciously at Han Li's back right as he was evading the oncoming arrows.

Chapter 942: Escape

Han Li seemed to have already anticipated this, and the profound acupoints on his legs flashed momentarily as he darted several feet to the side, evading the oncoming attack.

At the same time, he slashed his scimitar through the air, and a streak of white light flashed past as the giant ape puppet's head flew up into the air, while its body came tumbling down from above.

It appeared that Han Li had slain the giant ape puppet with ease, but it had come at a cost, and he was struck by several arrows and a large rock in the process.

The True Extreme Film around Han Li's body flickered erratically as all of the oncoming projectiles shattered upon impact, and the arrows weren't all that difficult to deal with, but the rock was imbued with tremendous power that surged into Han Li's body through his True Extreme Film, striking him with a great deal of discomfort.

However, he couldn't afford to be delayed here, so he took a deep breath before launching himself forward again.

Looking at the endless sea of puppets down below, Han Li couldn't help but be overcome by a sense of despair.

Even with his exceptional physical prowess, he was at a point where he was having to scrape the bottom of the barrel. If he couldn't escape from this place soon, then this would become his final resting place.

"Leave me behind and go on your own. You should be able to make it out of here without me weighing you down," Shi Chuankong suddenly said.

Han Li offered no response as he continued to fly forward while parrying away all of the oncoming arrows.

The latest volley of arrows had only just passed when more puppets sprang up from the ground to pounce at the two of them, and Han Li displayed no fear at all as he charged straight into the wall of puppets up ahead.

The starlight radiating from his body wasn't as bright as before, but he was still extremely fast and agile, weaving his way through the puppets like a fish in water while occasionally cutting down some of the puppets that he was unable to avoid.

At this point, he had already become very well-versed in dealing with these puppets' attacks.

He darted to the side to evade an attack from a tiger-headed puppet, then decapitated it with a swift slash of his scimitar.

However, right at this moment, two giant ape puppets suddenly burst onto the scene roughly ten feet in front of him, and they swung their maces at him with all their might, one from the left, and one from the right.

At the same time, two more giant ape puppets appeared behind him before also swinging their maces at him from behind.

The four puppets were working together in perfect tandem, and their four maces were all coming at Han Li from different directions, cutting off all avenues for retreat or evasion.

A cold look appeared on Han Li's face as he lashed out with his white scimitar, unleashing countless blade projections to oppose the four oncoming maces.

A string of loud booms rang out as the four maces were knocked back along with their puppet wielders.

However, Han Li's body also shuddered violently from the impact, and his face was completely drained of color. The starlight around his body was flickering erratically, and it was taking quite an effort just to remain aloft in the air.

However, right at this moment, the crimson key in the front of his robe suddenly released a burst of crimson light that surged into his body, transforming into a burst of warmth that quickly passed through all of his meridians.

This surge of warmth seemed to be a cross between bloodline power and starpower, and it was extremely immense.

The exhaustion that Han Li had accumulated up to this point instantly faded away, and in the blink of an eye, he was restored to peak condition.

This was naturally a massively pleasant surprise, and Han Li was ecstatic as he unleashed a flurry of blade projections that were far brighter and larger than before to cut down all of the puppets within a radius of over a hundred feet.

All of the oncoming puppets were instantly eradicated, including the four giant ape puppets.

Shi Chuankong was astonished to see this, and he asked, "How..."

"Now's not the time to talk," Han Li interjected. "Let's get out of here first."

Having been restored to peak condition, Han Li's speed was drastically enhanced, and before long, the two of them had been flying for several more hours.

A fiery red desert appeared up ahead, marking the conclusion of this set of gargantuan ruins.

"We've finally reached the end!" Han Li exclaimed in an ecstatic manner.

Right at this moment, all of the puppets down below let loose furious roars as they began attacking with all their might.

The snake-headed puppets were firing off arrows without pause, while the other puppets sprang up into the air to attack Han Li and Shi Chuankong, completely unconcerned about being harmed by the arrows.

In response, the starlight radiating from Han Li's body brightened significantly, and he sped through the puppet army as a white shadow, slicing through their ranks with ease.

It didn't take long before Han Li flew out of the army of puppets before entering the red desert, and for some reason, the puppets didn't seem to dare to step into the desert.

They stopped in their tracks on the edge of the desert, roaring in fury and indignation at Han Li and Shi Chuankong until they vanished into the distance.

After entering the red desert, Han Li flew onward for a while longer, and only after verifying that the puppet army had indeed refrained from coming after them did he heave a sigh of relief before descending onto the ground.

The ground below was radiating scorching heat, causing the nearby air to ripple slightly, but this amount of heat had no effect on Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

"This place is quite hot, but it shouldn't be enough to pose much of a hazard to those puppets. I wonder why they suddenly stopped," Shi Chuankong mused with a puzzled expression.

"I think they're not incapable of coming after us, but they don't dare to for some reason," Han Li said.

"That sounds about right," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"By the way, why did you warn me not to fly into the yellow clouds earlier?" Han Li asked.

Even above the red desert, there was still a dense layer of yellow clouds up above, and flashes of white light could be seen within it.

"There's a very powerful restriction in those clouds, and it'll attack anyone that ventures into them," Shi Chuankong explained as he pulled a dagger.

The dagger had countless flashing star runes engraved upon it, and it was a pseudo-star artifact that was not inferior to Han Li's scimitar.

With a flick of his wrist, the dagger was sent flying up into the air as a streak of white light, and it quickly vanished into the yellow clouds.

The clouds above immediately began to churn violently, following all of the white light within them converged before transforming into thick bolts of white lightning that struck the dagger from all directions, instantly reducing it to nothingness.

The white lightning then quickly dissipated and reverted back into the same white light as before, while Han Li looked on with an astonished expression.

Earlier, he had been rather curious about the yellow clouds and had considered venturing into them, but ultimately decided against it.

Thankfully, he had made the right decision. Otherwise, those bolts of white lightning would've been enough to at least severely wound him, if not kill him on the spot.

"How do you know about this, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked.

"It was mentioned in the information that Pokong gave me," Shi Chuankong replied as a sullen look appeared in his eyes.

"It seems like His Highness is very familiar with what things are like in the Great Ruins. Has he been here before as well?" Han Li asked.

Shi Chuankong faltered slightly upon hearing this, then shook his head as he replied, "I'm not sure."

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face, and he didn't ask any further questions.

"This place seems to be relatively safe, so let's take a rest here before continuing onward," Shi Chuankong suggested, and he was still looking very pale and weary.

Han Li nodded in response.

After such an extended period on the run, he was also feeling quite tired.

The two of them scoured the surrounding environment to ensure that there weren't any hazards lurking nearby, then took some pills before sitting down to rest.

Three days flew by in a flash.

"How are your injuries, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked.

"I'm mostly recovered now. At the very least, I can move around just fine, and I'll be fully recovered soon," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"Good. If we encounter any enemies from here onward, just leave them to me and focus on your own recovery," Han Li said.

The two of them then took a moment to discuss how they were going to proceed. They didn't know what was waiting for them deeper in this red desert, but they clearly couldn't return to those ruins, so ultimately, they decided to venture further into the red desert.

The desert was astonishingly massive, and even after traveling for over two months, they still hadn't reached the end.

They encountered no dangers or treasures along the way, and there was nothing to be seen aside from boundless seas of red sand.

"I didn't think there would be such an enormous place in the Great Ruins," Han Li remarked as he sped onward.

"Could it be that we're currently heading toward the edge of the Great Ruins?" Shi Chuankong asked with tightly furrowed brows as he rushed along behind Han Li.

The abundance of starpower in the Great Ruins had a very positive effect on injury recovery, and over the past two months, he had already made a full recovery.

"I don't think so. I can sense that the starpower here is more abundant than before, so we should be going deeper into the Great Ruins. Besides, even if we change directions now, there's no guarantee we'll be on the right track, so let's just keep going. Surely we'll get out of here eventually," Han Li said, and Shi Chuankong nodded in agreement.

All of a sudden, Han Li stopped in his tracks and cast his gaze forward with an elated look in his eyes.

Chapter 943: A Second Altar

"Have you discovered something, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Chuankong hurriedly asked.

"I did indeed discover something. Come with me," Han Li replied as he quickened his pace, and around fifteen minutes later, the two of them drew to a halt as they cast their eyes forward to discover a massive river at the end of the desert up ahead.

The river was close to ten kilometers wide, and its water was crimson in color. Countless waves were sweeping over its surface as it churned along, and upon arriving on the riverbank, Han Li was surprised to discover that the water was intensely hot, much like flowing lava.

"What a strange river... I think we should follow it downstream. Given how strange this river is, there must be something interesting downstream," Shi Chuankong suggested.

"My thoughts exactly," Han Li replied with a nod.

With that, the two of them changed course, making their way along the crimson river in a downstream direction, and after traveling for or five days, a massive oasis appeared up ahead.

Most of the plants on this oasis were also crimson in color, while the rest were white.

The vegetation in the oasis was very tall and dense, and the combination of crimson and white presented a stunning sight to behold.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were quite elated to see this oasis, but they didn't make any rash moves, and only after restraining their own auras did they step onto the oasis for a closer look.

After walking for a while, Shi Chuankong suddenly pointed into the dense forestry up ahead as he yelled, "Look over there, Fellow Daoist Li!"

Han Li turned in that direction to discover a footprint, one that appeared to be quite fresh.

"Looks like someone's gotten here before us. We don't know if they're friend or foe, so be careful," Han Li warned through voice transmission, and Shi Chuankong nodded in response.

The two of them continued onward while keeping an eye on the ground below, and they discovered more and more similar footprints.

Judging from the number of footprints, it appeared that a group of four people had ventured into this place before them.

The two of them quickly passed through the lush forest, and a giant city appeared up ahead.

The city was filled with buildings with sharp, spiky rooves that extended up toward the heavens like giant swords, and all of them were entirely crimson in color.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with each other, then made their way in through the half-open city gates.

The buildings inside the city were displaying some signs of decay, but they were in far better condition than the ones in the earlier set of ruins, and they were all mostly intact.

The two of them conducted a brief search of the buildings near the city gates, only to discover that most of them were completely empty. Furthermore, there were signs that those buildings had already been searched, presumably by the group that had arrived earlier.

"Aren't these Great Ruins supposed to be filled with countless treasures? We've already been in here for quite some time, yet we haven't managed to find anything aside from a pair of star artifacts," Shi Chuankong grumbled.

"Two star artifacts is already quite a bountiful haul. It's clear that this place has already been searched, so let's go straight to the center of the city. Hopefully, we'll be able to find some things there, but make sure to be careful," Han Li replied with a smile, and Shi Chuankong nodded in response.

The two of them continued deeper into the city, and it wasn't a very large place, so it didn't take them long to reach the center of the city, at which point they encountered a large plaza with a giant altar standing upon it.

The altar was also entirely crimson in color, and it was quite similar in appearance to the gray altar in the earlier set of ruins.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were hiding behind a building near the entrance of the altar, which was wide open, and Shi Chuankong said in an eager, "This altar looks very similar to the one from before, so it should have some good things inside. Should we go in and have a look?"

"Sure, let's go in. We didn't encounter the group of people that arrived before us on the way here, so they've most likely entered the altar as well. Hence, we have to constantly be on our guard," Han Li said.

"Rest assured, I'll be careful," Shi Chuankong promised.

"Let's go," Han Li said, and the two of them rushed out from behind the building before making their way into the altar.

Not long after they entered the altar, a glowing, white ovular design appeared on the ground at the entrance.

The design was formed by eight star runes, every single one of which was extremely complex, far more so than the ones that Han Li had learned from Mistress Liu Hua.

The ovular design slowly lit up, releasing rays of white light that converged toward the center to form what appeared to be an eye.

The eye took a glance deep into the altar through the entrance, then quickly faded away.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were completely oblivious to this, and after making their way through the entrance, they immediately began traveling deeper into the altar.

Beyond the entrance was a passageway that was thousands of feet in length, and just like the passageway in the gray altar, the walls on either side were also riddled with array patterns, forming a restriction that severely hampered spiritual sense.

The restriction here was slightly weaker than the one in the gray altar, so Han Li was still able to release his spiritual sense around twenty to thirty feet out of his body.

After passing through the passageway, a giant hall that was over ten thousand feet in size appeared up ahead.

The hall was quite brightly lit, and it was completely empty, but the walls were dotted with around two hundred to three hundred rectangular openings, each of which was several dozen feet tall, and all of them were also empty.

Their contents were currently spilled out onto the ground in the hall. It was a series of humanoid crimson puppets, all of which had already been dismantled.

On top of that, the ground was riddled with pits and craters, clearly indicating that a battle had recently taken place here.

These crimson puppets had full sets of organs, and large puddles of silver fluid had flowed out of their bodies and onto the ground, just like the black ape puppet that Han Li had encountered in the past.

In contrast, the snake, wolf, tiger-headed puppets from the set of vast ruins had no internal organs and weren't constructed with anywhere near the same degree of intricacy.

Han Li picked up a puppet fragment from the ground before giving it a close examination.

The fragment seemed to have been crafted from some type of red jade material, and even though it was only a fragment, it was still flashing with faint red light, indicating that it was quite a prized material. The material was far superior to what had been used to craft the black ape puppet, so these puppets had most likely been more powerful than the black ape puppet as well.

Thankfully, these puppets had already been destroyed. Otherwise, having to face so many of these puppets at once would've been quite a pain.

Having said that, the fact that the people ahead were able to dismantle these puppets indicated that they were definitely not to be taken lightly.

With that in mind, Han Li exchanged a glance with Shi Chuankong, and judging from the grim look on the latter's face, he had clearly also thought of the same thing.

The two of them didn't linger for long here as they continued deeper into the hall.

At the back of the giant hall was a doorway, beyond which was a dimly lit passageway that led even deeper into the altar.

As Han Li walked along, he discovered more puppet fragments, and a perplexed look flashed through his eyes upon seeing this.

These puppets had been completely smashed to bits. It didn't look like they had fallen in battle. Instead, it appeared more like someone was trying to search for something in these puppets, so they had hacked the puppets to bits after dismantling them.

What in the bodies of these puppets could've been worth searching so meticulously for?

The two of them quickly passed through the hall and into the passageway at the back.

Han Li carefully made his way down the passageway while constantly scouring his surroundings.

Not only was the passageway constantly twisting and turning, it was also sloping downward.

After rounding a corner, they arrived at a crossroads with three identical-looking paths before them.

All three paths were quite dimly lit, so it was impossible to see very far into them.

Shi Chuankong turned to Han Li and asked, "Which one should we take?"

Han Li swept his gaze over the three paths, then quickly settled his gaze onto the middle one.

He had spotted several faint footprints leading into the middle path, while the two had clearly not been frequented.

"Let's take the right one or the left one. The people ahead of us have already gone down the middle path, so even if there are treasures to be found, they would've already been taken. Hence, we have better chances of reaping spoils by taking one of the other paths," Han Li said, and Shi Chuankong raised no objections.

After a brief discussion, the two of them stepped into the passageway on the right.

The passageway was wide enough for four or five people to fit through side by side, and it only continued to widen further down.

Rays of white light were seeping out through the gaps in the walls of the passageway, so it was a little brighter than before.

All of a sudden, a sharp shriek rang out from up ahead, and both Han Li and Shi Chuankong instantly stopped in their tracks upon hearing this.

Before the two of them had a chance to do anything, a white-robed man suddenly sped onto the scene like lightning, wielding a sword of white light that it thrust directly at Han Li's chest.

The speed of the attack was quite alarming, even for Han Li, and he hurriedly took a step to the side to evade the attack.

At the same time, his white scimitar appeared in his grasp, and he slashed it through the air, striking the white-robed man on the chest in the instant that the two of them passed each other by.

However, to Han Li's surprise, his scimitar merely passed straight through the white-robed man's body, and it was as if he had struck nothing but empty air.

The white-robed man remained completely unaffected as it sped directly toward Shi Chuankong, who was standing behind Han Li, and he pierced his sword directly at Shi Chuankong's chest.

Shi Chuankong was rather taken aback, but his reactions weren't slow, and he hurriedly dodged to the side to evade the attack.

The white-robed man was extraordinarily fast, but his reactions seemed to be a little dull, and after failing to strike his targets, he sped directly past Han Li and Shi Chuankong for some distance before stopping in his tracks and turning around to pounce at them once again.

Chapter 944: Subduing the Talisman Spirits

Only then did Han Li and Shi Chuankong manage to catch a clear glimpse of the white-robed man. It was an authoritative figure dressed in a tight-fitting robe, much like the divine generals one would see in mortal temples, and there was a hazy, indistinct appearance about it.

"This is a Heavenly Chief Profound General!" Shi Chuankong exclaimed.

Before Han Li had a chance to ask what that was, the white-robed man was already upon them again, unleashing a flurry of white sword projections in their direction.

Han Li was just about to raise his scimitar to ward off the attacks when Shi Chuankong's urgent voice rang out from beside him.

"Heavenly Chief Profound Generals are capable of switching between tangible and intangible at will, so we won't be able to block its attacks. We have to dodge!"

Han Li hurriedly dodged to the side upon hearing this.

At the same time, he lashed out with his scimitar, unleashing a series of white blade projections, only for them to pass straight through the white-robed man's body once again.

The white-robed man seemed to have been infuriated by Han Li's attacks, and it abandoned Shi Chuankong to come after him, raining down more sword projections upon him as it did so.

The Star Moon Boots on Han Li's feet immediately began to glow as he darted through the air as an indistinct shadow, evading all of the sword projections with relative ease.

The white-robed man let loose a low roar upon seeing this, and it redoubled its efforts, unleashing an even more formidable storm of sword projections that virtually completely inundated Han Li from all directions.

An urgent look appeared in Shi Chuankong's eyes upon seeing this, and he was just about to enter the fray as well when Han Li's calm voice rang out from within the storm of sword projections.

"I can handle this thing on my own. Do you know if these Heavenly Chief Profound Generals have any weaknesses?"

"Heavenly Chief Profound Generals are talisman spirits manifested by Heavenly General Talismans. In the Devil Realm, we would be able to contain it using a sealing ability, but they're very difficult to suppress in the Scalptia Spatial Domain," Shi Chuankong replied with tightly furrowed brows, unable to think of a way to subdue the Heavenly Chief Profound General.

"I see," Han Li replied as a confident smile appeared on his face, and all of a sudden, a streak of translucent light shot forth through the air, following which the storm of sword projections around him abruptly faded away.

As a result, Han Li was revealed with a hand plunged into the white-robed man's chest, while the white-robed man seemed to be completely immobilized and rooted to the spot.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li pulled his hand out of the white-robed man's chest, revealing a palm-sized white talisman that was glowing faintly in his grasp.

The talisman was twisting and writhing incessantly, but it was unable to struggle free from the spiritual sense chains around it.

After the talisman was pulled out of its body, the white-robed man imploded into countless specks of white light, while Shi Chuankong took an elated glance at the spiritual sense chains around the talisman as he asked, "How did you do that, Brother Li? Are those chains formed by your spiritual sense?"

"It's a spiritual sense ability of mine," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

"I see. Thank heavens you had this ability up your sleeve. Otherwise, we would've truly been in trouble. This talisman has to be sealed or destroyed. Otherwise, it'll automatically draw upon the energy in its environment to manifest another Heavenly Chief Profound General," Shi Chuankong cautioned.

"It would be a waste to destroy just a precious talisman, so I'll seal it away for now," Han Li said.

Even though the talisman was trapped in the spiritual sense chains, he could sense that it was constantly absorbing the starpower in the surrounding environment in an attempt to break free.

All of a sudden, the spiritual sense chains around the talisman began to glow radiantly at his behest, transforming into a seal design that vanished into the talisman in a flash.

This was a sealing secret technique that he had developed using his spiritual sense chains by referencing Feng Tiandu's Origin Separation Yin Devil Arts.

The Heavenly General Talisman's struggles instantly ceased.

Han Li was very pleased to see this, and he stowed the talisman away.

The Heavenly Chief Profound General was quite formidable, and even in the outside world, it would be equivalent to a Golden Immortal cultivator. On top of that, it was also able to automatically absorb energy from the environment to sustain itself, so if he could refine the talisman, then he would essentially have an infinitely self-regenerating Golden Immortal Stage subordinate.

"Come to think of it, I've never heard of Heavenly General Talismans back in the True Immortal Realm. Could it be that this is a talisman unique to the Devil Realm?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not sure, perhaps so. I've seen records of Heavenly General Talismans in some books before, but I'd never seen it for myself prior to this," Shi Chuankong replied.

After that brief interlude, the two of them continued deeper into the altar.

As the two of them continued onward, the passageway up ahead became wider and brighter, and they could sense a faint burst of peculiar energy fluctuations in the air.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a cautious glance with each other before continuing onward.

After walking for around fifteen minutes, they rounded a corner, arriving in a square stone hall.

There were five translucent white stone pillars in the hall, all of which were giving off radiant starlight, making one feel as if they were surrounded by stars.

Aside from the pillar on the very left, the other four pillars each had a Heavenly General Talisman adhered to them, and in particular, the one in the middle was clearly far larger than the other three.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up slightly upon seeing this, but right at his moment, the four talismans seemed to have detected their arrival, and they began to glow radiantly while flying off from the stone pillars.

Immediately thereafter, the four talismans vanished in a flash, transforming into four white-robed men.

Three of them were identical to the one that Han Li had just sealed away, but the largest of the of the four Heavenly General Talismans had transformed into a Heavenly Chief Profound General that was far larger in stature than the other three, and it was also clad in a suit of white armor with a jade belt around its waist, as well as a long halberd in its grasp.

Furthermore, there was clearly a more intelligent gleam in its eyes.

The four Heavenly Chief Profound Generals pounced at Han Li and Shi Chuankong right as the former was about to unleash his spiritual sense chains again, and the armored general was particularly fast, reaching Han Li in the blink of an eye before swinging its halberd down upon his head.

Boundless killing intent erupted out of the halberd, crashing down upon Han Li and Shi Chuankong, making both of them feel as if they had fallen into a pit of quicksand.

Even though the halberd was crashing down upon Han Li, it had conjured up another projection that was simultaneously sweeping toward Shi Chuankong.

The attack was too fast for Han Li to dodge, so in response, two thick, translucent chains shot out of his glabella, with one of them wrapping itself around the oncoming halberd, while the other one appeared above Shi Chuankong's head in a flash.

Two loud clangs rang out as the spiritual sense chains were shattered upon contact, and the halberd and its projection continued to swing down, but the chains had bought Han Li some time.

He let loose a loud roar as all of the profound acupoints on his body lit up, releasing a tremendous aura that tore the surrounding space apart.

"You don't have a way to deal with these Heavenly Chief Profound Generals, so get out of here for now!" Han Li said as he pushed Shi Chuankong out of the hall, then abruptly vanished from the spot himself.

Immediately thereafter, the white halberd came crashing down onto the spot where he had just been standing, smashing a deep crater into the ground.

The armored man instantly swung around, then shot forth toward one of the other Heavenly Chief Profound Generals as a white shadow.

Right at this moment, Han Li appeared behind that Heavenly Chief Profound General without any warning, then plunged a hand into its body like lightning.

The Heavenly Chief Profound General's body imploded, and Han Li pulled out a white talisman that was surrounded by spiritual sense chains before vanishing from the spot once again.

Han Li had only just disappeared when the armored general's halberd came crashing down to smash another huge crater into the ground.

"You're very fast, but still a little lacking compared with me, so why don't you surrender and become my subordinate?" Han Li suggested as he appeared beside one of the five stone pillars, following which his spiritual sense chains formed a seal that vanished into the Heavenly General Talisman in his grasp.

The talisman instantly settled down, allowing him to stow it away.

The armored man let loose a furious roar, and all of the starpower in the nearby space converged toward it in a frenzy before surging into its body.

The five stone pillars also lit up even further, releasing rays of dazzling white light, all of which were giving off formidable starpower fluctuations.

In the blink of an eye, the armored man's body had swelled by around 30% of its original size.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately lashed out at the five stone pillars, shattering them in rapid succession.

As a result, the white light radiating from them faded away, and the armored man ceased to expand any further.

The armored man was even more infuriated upon seeing this, and it let loose a thunderous roar that caused the entire hall to tremble violently.

Immediately thereafter, it vanished from the spot before reappearing in front of Han Li, moving even faster than before as it swung its halberd down upon Han Li's head.

Han Li flew back in retreat while several spiritual sense chains shot out of his glabella alongside a white sword projection.

A burst of tremendous power erupted out of the Spiritual Sense Sword, snapping the halberd into two before crashing into the armored man's body.

A long crack was instantly inflicted onto its body, and it was almost split into two down the middle as it shot back in alarm.

A surprised look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

He had only unleashed his Spiritual Sense Sword on a whim, and he certainly wasn't expecting it to be so effective against the armored man.

Chapter 945: Joining Forces Again

"You're not getting away!" Han Li yelled as he abruptly vanished from the spot, only to then immediately reappear before the armored man.

A series of spiritual sense chains were wrapped around his arm, and he plunged his hand straight into the armored man's chest.

Having sustained such severe wounds, the armored man's speed was severely hampered, so it failed to evade Han Li's grasping hand, and it was instantly rooted to the spot.

Han Li pulled his hand out of its body, holding the largest of the five white talismans in his grasp, and he immediately sealed it away.

The armored man was far more powerful than the other Heavenly Chief Profound Generals, possessing powers that weren't inferior to those of a High Zenith cultivator, so Han Li was naturally very pleased to have been able to subdue it.

Right at this moment, the two remaining Heavenly Chief Profound Generals pounced at Han Li like lightning, slashing their swords into his body right as he was sealing the largest of the five Heavenly General Talismans.

Han Li's body was instantly sliced into two, only to then fade away, revealing it to have been nothing more than an afterimage.

Immediately thereafter, a pair of hands reached into the chests of the two Heavenly Chief Profound Generals, pulling out the Heavenly General Talismans inside before prompting sealing them.

The two remaining Heavenly Chief Profound Generals instantly imploded into specks of white light, while Han Li stowed the two talismans away.

Only then did Shi Chuankong re-enter the hall as he praised in an earnest manner, "Impressive as usual, Fellow Daoist Li. It seems like there's no end to your powers."

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Shi. It just so happens that my spiritual sense secret technique is a perfect counter to these things," Han Li replied with a smile before crouching down to inspect the five shattered stone pillars.

It seemed that these stone pillars were capable of gathering starpower, and that was why the five Heavenly General Talismans had been adhered to them to be nurtured.

He searched through the wreckage of the stone pillars for a while, then quickly pulled out five short rods that were each around an inch in length and around the same thickness as a human arm.

Each rod was riddled with engraved star runes, forming what appeared to be a set of star arrays.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this.

He had already developed a decent understanding of the starpower restrictions in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so even though the arrays on the five rods were quite complex, he was still able to roughly make sense of them.

This was a star gathering array that was countless times more profound than the star gathering array that he had learned from the Origin Realm Temple.

Han Li eagerly scoured his gaze over the starpower restrictions on the five rods, then pulled out a jade slip and engraved the arrays on the rods onto it.

He had prepared this jade slip prior to entering the Great Ruins, and it was precisely for this type of scenario.

Unfortunately, he had been a little too rough in his destruction of the stone pillars earlier, so the rods had been damaged in many parts, resulting in many of the runes on them being erased.

Even so, this set of starpower restrictions was still going to be immensely helpful to him.

After recording the damaged arrays onto his jade slip, Han Li continued onward with Shi Chuankong by his side.

From there, they didn't encounter any further attacks, and it didn't take long before they reached the end of the passageway, where a black staircase that was hundreds of steps tall stood before them.

At the foot of the staircase was a glowing, white exit, and a giant hall could be seen through this opening.

A string of resounding booms were ringing out incessantly up ahead, indicating that a battle seemed to be taking place inside the hall.

"Stay here for now, Fellow Daoist Shi, I'll go take a look at what's happening in there," Han Li said through voice transmission.

Shi Chuankong knew that Han Li's concealment techniques were superior to his own, so he raised no objections and nodded in response.

Han Li immediately channeled his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique and snuck over to the exit before peering out into the hall beyond.

The previous hall was already quite large, but this one was downright enormous, over a hundred times the area of the previous hall.

The ground and walls of this hall were all dark green in color, and there were two rows of massive stone pillars in the hall, one on the left, and one on the right.

The two rows of stone pillars ran straight down the length of the hall, and even with Han Li's eyesight, he was only just barely able to make out a tightly shut stone gate at the end of the hall.

Aside from that, there was nothing else in the hall, giving it a very empty and spacious appearance.

At this moment, there were two parties engaged in a fierce battle inside.

One one side were around a dozen crimson humanoid puppets and three Heavenly Chief Profound Generals, while the other party consisted of four people, all of whom were familiar to Han Li, namely Chen Yang, Xuanyuan Xing, Sun Tu, and Fang Chan.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this.

The crimson puppets were each around seventy to eighty feet tall, cutting extremely imposing figures, and even though they weren't armed with any weapons, their bodies contained tremendous power, and the very space around them trembled in the face of their attacks.

Furthermore, they seemed to be very adept at working together, and at this moment, they were standing side by side in a row, unleashing attacks that formed waves of formidable power to prevent Chen Yang and the others from advancing any further.

As for the Heavenly Chief Profound Generals, all of them were comparable in power to the armored general that Han Li had just subdued, and thanks to their insubstantial bodies, they were unaffected by the waves of power unleashed by the crimson puppets as they attacked Chen Yang and the others at will.

It was clear that Chen Yang's group was trying to reach the stone gate at the end of the hall, but they weren't able to make any progress against these puppets and talisman spirits.

The puppets didn't pose much of a threat, but the Heavenly Chief Profound General were a huge pain to deal with, and out of the four, only Sun Tu possessed a bone sword that was etched with black patterns that seemed to be pose some threat to the Heavenly Chief Profound Generals.

The black patterns on the bone sword were releasing rings of black ripples that proliferated throughout the hall, and they had no effect on Chen Yang and the others or the crimson puppets, but as soon as the three Heavenly Chief Profound Generals came into contact with the black ripples, they would instantly be slowed down significantly.

If it wasn't for that, Chen Yang and the others would've already sustained injuries from the Heavenly Chief Profound Generals.

The three Heavenly Chief Profound General were swinging their halberds rapidly through the air, unleashing flurries of white halberd projections that converged to form a large net, which descended upon Chen Yang and the others.

Sun Tu let loose a low roar as he slashed his bone sword through the air, and a metallic clang rang out as a giant black sword projection struck the net of halberd projections.

The net was instantly sliced apart, but the black sword projection was also destroyed, and the three Heavenly Chief Profound Generals and Sun Tu were both forced back into retreat.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the black bone sword in Sun Tu's hand with an intrigued look in his eyes.

The black patterns on the bone sword were giving off a burst of peculiar sealing power fluctuations, so it was no wonder that it was able to ward off the Heavenly Chief Profound Generals attacks.

"Fellow Daoist Li, Fellow Daoist Shi, come out and show yourselves. It's rather rude to watch from the sidelines like this," Sun Tu suddenly said as he turned his gaze to the entrance of the hall.

Chen Yang and the others displayed no surprise upon hearing this, and it seemed that they were already aware of Han Li and Shi Chuankong's presence.

Han Li was quite taken aback to hear this. He had thought that his aura was completely concealed by his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique, and Shi Chuankong was currently thousands of feet away. Spiritual sense was severely restricted here, so how had Sun Tu and the others discovered them?

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li beckoned to Shi Chuankong, and the latter rushed over to join him, following which both of them stepped into the hall together. Seeing as they had already been discovered, there was no point in hiding any longer.

"I'm very impressed that you were able to discover us, Fellow Daoist Sun Tu. May I ask how you were able to detect our presence?" Han Li asked with a smile.

In contrast with Sun Tu and the others, the puppets and talisman spirits were clearly quite surprised by the emergence of Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

"It's just a little trick that's really not worth flaunting. Seeing as your Green Goat City and our White Rock City have already forged an alliance, why don't we all join forces here?" Sun Tu invited with a smile.

"Our earlier agreement still stands, Fellow Daoist Li. The Great Ruins are fraught with peril, so it would be far too dangerous for the two of you to continue on your own. I'm sure there must be some precious treasures to be found in here, so let's take care of these puppets and talisman spirits, then split the treasures inside evenly among ourselves," Chen Yang said.

Meanwhile, Fang Chan was looking out behind Han Li and Shi Chuankong, seemingly searching for something, and a hint of disappointment flashed through his eyes when he discovered that there was no one behind them.

Shi Chuankong could tell that these crimson puppets and Heavenly Chief Profound Generals were far too formidable for the two of them to deal with, so he was also quite tempted to join forces with Sun Tu and the others.

However, he didn't say anything as he turned his gaze to Han Li, clearly content to follow his lead.

"I'm very flattered that you think so highly of me. In that case, I'd be happy to join you," Han Li replied with a smile after a brief moment of contemplation.

Meanwhile, the crimson puppets and Heavenly Chief Profound Generals were already pouncing at them again.

"Alright, in that case, let's get rid of these pesky things together. The longer we're delayed here, the greater the chance that something could go wrong, so let's not hold back. If you have any tricks up your sleeve, now would be the time to reveal them," Chen Yang declared.

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and three short yellow spears appeared in his grasp, all of which were etched with peculiar lightning-shaped patterns.

The three spears were then hurled through the air as a trio of yellow shadows, and they displayed incredible penetrative power, piercing through the waves of power unleashed by the crimson puppets before embedding themselves into the bodies of three of the puppets.

In the next instant, three loud explosions rang out as bursts of white lightning erupted out of the spears, forming three balls of white lightning that were each around ten feet in size.

The three puppets were instantly torn apart, with their fragments flying in all directions.

With these three puppets eliminated, the wall of force unleashed by the rest of the puppets was instantly significantly weakened.

Chapter 946: Different Objectives

"I'll handle these three talisman spirits, all of you can focus on eradicating those puppets," Sun Tu said, then immediately lashed out with his bone sword, unleashing a flurry of black sword projections that fanned out like a peacock spreading its canopy.

With Sun Tu engaging the three Heavenly Chief Profound Generals in battle, Han Li and the others immediately pounced at the remaining crimson puppets.

At this moment, Xuanyuan Xing was wielding a pair of black staves, each of which was around five feet in length. There were strips of yellow fabric tied all over the staves, much like the mourning sticks used in mortal funerals.

All of a sudden, a expelled a mouthful of blood, which split up into two before fusing into the mourning sticks, which instantly began to glow black.

As Xuanyuan Xing swung his arms through the air, countless staff projections were unleashed, sweeping toward the crimson puppets amid a chorus of ghastly howls.

The movements of the crimson puppets were slowed down slightly, seemingly affected by these ghastly sounds.

At the same time, Fang Chan inhaled deeply before releasing a burst of white soundwaves that erupted out of his mouth and nose before also sweeping toward the crimson puppets.

As a result, the puppets' movements were hampered even further, and the waves of force that they were generating were weakened once again.

Han Li pounced on this opportunity to fly through the air while lashing out with his white scimitar, unleashing a mountainous blade projection that was over a hundred feet in length to strike the opposing waves of force.

Shi Chuankong immediately followed suit, swinging his purple staff through the air to unleash a thick staff projection that also struck the waves of force.

The waves of power generated by the crimson puppets were already far weaker than before, and an opening was instantly smashed into them by Han Li and Shi Chuankong's attacks.

The two of them were ecstatic to see this, and they rushed in through the opening, arriving behind the crimson puppets in the blink of an eye.

"Well done, fellow daoists!" Chen Yang yelled in an ecstatic voice. "Once we dismantle these puppets, our work will be almost done!"

Radiant white light erupted out of his fists as he unleashed a flurry of countless white fist projections that rained down upon the puppets, while Han Li and Shi Chuankong attacked the puppets from behind.

At this point, there were only ten of these puppets left, and one of them, which was clearly larger than the others, suddenly let loose a low roar.

Two of the puppets immediately swung around to face Han Li and Shi Chuankong, and while the remaining eight puppets continued to lash out with their fists and feet, creating a massive net of force that stood in the path of Chen Yang's trio.

Ferocious winds swept through the entire hall, preventing the trio from getting any closer.

Meanwhile, crimson light flashed over the fists of the two puppets that were pouncing at Han Li and Shi Chuankong, and two bursts of crimson light erupted out of their fists before plunging into the oncoming storm of blade and staff projections.

Two resounding booms rang out as the blade and staff projections were all destroyed upon impact, while the two puppets reached out like lightning to grab onto the white scimitar and the purple staff.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he tugged forcefully on the hilt of his scimitar while pushing off against the ground with his feet, instantly launching himself up into the air before jumping onto the crimson puppet's shoulder.

Before the puppet had a chance to react, he threw a vicious elbow strike into its head, and a dull thump rang out as the puppet's head instantly exploded like a watermelon, sending large volumes of silver fluid erupting in all directions.

Han Li then used the shoulder of the headless puppet as a launching pad to send himself flying at the other eight puppets.

However, right at this moment, a white halberd came hurtling at his head from above.

The halberd was giving off an extremely sharp aura, leaving a visible gash in the space in its wake.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and the profound acupoints on his legs lit up as he sped away roughly ten feet to the side to evade the attack.

Immediately thereafter, a Heavenly Chief Profound General descended from above to stand in his path.

Han Li took a glance in Sun Tu's direction to discover that the latter was already struggling immensely to deal with the other two Heavenly Chief Profound Generals.

A pleased smile appeared on Han Li's face as he darted forward like lightning, reaching the Heavenly Chief Profound General in the blink of an eye.

The Heavenly Chief Profound General seemed to have caught off guard by this, but it didn't take any evasive measures as it swung its halberd directly at Han Li's head.

An alarmed look appeared on Chen Yang's face as he yelled from afar, "Get out of the way, Fellow Daoist Li! The attacks from those talisman spirits can phase through all physical objects, so you can't block them!"

However, Han Li made no attempt to evade the attack. Instead, radiant white light erupted out of the profound acupoints on his legs, encompassing the entire area in a radius of over a hundred feet around himself and the Heavenly Chief Profound General, making it impossible to see what was happening inside.

A dull thump rang out from within the white light, followed by the sound of a small explosion, and by the time the white light faded, Han Li was revealed to be on his own, with the Heavenly Chief Profound General nowhere to be seen.

Everyone in the hall aside from Shi Chuankong was very surprised to see this.

Han Li paid no heed to everyone's reactions as he abruptly vanished from the spot, then reappeared behind the eight puppets in a wraith-like manner before lashing out with his fists.

Five dull thumps rang out in rapid succession, and five puppets, including the largest of the bunch, had their heads smashed to bits, following which their mountainous bodies collapsed to the ground.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and it took Chen Yang's trio a moment to react before they erupted into cheers and pounced at the three remaining puppets.

Meanwhile, Han Li turned his gaze to Sun Tu's direction before vanishing from the spot once again.

In the next instant, he reappeared behind a Heavenly Chief Profound General before reaching out one hand, and once again, a burst of radiant white light erupted out of his profound acupoints to encompass the Heavenly Chief Profound General's entire body.

He wanted to keep his spiritual sense chains a secret from everyone, so he was going out of his way to conceal what he was doing.

Sun Tu was knocked back by the tremendous force that had erupted out of Han Li's hand, and by the time he steadied himself, the white light had disappeared along with the Heavenly Chief Profound General.

Han Li then turned his gaze to the final Heavenly Chief Profound General, and an urgent look appeared on Sun Tu's face upon seeing this as the bone sword in his hand began to release radiant black light.

Countless rays of black light instantly erupted out of the bone sword before wrapping themselves around the final Heavenly Chief Profound General like lengths of rope.

Immediately thereafter, a beastly roar rang out from Sun Tu's body, and a cloud of misty black light rose up from his bone sword, then transformed into a hazy, black beasty projection that opened its mouth up wide to devour the Heavenly Chief Profound General whole.

The black beastly projection then instantly vanished alongside the misty black light released by the bone sword, and Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, but didn't say anything.

Meanwhile, the crimson puppets had also been dismantled by Chen Yang and the others, and with that, the battle drew to a conclusion.

A slightly tense silence ensued.

Everyone had just displayed some of their trump cards, and in particular, Han Li had put on a spectacular performance that had astonished everyone. In the wake of these displays of power, a rather peculiar atmosphere had descended upon everyone.

"You two really made all the difference, Fellow Daoist Li, Fellow Daoist Shi. Otherwise, we would've been struggling against those foes for who knows how long," Sun Tu said with a smile, breaking the silence.

The tense atmosphere instantly eased slightly, and everyone else turned their attention to Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

"We just so happened to be passing by, and it seems like the threads of fate have brought all of us together," Han Li replied with a smile of his own.

"If I recall correctly, Fellow Daoist Shi was with City Lord E, right? The two of you seem to be quite familiar with each other, Fellow Daoist Li," Sun Tu remarked.

Before Han Li had a chance to say anything, Chen Yang replied in his stead, "That's a long story. Fellow Daoist Li and Fellow Daoist Shi are indeed acquaintances, but right now, all of us are working together to reap the spoils in these Great Ruins, so our individual personal ties hardly matter."

"By the way, Fellow Daoist Chen just mentioned that there are some precious treasures to be found in here. Could it be that all of you have already discovered something?" Han Li asked.

"Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan and I encountered City Lord Sun and Fellow Daoist Fang at the entrance of this altar, and we were all of the opinion that this seemed like quite an interesting place, one that was harboring precious treasures. Hence, we decided to come in and have a look together. However, as for exactly what can be found in here, that's still yet to be seen," Chen Yang replied.

"Now that Fellow Daoist Li and Fellow Daoist Shi have also joined us, I'm sure nothing will be able to stand in our way," Sun Tu said.

"That was quite a grueling battle, so let's take a short rest here before we continue," Chen Yang suggested as he took a glance at the stone gate at the end of the hall.

Xuanyuan Xing and Fang Chan were both looking rather pale, and they eagerly agreed to this proposal, taking some pills before sitting down with their legs crossed.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong weren't feeling all that tired, but they also sat down to rest, nonetheless.

Meanwhile, Sun Tu made his way over to the crimson puppets, then pulled out a black dagger before hacking one of the puppets to bits, seemingly trying to find something.

Han Li immediately recalled all of the puppet fragments that he had spotted on the way here, and he sat down to rest while secretly keeping an eye on Sun Tu.

Before long, Sun Tu had completely dismembered the puppet, and a hint of elation flashed through his eyes as he pulled out something before immediately stowing it away.

Even though he had acted quite quickly, Han Li was still able to identify that he had pulled out a pea-sized white crystal from the puppet's body.

After that, Sun Tu repeated the process with all of the other puppets, plucking out one white crystal after another.

Everyone rested here for roughly an hour before setting off again, arriving in front of the stone gate.

Chapter 947: A Second Key?

"If everyone's ready, then let's go in," Chen Yang said.

"I can deal with those puppets just fine, but if we encounter more of those talisman spirits, then I'll have to count on you, Fellow Daoist Li," Sun Tu said with a smile.

"Rest assured, City Lord Sun, I'll be sure to do my part," Han Li replied.

Sun Tu nodded in response, then turned to give Fang Chan a look, and the latter immediately pushed the stone gate open before stepping inside, followed by everyone else.

By the time everyone had gone through, Sun Tu swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of tremendous force to close the gate again.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he took a glance at the gate, then swept his gaze across the hall that he had just stepped into.

All of a sudden, all of the giant braziers hanging from the walls and the ceiling of the hall were set alight in unison, illuminating the entire hall with their bright flames.

There was a small basin at the center of the hall, and a strange-looking copper tree was situated there. There were close to twenty branches extending from the trunk of the tree, all of which were riddled with star runes.

What was even more peculiar was that there was a statue clad in a full suit of copper armor hanging from the end of each branch, looking much like a series of bodies that had died by hanging.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as his gaze roamed up the copper tree, and he discovered a bright pillar of white light at the top of the tree, within which was another crimson key.

Shi Chuankong immediately turned to Han Li with a surprised expression upon seeing this, and Han Li shook his head ever so slightly in response, indicating for him not to say anything.

However, right at this moment, the crimson key on the copper tree suddenly began to glow brightly, and Han Li felt a scorching sensation in front of his chest.

The burning heat caught him completely off guard, and he couldn't help but give a muffled groan.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Li?" Chen Yang asked with a puzzled expression, and everyone else immediately turned to him as well.

"I suffered some internal injuries on the way here, and my chest suddenly began throbbing a little, but I'm fine," Han Li explained.

Thankfully, the scorching sensation only lasted for an instant before fading away, and the key that was hidden in his robe didn't release any light, so it didn't attract any extra attention.

"We seem to be relatively safe for now, so why don't you sit down and take a rest, Fellow Daoist Li?" Chen Yang suggested. "If you don't attend to your injuries, they could come back to bite you later."

"That's a good idea," Han Li replied with a nod, then strode over to a corner of the hall before sitting down with his legs crossed.

Shi Chuankong hesitated momentarily upon seeing this, then strode over to his side before sitting down as well.

Meanwhile, Chen Yang turned his gaze to the crimson key on top of the copper tree with a solemn look in his eyes.

"This must be the key that you were referring to earlier, Fellow Daoist Chen. It seems that by some stroke of fortune, we were forced here by the puppets that we encountered," Sun Tu said with a smile.

"Indeed, our efforts have finally paid off," Chen Yang replied with a smile of his own.

"There's only one key here, so..."

Sun Tu's voice trailed off here, but it was quite clear what he was implying.

"According to my knowledge, there's more than one of these crimson keys in the Great Ruins, so there's no point in trying to claim any single one of these keys. It would be best if we can find others with the same key and work with them to reap more spoils," Chen Yang said with a smile.

Han Li was pretending to meditate with his eyes closed, and he sneered internally as he listened to the conversation between two the city lords.

Not only had Chen Yang and Sun Tu refrained from mentioning this crimson key to him prior to this, it was clear that Sun Tu was trying to claim the key for himself by leveraging what he perceived to be his and Fang Chan's superior powers over everyone else. However, he was forced to reconsider after hearing what Chen Yang had to say.

Right at this moment, Xuanyuan Xing suddenly interjected, "It looks like the things hanging from this tree are also puppets, so it most likely won't be so easy to acquire the key."

"Indeed, so let's all work together to obtain the key first," Sun Tu said, suddenly agreeable to the idea of working with everyone again.

"Alright, let's get started then," Chen Yang said with a nod, then sprang up toward the copper tree.

Sun Tu's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he gave Fang Chan a subtle look, upon which the latter immediately set off for the tree as well.

The two of them each landed on a different branch of the tree, and as soon as Chen Yang set foot on the branch, he immediately felt a burst of tremendous suction force act upon him from below, locking him firmly into place.

Fang Chan was also in the same situation, and the two of them were suddenly bound to the tree.

Right at this moment, a series of star runes lit up over the tree, following which bursts of white light began to spread over all of its branches.

Han Li opened his eyes upon sensing this change, just in time to see all of the puppets hanging from the tree beginning to sway from side to side.

Shortly thereafter, they began to fall from the branches of the tree like ripe fruits, and in the instant that they landed on the ground, specks of red light appeared in their eye sockets as each of them drew a saber that was strapped to their backs.

The sabers had no star acupoints, but they were etched with star runes that were giving off layers of white starlight.

The puppets spread themselves out into a line, and aside for the two that had jumped back onto the tree to confront Chen Yang and Fang Chan, the rest were all rushing directly at Han Li and the others.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh upon seeing this, then rose to his feet, and another battle ensued.

Two of the puppets were rushing directly at Han Li at an astonishing speed, attacking him from both the left and the right as they slashed their sabers through the air.

Han Li drew his white scimitar, and his Star Moon Boots lit up, instantly elevating his speed to its peak. In the blink of an eye, he dodged the pair of oncoming sabers before hacking his scimitar against the legs of one of the puppets.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as a large flurry of bright sparks erupted from the puppet's body, and even though Han Li's scimitar strike was able to leave a pronounced white mark on the puppet's armor, it hadn't actually been damaged in the slightest.

Han Li was quite surprised by how resilient the suit of armor was, and he stomped a foot down onto the ground while channeling his Titan Vajra Arts.

All of the profound acupoints on his arms lit up, and he grabbed tightly onto the hilt of his scimitar before unleashing another almighty blow.

A thin layer of starlight appeared over the scimitar, and in response, the puppet raised its saber above its head to block Han Li's attack.

A loud crack rang out as the puppet's saber was snapped into two, following which the white scimitar crashed down onto its shoulder.

Unfortunately, much of the scimitar's power had already been expended in the process of shattering the puppet's saber, so it was ultimately only able to slice around an inch into its armor, inflicting no substantial damage.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he attempted to withdraw his scimitar, only to discover that a burst of immense suction force had surged out of the puppet's armor, locking the scimitar firmly into place.

At the same time, the other puppet was already rushing at Han Li while swinging its saber at Han Li's lower abdomen, so he was forced to abandon his scimitar and dart back in retreat.

Meanwhile, Chen Yang and Fang Chan were still stuck firmly to the copper tree, so they could only battle their puppet assailants with their feet completely rooted to the spot. Initially, they were doing just fine, but as two more puppets entered the fray, they began to struggle.

In particular, Fang Chan had already been struck close to twenty times by his two puppet assailants, and his entire body was drenched in blood.

However, there was no pain in his expression at all, and his battle intent only seemed to be growing more and more fierce with each passing wound that he sustained.

Right as one of the puppet's plunged its saber directly at his heart, he abruptly opened his mouth to let loose an animalistic shriek, releasing bursts of semi-transparent soundwaves that were visible even to the naked eye.

As soon as the puppet's saber pierced into the oncoming soundwaves, it was instantly slowed down to a crawl, as if it had been plunged into a wall of wet sand.

At the same time, the entire tree began trembling violently from the soundwaves, and he and Chen Yang were finally able to free themselves.

Fang Chan stepped forward and plunged his hand straight through the soundwaves unleashed by his own roar, then grabbed onto the puppet's neck before tightening his grip with all his might.

A dull thump rang out as the puppet's neck exploded in his crushing grip, and its head fell onto the ground.

At the same time, a thin and intricate white bone spike shot out of Chen Yang's sleeve, then pierced into one of the puppets through a gap in its armor.

Immediately thereafter, the puppet exploded from the inside with a resounding boom.

Things progressed relatively smoothly from there onward, and it didn't take long before all of the puppets were vanquished.

Fang Chan had sustained around a dozen light external injuries, while Xuanyuan Xing had been stabbed through the stomach by one of the puppets, but aside from that, everyone else remained virtually completely unscathed.

Sun Tu took some time to treat Fang Chan's injuries, then turned to Chen Yang as he asked, "Who's going to take the key?"

Chapter 948: Conflict

"You are the one with the most advanced cultivation base out of all of us, so the key should go to you for safekeeping," Chen Yang said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"You clearly know more about these crimson keys than I do, so I think it should go to you," Sun Tu countered. "Before we discuss that, I can see that there's a restriction around the key. Do you recognize this restriction?"

"I've never been all that proficient when it comes to dealing with restrictions and arrays, so I'll have to trouble you, Fellow Daoist Sun," Chen Yang said in a modest manner.

"In that case, I'll do the honors," Sun Tu replied with a faint smile, yet right as he was about to make his way to the top of the copper tree, the gate of the hall suddenly exploded with a resounding boom before flying toward everyone.

Han Li and the others quickly sprang away to the side, and the gate crashed into the copper tree before exploding into pieces.

"If neither of you are willing to capture the key, then how about I do so in your stead?"

Han Li turned to the entrance of the hall with tightly furrowed brows to discover Qin Yuan, Fu Jian, and the black-robed man by the name of Shao Ying.

The three of them were standing side by side at the forefront, and trailing along behind them were two more figures, namely Duan Tong and a short and portly middle-aged man who Han Li didn't know the name of, but what Han Li did know was that he was an elder of Profound End City.

"When did you get here? How did you manage to bypass my Heavenly Star Eye?" Sun Tu asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"You thought that setting up a mere Heavenly Star Eye at the entrance of the altar would be enough as far as surveillance goes? You must think very little of us, City Lord Sun," Fu Jian chuckled.

Sun Tu fell silent as his expression darkened slightly.

"I would gladly hand over the key to the two of you if you had gotten here first, but isn't it a little unscrupulous of you to come in and try to claim the key after we've already done all of the dirty work and taken care of the puppets?" Chen Yang asked in a cold voice.

"I didn't think a smart man like you would be capable of saying something so naive, Fellow Daoist Chen. Would you not have done the exact same thing had you been in our place? Don't try to make yourself seem like a saint!" Qin Yuan chuckled with a cold sneer on his face.

"If you want to challenge all of us for the key, then go right ahead!" Chen Yang said as he took a step forward, and Sun Tu also took a step forward to stand beside him.

"I'll admit that you do have the numbers advantage, but quantity is hardly going to make up for inferior quality," Qin Yuan sneered.

"Get over here, Shi Kong! Do you intend to betray City Lord E?" Shao Ying asked in a cold voice as his hawk-like gaze fell upon Shi Chuankong.

Shi Chuankong remained completely unfazed as he gave Shao Ying a derisive sneer.

Right at this moment, Fu Jian suddenly said, "Fellow Daoist Sun, our two cities have always been quite close, so let me offer you a word of advice. Chen Yang is an extremely ambitious man who's willing to stoop to any lows to accomplish his objectives, and he's already colluding with Puppet City in secret, so choosing to work with him is nothing but a path to destruction!"

A slightly unnatural look appeared on Chen Yang's face upon hearing this, while Sun Tu's expression remained completely unchanged, and it was unclear if he already knew, or if he didn't believe Fu Jian.

Right at this moment, Chen Yang's voice suddenly rang out in Han Li's mind.

"Fellow Daoist Li, City Lord Sun and I should be able to take on Qin Yuan and Fu Jian, while Xuanyuan Xing and Fang Chan can handle Duan Tong and that Profound End City elder. Will you be able to keep Shao Ying occupied while Fellow Daoist Shi goes to claim the key?"

"My apologies, Fellow Daoist Chen, but I plan to stay out of this conflict," Han Li replied without bothering to resort to voice transmission.

He then took a few steps back with Shi Chuankong to distance themselves from everyone else.

Everyone was caught completely off guard by this turn of events, and they all turned to Han Li and Shi Chuankong with wariness and befuddlement in their eyes.

Han Li had always been quite wary of Chen Yang, and he had never regarded Chen Yang as a true ally, so he didn't want to get overly involved with him.

Hence, he was naturally unwilling to continue working with Chen Yang, and the best choice for him was to observe from the sidelines.

"You're a smart man, Fellow Daoist Li. As long as you stay out of this, I'm willing to let our past differences slide, and I'll also give you some compensation after all is said and done," Qin Yuan said with an elated smile.

"Cut the chit-chat!" Shao Ying suddenly yelled, and Fu Jian, Qin Yuan, and the others immediately launched themselves at the copper tree as profound acupoints lit up all over their bodies.

Chen Yang was about to try and convince Han Li to change his mind, but he was forced to focus his attention on the oncoming Fu Jian instead, while Sun Tu was challenged by Qin Yuan.

The elder from Profound End City grinned as he rushed at Xuanyuan Xing, who he perceived to be the weakest of the bunch.

Duan Tong took a glance in Han Li's direction, then leaped up into the air before swinging his enormous right arm down upon Fang Chan from above.

Fang Chan displayed no fear at all as he took a step back, then threw a punch up at the heavens in retaliation.

All of a sudden, Duan Tong raised his left arm to tug on the bandages around his right arm, and the bandages instantly slipped off to reveal a giant, black arm that was covered in fine scales.

There were close to a hundred profound acupoints glowing radiantly on the arm, and as it came swinging down, the space beneath it began to crackle and pop, as if it were being compressed to a breaking point.

Fang Chan opened his mouth to let loose a thunderous roar upon seeing this, releasing a wave of white soundwaves that swept through the air as his fist clashed against Duan Tong's.

……

A fierce battle ensued, and aside from Han Li and Shi Chuankong, Shao Ying was the only one without an opponent.

However, instead of rushing in to claim the key, he remained standing off to the side not far away, seemingly apprehensive of the possibility that Han Li and Shi Chuankong could be putting on an act.

After observing Han Li and Shi Chuankong for some time, he discovered that they really were displaying no intention of entering the fray, and only then did he turn a hesitant gaze toward the crimson key above the copper tree.

Immediately thereafter, he sprang up into the air toward the top of the tree, but he had only risen up from the ground when a streak of white light shot forth toward him at an astonishing speed.

It was a white flying dagger, and it almost struck his temple as it flew past him before embedding itself into the ceiling above.

Even though Shao Ying was able to evade the dagger, he was forced to descend onto one of the copper tree's lowest branches as a result, following which he turned to Chen Yang with a resentful expression.

It was Chen Yang who had hurled that flying dagger in his direction just now.

However, his top priority at the moment was to claim the key, so Shao Ying made no effort to retaliate against Chen Yang as he prepared to make his way up the copper tree, only to discover that his feet had suddenly become firmly rooted to the branch that he was standing on.

"Fellow Daoist Li, have I wronged you in any way? Why is it that you've chosen to end our collaboration at such a crucial juncture?" Chen Yang asked through voice transmission while warding off Fu Jian's attacks.

"I would like to help you, but you're harboring far too many secrets for me to trust you, so I have no choice but to proceed with caution for my own safety," Han Li replied.

"I understand that I've been keeping too much from you. How about this? You help us secure the key, and I'll tell you everything once the key has been obtained," Chen Yang proposed in an urgent manner.

"I'm afraid I have no intention of getting involved in this mess while I'm still completely oblivious to all of the circumstances involved," Han Li replied.

"'Fellow Daoist Li, I can tell that you've already obtained another key, and that's why you're not as eager as the rest of us to secure this one, but have you considered what's going to happen to you and Fellow Daoist Shi once all of us are dead and the others find out that you have another key?"' Chen Yang asked.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he was quite taken aback by the fact that Chen Yang was aware that he was in possession of another key.

However, he then quickly realized that Chen Yang had to have spotted some telltale signs back when the two keys had resonated with each other earlier.

"Is that supposed to be a threat?" Han Li asked as a cold look appeared on his face.

"Not at all, Brother Li, I'm just pointing out the fact that we are currently interdependent on each other for survival," Chen Yang replied in an urgent voice.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face as he cast his gaze toward Shao Ying. At this moment, a series of profound acupoints had lit up over his legs, sending tremors running through the copper tree, thereby allowing him to free himself bit by bit.

All of a sudden, Han Li heaved a faint sigh before springing up into the air without any warning.

Thanks to his Wingform Ascension Arts, he was able to tread upon air to reach the top of the copper tree in the blink of an eye, much to the chagrin of Qin Yuan and the others.

Chen Yang and Sun Tu both heaved a faint sigh of relief upon seeing this, and they exchanged a glance with each other before launching a fierce barrage of attacks at Qin Yuan and Fu Jian to buy Han Li more time.

As soon as Han Li landed on the copper tree, he was also instantly rooted to the spot.

Shi Chuankong also flew onto the tree after him, temporarily serving as his guardian.

Chapter 949: Unexpected Arrivals

Han Li paid no heed to the suction force acting upon him from the copper tree as he began carefully examining the pillar of white light before him.

This array was somewhat different from the one that he had bypassed to claim the previous crimson key, but they were both quite similar in nature, so it shouldn't be a difficult task to overcome this one.

With that in mind, he pulled out his Star Wave Pen and began to work.

With some experience already under his belt, Han Li was able to work much faster than before, and it didn't take long before his array was completed.

The pillar of white light slowly dissipated, and the crimson key fell into Han Li's grasp.

At the same time, the suction force emanating from the copper tree completely subsided.

Shao Ying was furious, thinking that he had fallen for a ploy collectively hatched by Han Li and Chen Yang, and he stomped down violently, snapping the branch beneath his feet as he launched himself at Han Li.

Meanwhile, Han Li and Shi Chuankong flew down from the tree, and before Shao Ying had a chance to come after him again, he raised the key high above his head as he yelled, "Everyone, get back! If you try to take the key from me by force, then I'll destroy it right now so no one gets it!"

Sure enough, Shao Ying immediately drew to a halt upon hearing this, glowering down at Han Li from the top of the copper tree with a dark expression, while everyone else in the hall also stopped what they were doing and disengaged themselves from their opponents.

"Haven't you already chosen not to get involved, Fellow Daoist Li? Why have you suddenly changed your mind?" Fu Jian asked with a displeased expression.

Han Li continued to hold the key aloft, and he offered no response.

"Do the cultivators of our Green Goat City have to follow your orders now, City Lord Fu?" Chen Yang sneered.

"It appears that we've fallen for their little ploy, Fellow Daoist Fu. We thought that they had turned on each other, but that was nothing more than an act to lure us into a false sense of complacency," Qin Yuan said.

"How dare you! Are you not afraid that I'll strike you down even at the cost of having the key destroyed?" Shao Ying threatened in a malicious voice.

Right at this moment, an authoritative voice rang out from outside the hall.

"That's enough nonsense from you, Shao Ying!"

Immediately thereafter, four more figures made their way in from outside.

The group was led by an unremarkable-looking middle-aged man and a short and well-built elderly man.

Neither of them should've commanded much attention, but they did, simply due to the fact that they were E Kuai and Mistress Liu Hua.

Standing behind them were Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing, and to Han Li's befuddlement, he noticed that as soon as E Kuai came into view, Chen Yang immediately took a step backward, as if he had something to hide.

"Welcome, City Lord E," everyone hurriedly greeted.

Shao Ying rushed over to E Kuai before extending a deep bow, but before he had a chance to say anything, a cold look suddenly appeared on E Kuai's face as he smacked Shao Ying to the ground.

Shao Ying hurriedly clambered to his feet before bowing down again, not daring to say anything, while Qin Yuan and the others looked on with fearful expressions.

Han Li tightened his grip a little further around the crimson key upon seeing this, and he was carefully observing E Kuai's expression as considered whether to hand over the key or threaten to destroy it again.

E Kuai's gaze roamed over everyone in the hall, and a hint of approval surfaced in his eyes at the sight of Han Li. He was slightly taken aback to see Shi Chuankong standing behind Han Li, but he didn't display too much of a reaction.

However, as his gaze fell upon Qin Yuan and the others, a displeased look instantly appeared on his face as he sneered, "You two sure enjoy instigating internal conflicts, City Lord Qin, City Lord Fu. It seems like you're always jumping at the first opportunity to turn on your own allies."

"Please don't misunderstand, City Lord E. We were only trying to claim the key for ourselves so that we could offer it to you, and in our haste to do so, we got into a slight disagreement with Fellow Daoist Sun and Fellow Daoist Chen," Qin Yuan hurriedly explained.

"Is that really what happened, Fellow Daoist Qin?" Sun Tu sneered.

"If you had been clashing against Puppet City cultivators for the key, not only would I not be displeased, I would've rewarded you instead, but instigating internal conflicts at such a crucial juncture is entirely unforgivable," E Kuai said in a cold voice.

"My sincerest apologies, City Lord E. We were blinded by our excessive eagerness to get our hands on the key. Once we return to Profound City, we'll be sure to compensate White Rock City and Green Goat City for our transgressions," Fu Jian hurriedly said.

"I'll let things slide for now, but you two better make sure to compensate Fellow Daoist Sun and Fellow Daoist Chen once we leave the Great Ruins. Seeing as the key was claimed by Green Goat City, it can remain in the possession of Fellow Daoist Li for now, and no one is to try and take it from him. All of us must work together to claim the most precious treasures in the Great Ruins, do I make myself clear?" E Kuai declared.

No one raised any objections to this arrangement, but right at this moment, Han Li stepped forward as he said, "City Lord E, now that you're here, it would be unreasonable for me to hold onto the key any longer. It should be kept under your supervision instead."

"Perhaps all of you are unaware of this, but there are actually five of these keys in total, and only when combined in one place can they open a restricted area deep within the Great Ruins. Hence, having a single key isn't going to be of much use. Seeing as you were the one who obtained the key, you can keep it until we reach the entrance to that restricted area," E Kuai replied with a smile.

Han Li didn't say anything further upon hearing this, and he tucked the key down the front of his robes.

The sound of an urgent heartbeat rang out once again as the two crimson keys resonated with each other in front of his chest and began beating like a pair of hearts.

Immediately thereafter, another burst of heat surged out of the crimson key before entering his body, instantly stirring up both the bloodline power and the starpower within his body.

In this instant, the profound acupoint on his body that was yet to be fully opened finally burst open.

Han Li was ecstatic, and he hurriedly suppressed the energy fluctuations threatening to erupt out of his body to conceal this latest breakthrough, but despite his best efforts, everyone still noticed something and collectively turned to look at him.

Han Li's expression remained calm, and in order to divert attention away from himself, he asked, "City Lord E, would you be able to tell us exactly what treasure is resting deep within these Great Ruins?"

"According to ancient legends, a set of remains that harbor boundless power can be found deep within the Great Ruins. It's a set of remains with truly miraculous powers, and even just witnessing them can grant immense benefits," E Kuai replied.

The fact that this set of remains was receiving such glowing praise from E Kuai clearly indicated that it was indeed no ordinary treasure, and looks of longing and greed surfaced in everyone's eyes upon hearing this.

At the mention of this set of remains, Han Li couldn't help but think of the Scalptia Holy Remains that Shi Chuankong had mentioned, and he snuck a glance at Shi Chuankong, only to find a cold and distant look on the latter's face.

He then turned his gaze to Chen Yang to discover that the latter was currently looking rather concerned.

"You know some things, don't you, Fellow Daoist Chen?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

After waiting for a short while, there was still no response from Chen Yang.

"Is City Lord E telling the truth or not?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"Fellow Daoist Li, I am indeed keeping some things from you, but I'm doing so for a reason, and I can't reveal these things to you right now..."

"Fellow Daoist Chen, you've already threatened me once, and if you're going to continue to keep secrets from me, then I think our collaboration should end here," Han Li interjected in a cold voice.

After a brief hesitation, Chen Yang sighed, "Fine, if you must know, then I'll tell you everything. In the beginning, I was actually from Profound City, not Green Goat City. My brother, Chen Lie, and I were both spies under the city lord's manor, and we were meant to be sent out to infiltrate other cities once our training was complete.

“For our final examination, we were both sent out to assassinate someone, and upon successfully carrying out the mission, we would receive vast quantities of cultivation resources and advanced bodily refinement cultivation arts. However, in a cruel twist of fate, our assassination targets for the mission were each other..."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Chen Yang paused here momentarily, then continued, "E Kuai sent Shao Ying to monitor us at the time, so we had no choice but to turn on each other, and in the end, I was the one who survived."

"Your past differences with E Kuai have nothing to do with me. I can work with you in order to better my chances of surviving in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, but challenging E Kuai would be no different from committing suicide, and I won't join you in such a futile endeavor," Han Li said.

"Of course, I have no intention of turning on E Kuai anytime soon. Right now, I'm just like you, Fellow Daoist Li, I'm just trying to survive," Chen Yang sighed in a resigned manner.

"So was he telling the truth just now?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid I don't know the answer to that question. After all, no one has ever found these remains before, but there are indeed legends that proclaim that a set of remains that harbor boundless power can be found deep in the Great Ruins.

“It's said that if one can obtain even a single finger bone from the set of remains and refine it into their own body, then their physical cultivation base and the number of profound acupoints they possess will be significantly elevated," Chen Yang replied.

Han Li was just about to say something else when E Kuai suddenly said, "Fellow Daoist Li, seeing as the key is in your possession, let's set off for that restricted area together right away. We can't afford to let the Puppet City cultivators get there before us."

"If all five keys must be assembled to access the restricted area, surely the Puppet City cultivators won't be able to go in even if they get there ahead of us," Sun Tu said.

"The Puppet City cultivators are all adept in the art of puppetry, so they may have some other tricks up their sleeves," Mistress Liu Hua said.

Chapter 950: Eliminating Potential Threats

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face in response to E Kuai's proposal, and he was hesitating about whether to go or not when Shi Chuankong's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Given that our teleportation tokens are fake, there's currently no way for us to return to the Holy Realm. If there's any place in the Scalptia Spatial Domain that can take us back, then it can most likely only be somewhere deep in these Great Ruins."

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly upon hearing this.

"Do you have some qualms, Fellow Daoist Li?" E Kuai asked in an amicable fashion.

"Truth be told, I currently have a Black Tribulation Centipede in my body, and that's always been a major threat looming over my head. If something goes wrong, I could lose my life at any moment, and my life may not matter much, but my demise could hamper our Profound City's plans, and that would be catastrophic," Han Li explained.

"A Black Tribulation Centipede? Isn't that something that you can get rid of, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua?" E Kuai asked as he turned to Mistress Liu Hua.

"It's... a long story. So be it, I'll get rid of his Black Tribulation Centipede," Mistress Liu Hua said with slightly furrowed brows, then led Han Li out of the palace.

All of a sudden, Mistress Liu Hua turned around with a dark expression as he said, "Did you plan to force my hand here and extort me into removing your Black Tribulation Centipede?"

"Please don't misunderstand, Senior Liu Hua. I only dared to bring up this matter because I heard from Fellow Daoist Gu that you were planning to remove my Black Tribulation Centipede after we leave the Great Ruins anyway," Han Li hurriedly explained.

"She told you everything already, did she? I should've known," Mistress Liu Hua grumbled.

"Speaking of Fellow Daoist Gu, have you seen her after entering the Great Ruins?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid not. At the time, the situation was very chaotic, and I wanted her to stick close to me, but we were separated anyway. It sounds like you haven't encountered her either, right?" Mistress Liu Hua replied with a concerned expression.

"Rest assured, Senior, I'm sure Fellow Daoist Gu is fine," Han Li replied, not directly answering the question.

"The fact that you're concerned for her safety tells me that you're not some heartless bastard. Otherwise, even if I'm acting under City Lord E's orders, I wouldn't have fully removed the Black Tribulation Centipede from your body. Alright, let's begin now," Mistress Liu Hua sighed.

Han Li could only nod in response with a wry smile.

Shortly thereafter, the two of them returned to the hall together, and the threat of the Black Tribulation Centipede was finally lifted.

"Can we set off now, Fellow Daoist Li?" E Kuai asked with a smile.

"Of course. Thank you for your patience, City Lord E," Han Li replied as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Alright, let's go!" E Kuai ordered, and everyone began to make their way out of the hall.

However, they hadn't gone very far when the entire hall suddenly began to tremble, and countless rapidly widening cracks appeared on its walls, while loose rocks came tumbling down from above.

"This place is about to collapse! We have to get out of here!" Sun Tu exclaimed, and a slight panic began to set in.

However, Han Li already knew what to expect, so he remained calm and composed.

He took a glance at Chen Yang out of the corner of peripheral vision, and he was surprised to find that Chen Yang was also completely unsurprised and unfazed by this sudden turn of events.

"Don't panic," E Kuai said in a voice that wasn't very loud, but instantly instilled within everyone a sense of calmness.

"There's nothing to be afraid of here," E Kuai continued with a faint smile, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of white light that instantly swelled and brightened upon flying out of his sleeve, transforming into a thick pillar of white light that erupted into the heavens with arcs of white lightning flashing around it.

The ceiling of the hall was instantly destroyed by the pillar of white light, and the ground above it was also melted away, causing the entire hall to tremble even more violently.

Immediately thereafter, the pillar of white light faded away, and a massive, scorched hole appeared overhead, leading up to the surface.

Everyone turned to E Kuai and awestruck expressions upon seeing this, and a hint of astonishment also flashed through Han Li's eyes as he turned his gaze to Chen Yang.

The arcs of lightning within the pillar of white light were identical in aura to the white lightning within the short yellow spear that Chen Yang had used earlier.

At this moment, Chen Yang was looking up at the massive hole above with a dazed expression and a slightly pale complexion.

However, everything was still collapsing rapidly, and countless cracks instantly appeared around the hole, making it appear as if it were also about to collapse.

E Kuai immediately flew out through the hole, and everyone else hurriedly followed along.

Even though most of them weren't able to fly like Han Li, climbing up to the hole in the ceiling was still a very simple task, and in the blink of an eye, everyone had arrived on the surface.

The entire altar was still trembling violently, and it didn't take long before it completely collapsed into the earth, leaving an enormous, bottomless crater in its wake.

Everyone was standing beside the crater, looking on with dazed expressions, while Han Li began to inspect his surroundings with a hint of concern in his eyes.

Countless puppets had emerged in the wake of the previous altar's collapse, and he didn't know if the same thing was going to happen here.

While there were many powerful Profound City cultivators gathered here, such a boundless sea of puppets would still be far too much for them to deal with.

The same thought had clearly occurred to Shi Chuankong as well, and the two of them exchanged a concerned glance with each other.

Sure enough, the ground began to tremble once again, and a wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

"What's going on? Is it an earthquake?"

As the tremors ran through the earth, countless puppets began to burrow their way out of the ground.

These were all crimson humanoid puppets that were very similar to the ones that Han Li and the others had fought earlier, and they were wielding large crimson swords that were giving off a fiery glow.

The crimson puppets immediately pounced at the Profound City cultivators as soon as they emerged from the ground, and everyone hurriedly formed a circle with their backs facing one another in response.

"How are there suddenly so many puppets?"

This was naturally quite an alarming turn of events, but everyone remained calm and collected as they drew their weapons to clash against the puppets.

It didn't take long for Han Li to cut down two of the puppets with his white scimitar, and to his dismay, these crimson puppets also had full sets of internal organs and silver fluid flowing in their bodies.

The superior craftsmanship granted them far more power and speed than the snake, wolf, and tiger-headed puppets from the previous altar, and with so many of them pouring out of the ground, it was going to be extremely difficult to escape from this place.

With that in mind, he took a glance at E Kuai and Mistress Liu Hua, and he was surprised to see that the two of them were looking quite calm and confident.

"Not to worry, everyone, these puppets can be easily dealt with. Fellow Daoist Liu Hua, I'll get you to do the honors," E Kuai said, and Mistress Liu Hua nodded in response before swiping a hand over his own waist, upon which a gray incense burner appeared in his grasp.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this.

This incense burner seemed to also be a star artifact, and as Mistress Liu Hua chanted an incantation, a large plume of gray smoke surged out of the burner before rapidly spreading to encompass a huge area in the span of just a few seconds.

As soon as the nearby puppets were caught within the gray smoke, their movements were instantly slowed down significantly, while their attacks also became feeble and powerless, but the smoke had no effect on Han Li and the others.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense over the puppets within the gray smoke, and he discovered that the silver fluid in their bodies had become far more viscous than before, thereby significantly slowing down its circulation.

An enlightened look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

Everyone was ecstatic to see this, and they hurriedly pounced on this opportunity to eradicate all of the nearby puppets, quickly clearing out a large area.

The remaining puppets seemed to be very apprehensive of this gray smoke, and all of them lingered outside the area encompassed within the gray smoke while roaring like wild beasts.

Sun Tu exchanged a glance with Chen Yang, then smiled as he said, "Impressive as always, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua. May I ask what this gray smoke is? It seems like these puppets are very fearful of it."

"It's just a little trick used to subdue these puppets, it can hardly be termed as impressive," Mistress Liu Hua replied in an indifferent manner.

Under E Kuai's instructions, everyone set off once again, and the gray smoke followed them wherever they went, maintaining a safe zone that was close to ten thousand feet in radius around them.

With the cloud of gray smoke hanging over them, the surrounding puppets posed no threat at all, and it didn't take long before everyone left the city, then emerged from the entire oasis.

Much to everyone's relief, the puppets in this place seemed to be bound to the oasis, so they didn't pursue everyone any further.

Even with the protection of the cloud of gray smoke, being surrounded by tens of thousands of hostile puppets was still not a good feeling.

E Kuai seemed to be aware of the location of the restricted area, and after leaving the oasis, he led everyone straight to that crimson river before continuing in the downstream direction.

Two months flew by in a flash, and everyone finally emerged from the crimson desert.

The ground up ahead gradually turned from red to black, and the air suddenly became very humid. The starpower in the air was even more abundant in this place, and the earth was dotted with vegetation, forming a lush rainforest.

Given the diverse environments that the Great Ruins had displayed thus far, no one was surprised to see a rainforest here, but there was a cloud of faint black mist permeating throughout the forest, shrouding the entire area in an air of mystery.

Chapter 951: Different Intentions

E Kuai paid no heed to the change in the surrounding environment as he continued to lead the way forward as if he were taking a casual stroll. It didn't appear as if he were using any special techniques, but he was able to cover a distance of close to a thousand feet with every single step.

Mistress Liu Hua, Fu Jian, Qin Yuan, and Shao Ying were following along closely behind him, while Chen Yang, Sun Tu, and Han Li were trailing along a little further behind.

Everyone remained silent as they trudged through the forest, and the only sound that could be heard was that of their rustling footsteps.

Han Li took a glance at E Kuai, then communicated to Chen Yang and Sun Tu through voice transmission, "Is this restricted area really up ahead, Fellow Daoist Chen? Why does this rainforest look so strange?"

Not only was E Kuai tremendously powerful himself, he also had the likes of Qin Yuan, Fu Jian, and Shao Ying on his side, so Han Li and the others were at a massive disadvantage. Under these circumstances, they were forced to set aside their personal differences to work wholeheartedly together.

"I've only heard very little about the Great Ruins, so I don't know exactly where these so-called remains are supposed to be. However, judging from the increasing abundance of starpower in the air, we do indeed seem to be advancing deeper into the Great Ruins. In any case, you have a key right now, so we always have some leverage if E Kuai decides to turn on us," Chen Yang said.

Han Li nodded in response, but internally, he was still feeling rather apprehensive.

"Speaking of the key, there's something that I can't make sense of. According to City Lord E, five keys are required to access that restricted area, yet Fellow Daoist Li only has one, but City Lord E hasn't mentioned anything about searching for the other keys. Could it be that he's already gathered all of the remaining four keys?" Sun Tu speculated.

"Perhaps so," Han Li replied as he took a glance at Chen Yang, who didn't say anything.

"I wonder exactly how these keys are used. If City Lord E really does have all four of the remaining keys, and these keys are still useful after we enter the restricted area, then we would truly be at a severe disadvantage on all fronts, so we have to proceed with caution," Sun Tu continued.

This was something that Han Li had failed to consider, and if this were the case, then that really would be a cause for concern.

All the while, E Kuai continued to casually stroll forward, seemingly completely unbothered by the fact that Han Li and the others were intentionally lagging behind.

"City Lord E, it's clear that Chen Yang and Sun Tu are up to no good. On the surface, they seem to be obedient to you, but if you ask me, they're most likely already colluding with Puppet City to hatch some sinister plot. I think we should kill them right now so they don't get the chance to turn on us.

“With your powers, I'm sure you'll be able to kill Li Feiyu in an instant before he has a chance to destroy his key!" Fu Jian suggested through voice transmission as cold killing intent flashed through his eyes.

"There's no need for that, I trust Chen Yang and Sun Tu not to work with Puppet City. They're only behaving this way because they're apprehensive of me, which is inevitable, considering the situation that we're in," E Kuai replied with a faint smile.

"You're too tolerant and benevolent, City Lord E! It's clear that Chen Yang still harbors resentment toward you for what happened all those years ago, so you have to be wary of him!" Fu Jian insisted in an urgent manner.

"There's no need to worry, City Lord Fu, I know what I'm doing. Right now, it's best for us to maintain the peace. If we turn on one another now, that'll only be playing into Puppet City's hands," E Kuai replied.

Fu Jian could only fall silent upon hearing this.

With that, everyone continued onward, each absorbed in their own thoughts, and several more days passed by.

At this point, the group had already ventured quite deep into the rainforest.

The trees in this area had become extremely massive, and the smaller plants had gradually disappeared.

E Kuai had announced to everyone that the restricted area was not far up ahead, and that was a very encouraging declaration.

Han Li was trudging through the forest while inspecting his surroundings with furrowed brows when Shi Chuankong asked through voice transmission, "Is there something wrong, Fellow Daoist Li? You've been looking rather troubled for a while now."

"Something feels strange to me," Han Li replied.

"How so?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Why is that despite the vast abundance of starpower in the Great Ruins, we haven't encountered any scaled beasts on the way here? Shouldn't this type of environment be perfectly suited to nurturing scaled beasts?" Han Li asked.

"Now that you mention it, that is indeed rather strange," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"Forget it, there's no point in thinking about that now. According to E Kuai, the restricted area should be just up ahead. Will there really be a way to leave the Scalptia Spatial Domain further up ahead?" Han Li asked.

"Pokong wasn't the one who informed me of this. Instead, I gathered this information after browsing through all of the information on the Scalptia Spatial Domain that I could find in our imperial scripture library, so it should be reliable," Shi Chuankong replied.

"Rest assured, I do trust you, Fellow Daoist Shi, but this is a very important matter, so would you be able to elaborate further?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid I can't reveal any more information to you on this subject as it concerns a secret of our Night Sun Empire. However, I can swear a vow to the Baleful Holy Emperor that I'm telling you the truth," Shi Chuankong replied in a serious manner.

"In that case, I won't ask any more questions," Han Li replied with a nod, much to Shi Chuankong's relief.

The group continued onward for almost another day when a large cloud of crimson mist appeared up ahead.

The cloud of mist was extremely dense, and it spread as far as the eyes could see in all directions, standing in everyone's path like a crimson wall.

Furthermore, the cloud of mist was churning and rumbling incessantly, presenting a very peculiar sight to behold.

Everyone stopped in their tracks and peered into the crimson mist momentarily before collectively turning to E Kuai.

"There's no need to be concerned, everyone. This area is known as the Sulfurous Mist Sea, and we'll be able to see the restricted area once we pass through this place. Not only does the Sulfurous Mist Sea not pose any danger, this is where Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds take shape, so if you're lucky, you may be able to encounter a cloud or two," E Kuai said as he continued onward without pause, and everyone's eyes instantly lit up slightly upon hearing this.

"Do you know about this place, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"I don't, but if this is the place where Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud can be found, then this is a massive opportunity," Shi Chuankong replied as he peered into the crimson mist up ahead with an excited look in his eyes.

"Visibility is very limited in the mist sea, so take care not to get lost," E Kuai warned as he strode into the crimson mist, followed by everyone else.

As soon as Han Li stepped into the crimson mist, he instantly felt an enormous weight crash down upon him, as if he were walking on the seabed.

The crimson mist was extraordinarily heavy!

Han Li raised an eyebrow at this sudden change, but this amount of pressure wasn't enough to have much of an impact on him, so he continued onward without a hitch.

Inside the crimson mist, visibility was limited to less than two hundred feet, and the mist was also very restrictive on one's spiritual sense, limiting his spiritual sensory range to only around two hundred to three hundred feet.

The sea of mist seemed to be enormous, and even after walking for around fifteen minutes, there was still no end in sight.

Initially, everyone was feeling rather apprehensive, but after walking for a while, they encountered no danger, so they began to relax, and everyone spread out in a line to search for Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds.

The only one who appeared to be disinterested in searching for Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds was E Kuai, and this was a detail that didn't escape Han Li's attention.

The fact that E Kuai was so knowledgeable about the Great Ruins struck Han Li with a sense of unease.

"What are you doing, Fellow Daoist Li? I know your spiritual sense is particularly powerful, so you should put it to good use and search for Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds as well," Shi Chuankong urged.

Han Li snapped back to his senses upon hearing this, then released his spiritual sense throughout the surrounding area.

The Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud was a reward reserved for the top finisher in the Five City Martial Gathering, so it was naturally something that he also desired.

Right at this moment, Chen Yang suddenly shot forth in a certain direction, and Han Li hurriedly released his spiritual sense in that direction upon seeing this.

A burst of crimson light shot out of the mist up ahead before being caught in Chen Yang's grasp, revealing it to be a palm-sized gelatinous crimson cloud that was giving off a faint crimson glow.

Han Li was quite far away from Chen Yang, so he wasn't able to see him, but his spiritual sense instantly locked onto the blood cloud.

The cloud was giving off a burst of extremely potent energy fluctuations that encompassed both starpower and bloodline power, so this was undoubtedly a Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud.

Everyone else had also sensed this, but seeing as the blood cloud had already fallen into Chen Yang's hands, they could only reluctantly accept this outcome.

There was an ecstatic look on Chen Yang's face as he immediately devoured the blood cloud whole, seemingly worried that someone would try to take it from him.

After swallowing the blood cloud, Chen Yang's entire body instantly began to glow with radiant crimson light, and in the blink of an eye, over a hundred profound acupoints had lit up over his body, seemingly in an involuntary fashion.

An alarmed look appeared on his face upon seeing this, and he hurriedly darted back to conceal himself within crimson mist.

Even though Chen Yang had acted quite quickly, Han Li's spiritual sensory range far exceeded that of everyone else, and before Chen Yang was able to back out of his spiritual sensory range, he was able to see that over 260 profound acupoints had already lit up over his body.

Chapter 952: Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds

Not long after Chen Yang vanished into the crimson mist, a string of strange sounds akin to draconic roars and thunderclaps began to ring out incessantly.

Before long, a tremendous aura began to sweep through the air in all directions, causing the nearby crimson mist to churn violently.

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon seeing this, and it was clear from the commotion that these Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds truly were extraordinary things.

Right at this moment, both Shi Chuankong and Xuanyuan Xing detached themselves from the group before darting into the crimson mist, while Sun Tu sped away in another direction immediately thereafter, followed closely by Fang Chan.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then also abruptly vanished from the spot.

In the blink of an eye, everyone in Han Li's group had disappeared.

An eager look appeared on Zhu Ziqing's face upon seeing this, and she was just about to leave as well when Zhu Ziyuan grabbed onto her arm to stop her.

She was just about to complain when E Kuai said, "You can search for Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds, but make sure you don't spread out too much in case you get lost. Our main objective is to enter the restricted area, and compared with the holy remains, Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds are all too insignificant."

Sun Tu and the others gave affirmative responses from afar, but none of them turned back.

E Kuai's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"City Lord E, these people must be reined in! They're no longer even respecting your authority!" Fu Jian harrumphed coldly.

"It's inevitable that they'll be tempted to go after something as precious as Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds, so just let them be. Fortunately, there aren't any hazards present in this area, so there won't be any major mishaps," E Kuai replied.

An indignant look appeared on Fu Jian's face upon hearing this, but he didn't say anything further.

"If you want to go and search for blood clouds, then you can all go as well, but make sure not to go too far," E Kuai said to Fu Jian and the others.

Fu Jian, Shao Ying, Zhu Ziyuan, and the others were all ecstatic to hear this, and they hurriedly thanked E Kuai before departing as well, leaving only E Kuai and Mistress Liu Hua behind.

"You're not going with them, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua?" E Kuai asked.

"An old man like me can't compete with those young people anymore. Besides, even though there are no natural hazards present in this area, there's no guarantee that there won't be any backstabbing, so it's safer to stay with you, City Lord E," Mistress Liu Hua replied with a smile.

"I suppose that's true," E Kuai replied with an amused smile before continuing onward, but at a far slower pace than before.

"Come to think of it, didn't you say that there Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds are supposed to be quite rare? How is it possible that two have suddenly appeared at once?" Mistress Liu Hua asked.

E Kuai merely gave a faint smile and offered no response.

……

After traveling some distance into the crimson mist, Han Li stopped in his tracks, then channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to release his spiritual sense to scour the surrounding area.

Close to an hour later, another chorus of draconic roars rang out, clearly indicating that someone had just obtained a Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud, but it was unclear who it was.

In terms of spiritual sensory range, Han Li was confident that he wouldn't lose to E Kuai or anyone else, yet he hadn't found even a single Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud up to this point.

A hint of urgency welled up in his heart as he began to pick up the pace while continuing to scour his surroundings with his spiritual sense.

All of a sudden, his expression changed slightly as he cas this gaze to the right, where he had detected some faint energy fluctuations with his spiritual sense.

A burst of white light flashed over his body as he instantly shot forth in that direction.

Before long, he arrived at a rift in the ground that was several hundred feet wide and immeasurably long and deep.

Those faint energy fluctuations were coming from deep within the rift.

Han Li didn't hesitate in the slightest as he dove into the rift, and it didn't take long for him to reach the bottom.

There, he spotted two Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds hovering over the ground, bouncing back and forth in the confined area like a pair of headless flies.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he immediately pounced onto one of the blood clouds before grabbing onto it, yet right as he was about to make a grab for the second one, two figures suddenly crashed down from above, namely Fu Jian and Duan Tong.

Both of them pounced at the remaining Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud in unison, but Han Li was able to get there ahead of them.

"Hand over the blood clouds and we won't hurt you," Fu Jian demanded with a cold look in his eyes.

Han Li paid no heed to him as he stowed the two Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds away before rising up into the air.

"How dare you!"

Fu Jian was furious as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of black light that caught up to Han Li in the blink of an eye.

A loud clang rang out as Han Li blocked the streak of black light with his white scimitar, but right at this moment, a cold sneer appeared on Fu Jian's face, and the single streak of black light abruptly split up into eight identical streaks of black light before hurtling toward various vital regions of his in unison.

Han Li lashed out with his scimitar in response, unleashing eight white blade projections that swept toward the streaks of black light.

At the same time, a layer of bright starlight appeared over his other arm as he swung around before throwing a punch in a certain direction.

A string of loud clangs rang out as the blade projections clashed against the streaks of black light to repel them, while Han Li's fist clashed against the tip of a black sword that had emerged out of thin air without any warning.

The black sword was sent flying back through the air, while Han Li drifted back in retreat while looking down at a small gash on his own fist with furrowed brows.

A look of dismay appeared on Fu Jian's face in the wake of his failed sneak attack.

"As opposed to wasting time with me here, I suggest you go try your luck elsewhere, City Lord Fu. Farewell."

Han Li cupped his fist in a parting salute, then sped away as a streak of white light, doing so just in time to evade a punch from Duan Tong.

Fu Jian stomped a foot down onto the ground to launch himself after Han Li, while Duan Tong followed along in silence.

The three of them flew out of the rift in the ground almost at the exact same moment, and Han Li didn't want to engage them in a direct conflict, so he immediately began flying back in E Kuai's direction.

A flash of killing intent passed over Fu Jian's face, and he was just about to do something when a voice suddenly rang out.

"Is it not a little unbecoming of a city lord like yourself to pick on a cultivator from my Green Goat City, Fellow Daoist Fu?"

Immediately thereafter, Chen Yang emerged from the crimson mist up ahead.

It was unclear exactly how many profound acupoints had opened using that Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud, but his aur was clearly more powerful than before.

Fu Jian stopped in his tracks as he said, "There must be a misunderstanding, City Lord Chen. We only just so happened to be searching for Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds in this area. Congratulations on the breakthroughs that you've made."

Duan Tong also stopped in his tracks as the profound acupoints on his body faded away.

"I see. In that case, it appears I was mistaken," Chen Yang said with a faint smile.

"If there's nothing else that you wish to speak to me about, then I'll be taking my leave now," Fu Jian said as he took a glance at Han Li, then turned to depart with Duan Tong.

"Are you alright, Fellow Daoist Li?" Chen Yang asked as he turned to Han Li.

"It's a good thing that you arrived just in the nick of time, Fellow Daoist Chen," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"With your powers, I'm sure you would've been fine even without my intervention, but Fu Jian is a very close subordinate to E Kuai, so try to avoid any direct conflicts with him unless there's no other alternative," Chen Yang cautioned.

After that, Chen Yang took a glance at the front of Han Li's robes, then quickly departed as well, making no mention of the two Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud that Han Li was carrying.

Following Chen Yang's departure, Han Li sped away in another direction, and after about fifteen minutes, he had arrived in a relatively safe area.

Once there, he pulled out the two Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds with an excited look in his eyes.

Such an exceptional bodily refinement treasure was undoubtedly going to be highly sought after even in the outside world, let alone in a place as barren and lacking in cultivation resources as the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

However, it felt a little strange to him that something so extraordinary seemed to be so easy to obtain in this area.

Perhaps this is why the Great Ruins are such an alluring place to the cultivators of both cities.

With that in mind, Han Li was just about to devour a Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud when another chorus of draconic roars rang out from afar, indicating that someone else had found another Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud nearby.

Han Li returned his gaze to his two Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds, then devoured them both at once.

With someone else refining a Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud nearby, this was the perfect cover for him to do the same thing.

In the next instant, his entire body shuddered, following which his skin turned bright red, and the two Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds transformed into a burst of intense heat that spread through his body.

It was as if a flame had appeared in his stomach, scorching all of his internal organs to inflict such excruciating pain upon him that even he couldn't help but give a muffled groan, despite his tremendous mental fortitude.

He clenched his fists tightly as he fought through the agony.

No one had told him that devouring Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds would be such a painful process, and it didn't seem like Chen Yang had suffered anywhere near as much earlier.

However, what he failed to consider was that Chen Yang had only devoured a single Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud, while he had devoured two at once.

Chapter 953: Crimson Gate

Han Li only just barely had a chance to brace himself before the burst of heat formed by the Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds began to spread through his entire body, making it feel as if all of his meridians were about to be forcibly torn apart.

His complexion instantly became deathly pale, but his skin was still bright red, and a series of egg-sized bulges were roaming over his body like living creatures, presenting a bizarre sight to behold.

His expression was twisted in agony as large droplets of sweat flowed down his forehead, and his body was trembling uncontrollably.

His bloodline power was ignited by this burst of heat, and all of his profound acupoints lit up over his body in an involuntary manner.

Despite his immense mental fortitude, Han Li was beginning to fade in and out of consciousness.

He was doing everything in his power to protect his own consciousness so that he didn't completely faint, but right at this moment, his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts were activated on their own, guiding the bursts of heat to different parts of his body.

If he were fully conscious at this moment, he would notice that the bursts of heat were being guided toward the profound acupoints recorded in the cultivation art.

A string of loud pops rang out from all parts of his body as the bursts of heat began to invade new profound acupoints that were still yet to be opened.

Everytime Han Li was about to fade out of consciousness, bursts of excruciating pain would spear through his entire body, forcibly bringing him back to lucidity.

Before long, he began to sense the changes taking place in his body, and a hint of elation welled up in his heart.

He gritted his teeth against the excruciating agony as he sat down with his legs crossed to channel his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, guiding the bursts of heat toward these new profound acupoints.

To his surprise, these profound acupoints put up next to no resistance, and in mere moments, one had already been opened.

One profound acupoint was opened after another, and before long, over twenty profound acupoints had been opened in succession.

At this moment, there were 263 profound acupoints glowing over his entire body!

Right at this moment, the burst of heat wreaking havoc in his body faded away, only to be replaced by a cool and refreshing sensation.

The contrast was such a blissful one that he was almost unable to suppress a moan of pleasure, and it took him quite some time to compose himself.

The Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud had truly lived up to its incredible reputation.

Han Li could scarcely believe that he had managed to open so many profound acupoints in such a short time, but this was the reality.

I wonder if opening profound acupoints using Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud will have any detrimental effects.

As he was considering this notion, the cool sensation in his body also faded away, and in the blink of an eye, everything returned to normal.

Han Li didn't dare to make any rash moves, and he waited until the bloodline power in his body completely settled down before making his way back to the others.

Even though he had left for quite some time, he had made sure to remember the direction that the main group was in, so he never lost his way.

At this point, the sea of crimson mist had become far thinner than before.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li found his way back to the main group. Perhaps E Kuai and Mistress Liu Hua had intentionally been waiting for everyone, but they had been making rather slow progress.

Aside from Shi Chuankong, Xuanyuan Xing, Fu Jian, and Duan Tong, everyone else had already returned.

E Kuai displayed no reaction to Han Li's return, while Mistress Liu Hua took a glance at him, only to quickly turn away again.

"You're finally back, Fellow Daoist Li. I can tell that you've made some significant strides!" Chen Yang said as he approached Han Li.

"I made some decent progress," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

"That's good to hear, but don't get complacent. I've heard that Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing have also obtained Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds. In particular, Zhu Ziyuan was very formidable to begin with, and now that he's obtained a Sulfurous Flame Blood Cloud, the situation is not looking good for us," Chen Yang said through voice transmission.

Han Li cast his gaze toward Zhu Ziyuan upon hearing this, but the latter's gaze remained fixed up ahead with a look of focus in his eyes.

"Fellow Daoist Shi and Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan still aren't back yet. Fu Jian and Duan Tong haven't returned, either. Is it possible that they've run into one another?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"I don't think that's very likely. Fellow Daoist Shi and Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan were among the first people to leave, so perhaps they've gone exploring somewhere far away," Chen Yang replied in an unconcerned manner.

Han Li was still a little worried about Shi Chuankong, but he didn't say anything further.

Thankfully, it didn't take long before Shi Chuankong and Xuanyuan Xing returned to the group, and both of them were looking rather depressed, clearly having failed to secure any Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds.

Shortly thereafter, Fu Jian and Duan Tong also returned. Judging from their reactions, their luck hadn't been much better, and an angry look flashed through their eyes as they glanced at Han Li, who paid no heed to their hostilities.

At this point, everyone had already returned to the group, and thus, E Kuai picked up the pace.

After walking for close to another three hours, the surrounding crimson mist finally completely faded away, revealing an undulating mountain range up ahead.

The mountain range was enormous, stretching as far as the eyes could see, and the mountains within it were completely barren and devoid of vegetation, presenting a completely different environment from the rainforest that the group had just emerged from.

What was most strange of all was that the entire mountain range was crimson in color, and there were several crimson rivers flowing between the mountains, as well as a sweet aroma of blood in the air.

E Kuai continued onward without pause, leading the way into the mountain range, and after crossing over several mountains, everyone arrived before a giant basin.

Several large rivers came together here, and an enormous crimson palace was standing at the point where the rivers were connected. The palace wasn't much shorter than the nearby mountains, and it was dozens of kilometers in area, resembling a gargantuan crimson beast prowling in the basin.

The construction of the palace displayed exceptional craftsmanship, and the entire structure was giving off radiant crimson light, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

"What a majestic palace!" Shi Chuankong praised in an earnest manner.

At this moment, the crimson stone gates at the entrance of the palace were tightly shut, and there were countless crimson runes and designs inscribed upon it, forming what appeared to be an extremely complex array.

Han Li examined the array closely, and he quickly discovered that it was similar to a star array in some ways, but also completely different. It seemed to be the product of a star array combined with some other type of array.

There were five small black holes on the array, arranged evenly to form a unilateral pentagon.

These black holes clearly resembled keyholes, and Han Li's eyes lit up slightly as he laid a hand over the two crimson keys that he was carrying.

Looking at the crimson palace, a fervent gleam had appeared in E Kuai's eyes, and even his breathing had become slightly heavier.

"Is this the restricted area where the holy remains can be found, City Lord E?" Sun Tu asked.

"That's right," E Kuai replied before taking a deep breath to regain his composure.

Everyone else immediately erupted into chatter upon hearing this.

A contemplative look appeared on Sun Tu's face as he observed the palace, and he suddenly strode over to its gates before pressing a hand against them.

Bursts of white starlight began to emanate from the palm of his hand before rippling incessantly, seemingly searching for something.

Moments later, Sun Tu withdrew his hand as he declared, "I can indeed sense the aura of a set of remains inside."

"What do you mean by that, City Lord Sun? Were you suspecting City Lord E of lying to us?" Fu Jian asked in a furious voice.

Sun Tu merely took an expressionless glance at Fu Jian and offered no response.

E Kuai raised a hand, gesturing for Fu Jian to stand down as he said, "City Lord Sun has never been here before, so it's understandable for him to proceed with caution. If anyone else also suspects me, then you can all feel free to come forward and take a look."

"It's all thanks to your protection that our Profound City has been able to remain standing to this day, and our Excess Passage City and Profound End City have always had absolute trust in you, City Lord E. However, that doesn't appear to be the case for everyone," Fu Jian sneered as he took a glance at Sun Tu and Chen Yang, while Qin Yuan hurriedly chimed in in agreement.

Chen Yang's eyes narrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he offered no response.

"Seeing as no one else wants to come forward, then let's not waste any more time," E Kuai declared as he took a step forward, and Fu Jian and others eagerly nodded in response.

Right at this moment, Sun Tu's voice rang out once again.

"Hold on a second!"

"Sun Tu! You need to learn your place! Don't forget that you're just a subsidiary city lord of Profound City!" Fu Jian yelled in a furious voice.

"Why are you getting so worked up, City Lord Fu? I just wanted to ask City Lord E a question," Sun Tu said with a faint smile.

E Kuai wasn't bothered at all, and he prompted with a faint smile, "Go ahead, City Lord Sun."

"I recall that you mentioned that five keys are required to access this restricted area. Right now, the only key that I know of is in Fellow Daoist Li's possession, so could it be that you're carrying all four of the other keys?" Sun Tu asked.

Chapter 954: Pentagonal Crater

"You think far too highly of me, City Lord Sun. I've only been in these Great Ruins for a short time, just like everyone else, so how could I have possibly gathered all four of the other keys. At the moment, I only have two," E Kuai replied with a smile as he flipped a hand over to produce a pair of crimson keys.

"So that means we only have three keys in total. In that case, how can we open these gates?" Sun Tu asked as his brows furrowed slightly, and Fu Jian and Qin Yuan also turned to E Kuai to hear his answer.

"Rest assured, everyone, all five keys have already been assembled. Fellow Daoist Chen, Fellow Daoist Li, I believe it's time for you to show everyone your keys," E Kuai said with a faint smile.

Everyone immediately turned to Han Li and Chen Yang with surprised expressions upon hearing this.

"I was just about to bring out my keys," Han Li replied with a composed expression, but internally, his mind was racing.

E Kuai had led everyone here without any hesitation, seemingly completely unconcerned about the prospect of having insufficient keys, and that had already tipped Han Li off the possibility that he was somehow able to find out who was carrying the other keys and how many they had in their possession.

With that in mind, Han Li pulled out two keys from the front of his robe, while Chen Yang also revealed the single key in his possession.

"So the two of you had three keys all along! As expected, City Lord E always has everything under control," Sun Tu praised with a faint smile.

Chen Yang took an apologetic glance at Sun Tu, then cupped his fist in a salute toward E Kuai as he said, "These keys are extremely important, so Fellow Daoist Li and I have been holding onto them this entire time for safekeeping purposes."

"It's fine. The Puppet City cultivators are still yet to make an appearance, so it's better to be safe than sorry," E Kuai replied with a dismissive wave.

"Thank you for your understanding, City Lord E," Chen Yang said with a relieved expression.

"Seeing as all five keys have already been assembled, then hurry up and stop wasting everyone's time!" Fu Jian harrumphed coldly while glowering at Chen Yang and Han Li with a disdainful expression.

"Hold on, I have something to say before we open the gates," Han Li suddenly said.

"Li Feiyu, you're nothing more than a mere gladiator of Green Goat City, so just keep your mouth shut and hand over your keys! There's no place for you to speak here!" Fu Jian sneered.

"It's fine, let's hear what Fellow Daoist Li has to say," E Kuai said.

"Thank you, City Lord E. I just wanted to ask how we're going to split the treasures in the restricted area among ourselves," Han Li said with a smile, and everyone immediately fell silent upon hearing this.

"City Lord E has already said that everyone gets a share of the treasures in the restricted area, and that they'll be split evenly among everyone," Fu Jian said.

Han Li turned to Fu Jian with a derisive sneer upon hearing this.

Shao Ying also turned to him with a disdainful expression as he scoffed, "Fellow Daoist Fu Jian, you haven't made any contributions on the way here, yet you want to get the same split of treasures as City Lord E? How incredibly optimistic of you!"

"I was only relaying what City Lord E had said earlier! If you think this method of distribution is inappropriate, then you can make your own suggestion, Fellow Daoist Shao," Fu Jian countered with a furious and embarrassed expression.

"City Lord E was the one who led all of us here, and he also acquired two keys, so I think he should get half of the treasures in the restricted area, while we split the rest among ourselves," Shao Ying declared.

"So you suggest that we distribute the treasures based on the merit of our contributions? I suppose that's reasonable. City Lord E has indeed made the greatest contribution out of all of us, but Fellow Daoist Li has also secured two keys, so how much should he get? And what should I be getting for my one key?" Chen Yang asked.

Shao Ying had no response to this.

"I don't think there's any method of distribution that can ensure absolute fairness. In my opinion, we should split the treasures inside into ten parts and distribute them among our five cities. Profund City gets three parts, Green Goat City gets two, and the remaining five parts will be split evenly among our three cities.

“As for how the treasures are distributed among the cultivators of each city, that'll be up to them to decide," Qin Yuan proposed, and everyone fell into deep thought upon hearing this.

"I think this is a reasonable proposal," Chen Yang declared after some contemplation.

Meanwhile, Shi Chuankong was looking a little concerned.

After entering the Scalptia Spatial Domain, he had stayed in Green Goat City, but was then quickly sent to Profound City, so he didn't know which city he belonged to.

Right at this moment, Chen Yang's voice rang out in his mind through voice transmission.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Shi, even though you didn't stay in our Green Goat City for long, I still count you as a citizen of our city."

A relieved look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as he gave a grateful response.

Fu Jian and Sun Tu considered this arrangement momentarily before also expressing their approval.

Shao Ying still seemed to be displeased, and he was just about to say something when E Kuai declared, "Fellow Daoist Qin's proposal is quite reasonable, so let's adopt it for now."

With E Kuai making his decision known, Shao Ying naturally couldn't raise any further objections, and everyone began to discuss the method of opening the gates.

According to E Kuai it was quite simple, and all that had to be done was to push all five keys into their corresponding keyholes at once.

E Kuai handed one of his keys to Shao Ying, while Han Li gave one of his keys to Sun Tu, and before long, E Kuai, Shao Ying, Chen Yang, Han Li, and Sun Tu had positioned themselves in front of the gates, with each of them holding one key.

"Go!" E Kuai yelled as he pushed his key into the hole, and everyone else immediately did the same.

As soon as the five keys were pushed into the keyholes, the stone gates instantly began to tremble, and all of the crimson patterns on their surfaces began to glow radiantly, forcing everyone to shield their eyes.

Right at this moment, a string of mechanical clicks rang out from within the palace, and the five keys disappeared into the holes.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of viscous crimson light erupted out of each of the five holes, then twisted themselves together like rope to form a massive crimson rune.

In the next instant, the crimson rune vanished into the stone gates, and all of the crimson patterns on the gates faded away.

The gates then swung open inward, revealing a wide and dark passageway.

"Let's go," E Kuai said as he led the way inside, and everyone else immediately followed along.

After everyone had stepped into the palace, a burst of rumbling rang out from behind them as the stone gates swung shut again.

With E Kuai leading the way, everyone made their way through the passageway before arriving on a plaza.

The entire area was shrouded in darkness, but right at this moment, a series of giant orbs began to light up on the ceiling overhead, much like stars on a dark night sky.

Han Li looked up and was greeted by the sight of radiant starlight cascading down from above alongside bursts of starpower fluctuations that spread in all directions.

Immediately thereafter, a flame lit up on each of the two walls on either side in the distance, then spread over the entire length of the walls as lines of fire, illuminating everything within the area.

The white stone plaza that everyone was standing on wasn't very large, and there was a line of railing no more than a thousand feet up ahead.

Everyone strode over to the railing to discover that there was a bottomless black abyss on the other side, out of which gusts of cold wind were blowing incessantly.

At the center of the railing were three stone arch bridges that were each over a hundred feet wide and roughly a thousand feet in length, leading all the way to a giant circular white altar.

The altar was over ten thousand feet in radius, and it was also surrounded by white railing, giving it the appearance of a lone, circular mountain standing at the center of the abyss.

E Kuai led everyone down the middle stone arch bridge onto the altar, and as soon as everyone set foot onto the altar, they were stunned by the unimaginably formidable bloodline aura that suddenly swept over them.

Only then did Han Li notice that there was a pentagonal crater at the center of the altar, and that was where the incredibly powerful bloodline aura was coming.

Standing on each of the five corners of the pentagonal crater was a strange-looking black scaled beast stone statue. They resembled incredibly rotund toads, each with a pair of wings on their backs. Their necks were disproportionately thin and long compared with their bodies, and connected to each neck was a giant lizard-like head that extended out into the air above the crater.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of these stone statues, wary of the possibility that they could be puppets that could spring to life at any moment.

Right as everyone was hanging back, unsure of how to proceed, E Kuai strode over to the edge of the pentagonal crater on his own, and only then did everyone else hurriedly follow along.

Han Li peered down into the crater to discover that was an enormous pond of blood, and there was an unfathomable volume of blood inside that was undulating like the tide, while a layer of dense crimson mist was present over its surface.

However, regardless of how violently the blood in the pond and the crimson mist above it churned and surged, both remained strictly within the confines of the crater.

What was even more surprising to Han Li was that among the churning waves of blood, he could make out pieces of white bones that were as translucent as jade, all of which were giving off tremendous bloodline auras.

Chapter 955: Burial Site

"Everyone, this altar is the place that we've been searching so arduously for," E Kuai declared, and everyone turned to him upon hearing this.

"Is this where the ultimate treasures of the Great Ruins reside, City Lord E?" Qin Yuan asked with a perplexed expression.

"I'm sure all of you have already sensed the tremendous bloodline aura in this place. Is this not already an exceptional treasure for us bodily refinement cultivators? On top of that, the set of remains that I mentioned is also in this pond," E KuaI replied, and everyone immediately looked down into the pond again upon hearing this.

Han Li peered into the pond like everyone else, but even with his eyesight, he was only able to see thick layers of bones beneath the blood, and he was unable to determine whether the holy remains were actually present inside.

"City Lord E, if the remains are in this pond, then does that mean that we have to go into the pond to retrieve them?" Fu Jian asked.

"That would no different from committing suicide. The bloodline power in this pond is beyond anything you can imagine, and if you try to enter it, you'll only be contributing your own bones to the piles of bones that are already at the bottom of the pond," E Kuai said.

"What should we do then?" Sun Tu asked.

"This pond is built upon a blood sacrificial array, and those five statues are the cornerstones of the array. I'm going to need all of the city lords to help me activate the array together and draw the set of remains out of the pond," E Kuai replied.

"City Lord E, I was hoping you would be able to enlighten me on something," Qin Yuan said with slightly furrowed brows.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Qin," E Kuai prompted.

"None of us have entered the Great Ruins prior to this, so why is it that you seem so familiar with everything in here, City Lord E?" Qin Yuan asked.

Everyone turned to E Kuai upon hearing this, and it was clear that Qin Yuan wasn't the only one troubled by this question.

"While exploring the Scalptia Spatial Domain on my own some years ago, I came across an ancient plaque that provided details about a certain secret area. It wasn't explicitly stated that this secret area was the Great Ruins, but I always had my suspicions. After entering the Great Ruins, I was able to verify many of the things detailed on the plaque on the way here, and that confirmed my suspicions. As for whether you believe me or not, we've already come so far, so why not place your trust in me one final time?" E Kuai said as he swept his gaze over everyone.

Han Li didn't buy this story at all. It was very likely that he had made up this story on the spot, but it was impossible to rebuke him because no one aside from him knew anything about this place.

Having said that, it was indeed true that they had already come this far, and no one was going to be willing to turn back empty handed.

"We have full trust in you, City Lord E. At the very least, you have my trust. It's just that no one has ever been here before, so I think we should all carefully examine this area to ensure that there are no hidden traps around before we activate the array. What do we all say?" Sun Tu proposed, and everyone began nodding in agreement.

"Of course, I was about to suggest the same thing, Fellow Daoist Sun," E Kuai said with a smile, and thus, everyone split up to examine the entire altar around the pentagonal pond.

Instead of approaching Chen Yang, Han Li teamed up with Shi Chuankong to examine the outskirts of the altar along the stone railing.

Chen Yang took a glance at the two of them, then turned and made his way toward one of the black stone statues, followed closely by Xuanyuan Xing.

Meanwhile, the other city lords and their subordinates had each gone to examine one of the remaining four stone statues.

Sun Tu arrived at the foot of one of the statues, then looked up at its protruding neck for a while before laying a hand onto it and injecting a wisp of starpower inside.

The statue remained completely still, displaying no reaction to the injection of starpower.

Sun Tu's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he swept a hand over the blood pond, upon which a tendril of crimson mist rose up from below before swirling its way up his sleeve.

A faint rustling sound rang out, following which his sleeve reverted back to its original state.

Moments later, a reassured look appeared on Sun Tu's face, and he cast his gaze toward Fang Chan.

At this moment, Fang Chan was leaning against the stone railing, looking down at the blood pond below with an enraptured look on his face and drool coming out of his mouth, much like a starving man greeted by the sight of a magnificent feast.

"Get back, Chan'er! You cannot enter that pond, do you hear me?" Sun Tu warned with a serious expression.

Fang Chan turned to him with a disappointed expression.

"Once the array is activated, you have to make sure to keep a lookout and protect me. Once we retrieve that set of remains, I'll do my best to secure a part of it for you," Sun Tu assured with a faint smile.

An elated look immediately appeared on Fang Chan's face upon hearing this.

Meanwhile, Fu Jian was examining another statue, while Duan Tong trailed along behind him with a hesitant expression.

"If you have something to say, then say it," Fu Jian said.

"For some reason, I have a bad feeling about this place. How about I operate the array in your stead, City Lord Fu? If something goes wrong, it'll be easier for you to save me than for me to save you," Duan Tong proposed through voice transmission.

"E Kuai specifically asked for all of the city lords to enter the array, so he must have his own considerations, and I'm sure he wouldn't agree for you to let you take my place. On top of that, your cultivation base is most likely insufficient to activate the array," Fu Jian replied through voice transmission.

Duan Tong fell silent upon hearing this.

"There's no need to be overly concerned," Fu Jian said as he patted Duan Tong on the shoulder. "I have some tricks up my sleeve, so even if any mishaps occur, I can look after myself just fine."

Duan Tong nodded in response, looking slightly more reassured.

Qin Yuan had been keeping an eye on Fu Jian the entire time, and the two of them exchanged a glance and a nod from afar.

Each of them had already examined a stone statue and the blood pond without discovering anything amiss, and after carefully examining the ground around the five statues, they didn't find anything worthy of concern, either.

Han Li was gradually making his way toward the center of the altar from its outskirts, pausing momentarily in front of each stone pillar to examine the patterns etched onto its surface.

All of a sudden, his brows furrowed slightly, and he turned around to discover Zhu Ziqing standing beside him.

"You're Li Feiyu, right? My brother tells me that there's more to you than meets the eye, but I can't tell what he's referring to," she remarked.

"I'm afraid your brother is mistaken, I am but a mere gladiator of Green Goat City," Han Li replied in an expressionless manner.

"In any case, I'm very interested in you. It's very remarkable that a human like you was able to refine your body to this extent. That alone makes you very special in my eyes," Zhu Ziqing said as she stroked her own chin.

Zhu Ziyuan's attention had been focused on the blood pond this entire time, and only now did he notice that his sister was no longer by his side.

"What are you doing over there? Hurry up and get back here!"

Zhu Ziqing gave him a sheepish smile before sticking out her tongue in a cheeky manner, then returned to his side before tugging on his sleeve.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

He still recalled that his youngest sister was the sibling that he had been most fond of back in that small village, but having already spent countless years on the path of cultivation, his memory of her had become rather murky.

Zhu Ziyuan gave Han Li an apologetic nod, then departed with his sister.

Meanwhile, Chen Yang was circling around one of the stone statues, but as he did so, his eyes were constantly darting around from side to side, clearly indicating that there was something on his mind.

"City Lord Chen," Xuanyuan Xing called out with a concerned expression, and only then did Chen Yang snap back to his senses, following which he took a glance at Xuanyuan Xing, but didn't say anything.

He strode over to the stone railing, and after looking down into the blood pond for a moment, he suddenly reached a hand into his own sleeve before pulling out a yellow spear with lightning patterns etched upon it.

With a sweep his hand, the spear shot through a gap in the railing before plunging into the blood pond.

A resounding boom rang out as the spear exploded into a ball of white lightning that was around ten feet in size within the pond.

White lightning erupted in all directions, scattering much of the crimson mist, but it was still unable to rise up out of the blood pond.

Everyone was given quite a fright by the explosion, and they turned to discover that the blood in the pond was clearly flowing much quicker than before, forming waves that crashed against the five walls of the pond.

"What the hell are you doing, Chen Yang?!" Qin Yuan yelled.

"I was just trying to see if there was anything strange inside the pond," Chen Yang explained in a calm manner.

E Kuai only took a brief glance at the blood pond before returning his gaze to the stone statue in front of him, while Shao Ying, Zhu Ziyuan, and Zhu Ziqing stood behind him in silence.

Some time later, the waves in the blood pond gradually subsided, and nothing out of the ordinary took place.

Chapter 956: Entering the Blood Pond

"Alright, now that everyone's had a chance to examine everything, should we discuss how we're going to activate the array and retrieve the remains? It hasn't been easy coming this far, and I hope you're not all just here for sightseeing purposes," E Kuai said, and even though his expression remained placid, there was clearly a hint of impatience in his voice.

The other city lords hadn't detected anything amiss, so they had no excuses to delay any longer. Hence, after exchanging a few glances with one another, all of them gathered around E Kuai.

At this point, Han Li and Shi Chuankong had already made their way around to the other side of the altar, where they spotted three more white stone arch bridges in the distance, leading deeper into this space from the altar.

There were no flames to illuminate the darkness beyond those bridges, so it was impossible to see what was there.

After hearing E Kuai's call, the two of them immediately stopped in their tracks, then hesitated momentarily before returning to the main group.

"Up to this point, I've been able to verify much of the content inscribed on the stone plaque that I mentioned, so its contents appear to be reliable. Hence, why don't we use the method on the plaque to try and activate the altar?" E Kuai suggested once everyone had gathered around.

"In that case, please tell us how to proceed, City Lord E," Qin Yuan said.

"This blood sacrificial array has a total of five cores that need to be activated by five people in unison. I would like the other city lords to enter the array with me as your cultivation bases and physical constitutions will hold you in good stead against the tremendous pressure that'll be exerted on us from the operation of the array.

“Everyone else will be responsible for lookout duty. That way, all cities will have contributed to the cause, thereby making everyone worthy of their share of the spoils," E Kuai said.

Everyone fell silent upon hearing this, and there was an atmosphere of skepticism in the air.

E Kuai didn't try to hurry anyone into making a decision, merely observing the four city lords in silence.

"City Lord E, can you tell us what dangers we could face while the array is in operation? That way, we'll be able to at least somewhat prepare ourselves for any unforeseen mishaps," Sun Tu said.

"On the path of cultivation, risk and reward always come hand in hand. The more risk you incur, the greater the reward you could potentially receive, so how much you make out of this opportunity is up to each of you," E Kuai replied with a faint smile.

"What does that mean, City Lord E?" Fu Jian asked with slightly furrowed brows, and everyone else was also rather perplexed by this answer.

"My guess is that while the array is in operation, a vast amount of bloodline power will escape from the blood pond in the form of blood mist to enter the bodies of the five people situated at the cores of the array. The influx of bloodline power could either significantly enhance our bodies, or overwhelm us and result in self-detonation, hence the risk and the reward," E Kuai explained.

"So that means that all five of us will be able to absorb the bloodline power in this pond to bolster our own physical constitutions?" Fu Jian hurriedly asked with an excited look on his face.

Everyone else was also ecstatic to hear this, with the exceptions of Chen Yang, Han Li, and Sun Tu, who were still looking very concerned and skeptical of E Kuai's claims.

Han Li's intuition told him that there was more to this array than met the eye, and that E Kuai was downplaying the risk involved in operating the array, so he had no choice in getting involved in this at all. In any case, the thing that he was truly interested in wasn't here. Instead, there was a very good chance that it was somewhere in the darkness on the other side of those three stone arch bridges.

"That's right, Fellow Daoist Fu. However, the process is going to be excruciatingly painful, and we must all persevere until the holy remains are drawn out of the pond by the power of the array," E Kuai said.

"While this is indeed an alluring prospect, the fact of the matter is that our bodies can only hold so much bloodline power. There's clearly far too much bloodline power in this pond for us to withstand. What if all of us are overwhelmed before the holy remains are revealed? Won't we all suffer the terrible fate of self-detonation then?" Sun Tu asked.

Qin Yuan and the others immediately turned their attention back to E Kuai upon hearing this question.

"Rest assured, everyone, the five cores of the array are all interconnected. As soon as one of us is on the verge of being overwhelmed by the influx of bloodline power, the excessive bloodline power will be evenly distributed to everyone else, thereby ensuring that the array remains in balance, so if one of us self-detonates, then all of us will self-detonate, and no one is incurring more risk than anyone else," E Kuai explained.

"Even so, all of us are still taking on a significant amount of risk," Sun Tu mused with a hesitant expression.

"Of course you can't just expect good things to fall onto your lap without taking any risks, City Lord Sun. If you really don't want to go through with this, then I'll gladly take your place," Shao Ying said with a smile.

Aside from the city lords, he was the only one present worthy of entering the array.

"There's no need for that, Elder Shao," Sun Tu replied with a smile. "I do have some qualms, but I'm still willing to do my part and enter the array with the other city lords."

"Rest assured, everyone, if the bloodline power becomes too much for us to bear, then I'll lead everyone out of the array in unison. Just follow my instructions, and everyone will be safe. Does anyone else have any other questions?" E Kuai asked with a smile.

No one else raised any further questions, so E Kuai declared, "In that case, please familiarize yourselves with the activation method for the array, and we'll enter the array once you're all ready."

He then openly articulated the array activation method to everyone without making any effort to hide it.

Shortly thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air as he ordered, "Enter the array!"

All of the city lords instantly sprang up into the air in unison before landing atop the head of the five statues.

As for Han Li and the others, they were instructed by E Kuai to open some distance between themselves and the blood pond to observe from afar.

The five city lords sat down with their knees crossed, then began to chant an incantation while making a series of hand seals.

Initially, the blood sacrificial array displayed no reaction, but over time, crimson mist swirling inside began to gather in the five corners of the array, revealing large sections of the blood pond underneath, which had begun bubbling incessantly.

At the same time, the five statues also began to display some changes.

Han Li had always been rather apprehensive of the statues, so he was the first one out of everyone to notice these changes.

His brows furrowed slightly as he noticed that a layer of fine patterns had appeared over the surface of the statue beneath Chen Yang, and one could easily mistake those patterns as a layer of scales if they didn't look closely.

However, as those patterns began to glow red, everyone discovered that it was actually a layer of tiny runes that were similar to star runes.

Once all of the runes on the five statues had lit up, the eyes of the statues abruptly sprang open, revealing a bright red gleam.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of rumbling erupted from underground, causing the entire altar to shudder violently.

The blood within the pond was instantly stirred up into a frenzy, bubbling and churning incessantly, while the crimson mist that had gathered at the five corners of the pond began to swirl upward in the form of corkscrew-shaped pillars.

The five statues opened their mouths up wide to accept the swirling pillars of crimson mist, and at the same time, a pentagram array appeared on the top of each of their heads in unison.

A pillar of crimson light then erupted out of each of the arrays, encompassing the five city lords within them.

Crimson mist began to surge out of the pillar of crimson light before entering their bodies through all of their orifices, instantly causing their skin to turn bright red.

Meanwhile, the runes on the five statues were only glowing brighter and brighter, and bursts of crimson light erupted out of their wings before spreading outward and connecting together to form a light barrier that encompassed the entire blood pond.

An alarmed look appeared on Duan Tong's face upon seeing this, but Shao Ying reassured, "Not to worry, this is just a barrier conjured up by the array. Once the array ceases operation, the barrier will vanish on its own."

Meanwhile, Fang Chan was standing behind the statue that Sun Tu was situated on, peering into the light barrier with a rare look of focus on his face.

As more and more crimson mist surged out of the statues, the eyes of the five city lords had already turned bright red. On top of that, clumps of crimson crystals had appeared around their eyes, making it appear as if they had grown clusters of scales.

As the bloodline power surged relentlessly into their bodies, mixed emotions of anxiety, excitement, tension, and anticipation had appeared on all of their faces.

After some careful examination, Chen Yang was able to determine that there was no restrictive power in the light barrier that encompassed the entire blood pond, and that made him feel slightly more reassured.

He exchanged a glance and a nod with Sun Tu from afar, and the latter had clearly detected this as well. If anything were to go wrong, the two of them should be able to leave the array at any moment.

Fu Jian and Qin Yuan quickly made the same discovery as well, and in the wake of this reassuring discovery, they were able to focus wholeheartedly on operating the array.

Chapter 957: Scaled Hou Guardian

All of a sudden, Qin Yuan suddenly let loose a long roar, and his cheeks had taken on a bright red complexion, while an excited gleam had appeared in his eyes, in stark contrast with his usual sickly appearance.

His robes were flapping audibly despite the absence of wind, and a vast number of specks of white light had appeared over his body, over two hundred of which were quite substantial in appearance, while the majority were more illusory and insubstantial.

Immediately thereafter, a similar sight presented itself on the bodies of Chen Yang, Fu Jian, and Sun Tu as well.

As for E Kuai, specks of substantial and insubstantial light had appeared over his body as well, but there were over eight hundred of the former variety.

"Brother Li, those specks of light appear to correspond with the profound acupoints on their bodies. Could it be that these are all the profound acupoints that they've opened?" Shi Chuankong speculated through voice transmission.

"There are far too many of them for all of them to be profound acupoints. If I had to guess, those more substantial specks of light should be the profound acupoints that they've already opened, while the rest are the ones that they're still yet to open. Having said that..."

Han Li's voice trailed off here as a thoughtful look appeared on his face.

"What is it?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Do you still recall how back when we first met Chen Yang, he mentioned that E Kuai had already opened over a thousand profound acupoints? Why is it that we can only see fewer than nine hundred right now?" Han Li asked.

"Could it be that he intentionally lied to us or was just trying to scare us?" Shi Chuankong speculated.

"I'm not sure, I guess we'll just have to ask Chen Yang about it later," Han Li replied.

Right as the two of them were conversing with each other, the crimson light radiating from the five pentagram arrays on the stone statues suddenly brightened significantly, and the faces of the five city lords instantly became contorted with agony, as if they were in excruciating pain.

Everyone hurriedly turned their attention to the city lords upon seeing this, and they discovered that crimson light had begun to gather in some of the profound acupoints on their bodies that were still yet to be opened, and they were gradually taking on a more and more substantial form.

At the same time, their auras were also rapidly elevating, and it seemed that they really were benefitting immensely from the influx of bloodline power.

Envious looks appeared in everyone's eyes upon seeing this.

Meanwhile, the blood inside the pentagonal pond was churning even more violently, as if it had been brought to a boil, raising up large plumes of crimson mist that were absorbed by the five statues. As the blood in the pond was depleted, the bones submerged within it were gradually revealed, and it really did seem like it was only a matter of time before the set of remains at the bottom of the pond rose to the surface.

Han Li had been carefully observing the array this entire time, but he hadn't noticed anything amiss, and he couldn't help but wonder if his concerns were perhaps unwarranted.

"I'm going to take a look down the back, Brother Shi. You stay here and keep an eye on everything else. If anything happens here, do your best to remain uninvolved until I get back," Han Li said through voice transmission.

Shi Chuankong faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "If you feel like something's going to happen here, then why don't you let me come with you?"

"We don't know what's waiting for us further down this hall, so there's no need for you to come and take the risk with me, and I really do need you to stay here and keep an eye on things. On top of that, we don't want to make it seem like we're very close with each other as that could arouse suspicions from the others," Han Li explained.

Shi Chuankong wasn't entirely convinced by this, but he still nodded in agreement in the end.

With that, Han Li made his way around the light barrier that encompassed the blood pond before making his way toward the three stone arch bridges on the other side of the altar.

However, he had only taken a few steps when Shao Ying suddenly appeared in his path.

"Where are you going, Fellow Daoist Li?"

Shi Chuankong was just about to step forward to back Han Li up, but Han Li urged him to stand down through voice transmission.

"All of the city lords are busy operating the array, and I can't help them in any way, so I thought I'd do some exploring on my own. Is there a problem?" Han Li asked.

"Right now, we're at a crucial juncture of the array's operation, and it's of the utmost importance that nothing goes wrong. Hence, I think it would be best for you to stay here and keep a lookout for your city lord," Shao Ying said in a cold voice.

"Our city lord already has Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan and Fellow Daoist Shi looking out for him, so I'm sure he'll be fine," Han Li countered.

"Even so, I can't allow you to walk around as you please. What if you inadvertently set off some type of trap that impacts the operation of the array?" Shao Ying objected in an unrelenting manner.

"Get out of my way, Shao Ying! Some of the other people here may be afraid of you, but that doesn't apply to me. If it's a fight that you want, then I'll gladly oblige!" Han Li sneered.

Shao Ying was naturally not afraid to face Han Li in battle, but if a battle were to ensue between the two, Xuanyuan Xing and Shi Chuankong would undoubtedly also get involved, as would Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing. There was no telling what the cultivators of the other three cities would do, and if they were to be swept up in the battle too, then the situation would truly descend into complete chaos.

While he was confident in his own ability to kill all of the cultivators from the other cities with the help of Zhu Ziyuan, there was no guarantee that such a battle wouldn't affect the operation of the blood array, and the consequences of that would be far too much for him to bear.

"You better not cause any trouble. Otherwise..."

Han Li sped past Shao Ying in a flash before the latter had a chance to articulate his threat, and in that instant, Han Li displayed such incredible speed that even Shao Ying had failed to react.

He hurriedly darted back in retreat to open up some distance between himself and Han Li, and an apprehensive look had appeared in his eyes.

Han Li paid no heed to Shao Ying as he made his way toward the three stone arch bridges.

Everyone's attention was focused on the five city lords within the blood array, so the minor altercation that had just taken place between Han Li and Shao Ying hadn't attracted much attention.

Zhu Ziqing was standing beside her brother, watching Han Li's departing figure with a curious look in her eyes, while Mistress Liu Hua was also looking at Han Li with a perplexed look in his eyes.

However, he still had to stay here to observe the changes in the blood array, so he naturally couldn't follow Han Li.

……

The three stone arch bridges in the back were completely identical in style, material, and construction to the ones in the front.

Once again, Han Li made his way over the middle bridge, and he quickly reached the other side.

On the other side of the stone bridge was another flat plaza that wasn't particularly large, and there were two giant stone gates up ahead.

There were no flames on the walls here, so the entire area was very dark, but Han Li was able to make out a carving of a beastly head engraved onto the stone gates thanks to his exceptional eyesight.

It was a lion-like head that was covered in scales, and it also had a single sharp horn.

There was a line that ran down the center of the head, splitting it down the middle lengthwise, with one half of the head on each gate.

Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed in contemplation as he recalled back to the contents of the jade slip that Daoist Xie had given to him.

Some time later, he murmured to himself, "There's a Scaled Hou Beast guardian engraved onto these gates, so this should be the place..."

With that, Han Li strode over to the gates, but instead of pushing them open, he laid his palms flat against two of the beastly carving's protruding fangs before pressing on each of them a few times.

A faint click rang out as rest of the fangs in the carving's mouth slid away in unison to reveal a pitch-black opening.

Han Li inspected his surroundings briefly, then made his way inside.

Immediately thereafter, another faint crack rang out as the fangs of the beastly carving slid back into place to block the opening again.

Upon entering through the opening, Han Li found himself in an area that was completely shrouded in darkness, and even with his eyesight, he was unable to see anything.

All of a sudden, the faint yet audible sound of a water droplet splashing onto the ground rang out from directly up ahead.

Han Li channeled his Titan Vajra Arts, and the profound acupoints on his arms began to radiate white light that illuminated the surrounding area.

Only then did it become clear to him that he was currently standing at the top of a stone staircase.

The light radiating from his profound acupoints was rather limited, so he was only able to see about five to six steps ahead.

After a brief hesitation, he began to make his way down the staircase step by step.

After descending close to twenty steps, the ground up ahead suddenly flattened out. It seemed that he had arrived on a level platform, and the sound of the falling water droplets had become even more pronounced here.

Han Li walked a few steps toward his perceived source of the sound, arriving before a stone pillar that was around three feet tall, with a stone basin that was around a foot in diameter at the top. The basin was filled with some type of black liquid that was giving off a faint, rank odor, and it seemed to be some type of beast fat.

Another faint splash rang out as a drop of liquid fell into the basin, sending faint ripples proliferating over the surface of the liquid that was already inside.

Han Li rubbed his fingers together, and a burst of starpower erupted out of his fingertips as a speck of white light, which fell into the stone basin.

A flame was instantly ignited within the basin, immediately following which two lines of fire surged out of the basin, spreading along the indentations that branched out from either side of the stone pillar.

Chapter 958: Weeping Blood Array

Han Li's gaze followed the movement of the line of fire, all the way until it had spread along the ground for over a thousand feet, at which it seemed to have reached its conclusion.

All of a sudden, the ground on either side erupted into flames, illuminating the entire space that Han Li was in.

Han Li inspected his surroundings momentarily, and a stunned look appeared on his face.

The space that he was in was around two thousand to three thousand feet in size, and there was a series of massive reliefs engraved onto the walls, depicting tall mountains, turbulent rivers, majestic cities, and various other pieces of stunning scenery.

The forests engraved onto the walls were teeming with exotic beasts, while cultivators were flying through the air, and it seemed to be depicting a scene that would only be found outside of the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

Why are there reliefs like these in a place like this? Could they have been made by someone in reminiscence of the outside world?

Han Li strode over to the walls to carefully examine all of the reliefs engraved upon them, and he discovered that the reliefs weren't connected, and there didn't seem to be any clear correlation between them, either.

Before long, Han Li had made his way deep into this space, where he spotted a black stone coffin that was around thirty feet in size on the ground. Engraved onto the coffin was what appeared to be a male puppet with a string attached to each of its joints, suspending it in mid-air. Its expression and limbs were all very stiff, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

All of the strings ran over the surface of the stone coffin before converging above the puppet's head, and upon closer inspection, Han Li discovered that there all of the strings had come together to form a yin-yang symbol above the puppet's head, but there was no customary eight trigrams design around the yin-yang symbol.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li gently laid a hand upon the yin-yang symbol, and he discovered that there was some give to it, so it could be pressed down by external force.

An elated look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he began to chant an incantation as he pressed down upon the yin-yang symbol.

The yin-yang symbol slowly sank down under the gentle pressure exerted by Han Li's hand, and the sound of stone grating on stone rang out as the stone coffin slid downward to reveal a transparent, cubic, crystal container, with each side roughly measuring five inches in length.

Inside the crystal container was a hollow silver ball that was riddled with extremely complex patterns, and it was also giving off peculiar energy fluctuations that were similar to soul power fluctuations.

Looks like this is it...

He observed the silver ball momentarily, then carefully examined the area around the crystal container, yet right as he was about to reach out to grab it, it occurred to him that something wasn't quite right.

He raised his head to continue inspecting the scenic reliefs on the surrounding walls, following which he made his way back to the stone coffin before replacing its lid.

He then began to pace back and forth while thinking back to the contents of the jade slip, and a particular detail suddenly sprang into his mind.

A look of realization then appeared on his face as his gaze roamed over the surrounding reliefs once again.

He made his way around the stone coffin until he was directly behind it, then began to stroke his hand along the relief on the wall before pressing down onto the sun engraved upon it.

A faint click rang out as the sun sank into the wall under the pressure exerted by his hand.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and he made his way over to the next relief on his right.

This relief depicted an image of an impending storm, and Han Li pressed down onto a particular cloud on the wall.

After that, he pressed down onto a river and a mountain on the next two reliefs.

The detail that he had recalled from the jade slip was that the eight trigrams were supposed to be concealed within these reliefs, and that was why they were absent from around the yin-yang symbol.

As all of the hidden mechanisms that represented the eight trigrams were pressed down by Han Li, the entire space began to tremble violently, and the stone coffin on the ground sank down in a shaky manner to reveal an entrance to a passageway.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

The entrance of the passageway wasn't very large, only able to fit one person at a time, and it revealed a stone staircase that led underground.

Han Li made his way down the staircase, and after descending around a dozen steps, the staircase turned left, leading to an opening that had white light glowing inside.

Han Li carefully made his way through the opening, arriving in another space that was only less than two hundred feet in size and was almost completely empty.

However, even though the area wasn't very large, there were dense clusters of star bones embedded into the walls, and the light that they were giving off was what was illuminating this space.

Han Li cast his gaze forward to discover a rectangular, black stone table positioned against the wall directly across from him, upon which were placed two extremely intricate white jade boxes.

After briefly examining the surrounding area to ensure that nothing was amiss, he strode over to the table and removed the lid of one of the jade boxes.

A fist-sized ball was revealed, sitting peacefully inside the box.

The ball was black in color, and just like the silver ball that Han Li had seen in the stone coffin, it was also hollow and riddled with strange patterns.

However, this ball wasn't giving off any energy fluctuations, and it didn't appear to be remarkable in any way aside from its intricate appearance. Hence, in contrast, the silver ball from before seemed more like a genuine artifact.

Han Li lifted the ball out of the box, then began to carefully inspect it while cradling it over the palms of his hands, and he spotted arcs of golden lightning that were as thin as strands of hair silently flashing deep within the heart of the ball.

Han Li had a feeling that this was no ordinary item, so he carefully tucked it down the front of his own robe.

After that, he turned his gaze to the other jade box.

This box had a round disc that was riddled with complex patterns embedded onto its surface, and there were two circles of holes on its outer edge, with a tiny golden rune visible beneath each hole.

Han Li reached out to lift the jade box, only to discover that it seemed to be fused as one with the table, refusing to budge even a single inch.

A series of profound acupoints lit up over his arms as he redoubled his efforts, and the jade box shuddered violently along with the table beneath it, but both the box and the table remained firmly locked into place.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and he suddenly raised a fist before throwing a punch at the jade box.

A burst of radiant starlight immediately flashed over the surface of the jade box, releasing a burst of tremendous power that forced Han Li to stumble back a step.

A perplexed look appeared on his face as he turned his gaze back to the jade box. The jade slip that Daoist Xie had given him had explicitly mentioned that the black ball was something that had to be secured, but there was no mention of what was in the other jade box.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as a series of profound acupoints lit up over his body, and he mustered up even more power before throwing another punch at the jade box.

The retaliative force released by the jade box was even stronger this time, forcing Han Li back several steps, all the way until his back was against the wall.

Han Li harrumphed coldly as he prepared to launch an even more powerful attack at the jade box, butright at this moment, he noticed that a crack was slowly appearing on the ground beneath his feet, leading straight to the underside of the jade box on the stone table.

He immediately realized that he couldn't continue to try and break open the jade box through brute force. Otherwise, this entire space was going to be destroyed along with it. On top of that, he didn't have any more time to waste here.

Right as Han Li was able to return to the main group, he suddenly spotted an image of a starry sky on the ground, illuminated by the light radiating from the star bones on the surrounding walls.

However, the image was quite small, and there were also parts that were missing.

Han Li observed the image for a long while before a look of surprise and realization suddenly appeared on his face, and he clapped his hands together as he exclaimed, "I see now!"

Immediately thereafter, he pulled his Star Wave Pen out of his sleeve and began repairing the image.

After completing his final stroke, Han Li stood up straight again to examine his own handiwork.

The starry sky image on the ground had begun radiating dazzling light, and a string of faint mechanical clicks rang out as the disc on the jade box began to slowly turn, following which the box sprang open on its own.

An elated look appeared on Han Li's face, and he peered into the jade box to discover a sheet of light gray beast hide that had been folded into a small square.

Han Li picked up the sheet of beast hide before spreading it open to reveal an image of an underground pentagonal altar, with a strange winged beast statue perched on each corner of the altar.

It was identical in appearance to the blood sacrificial altar that the five city lords were currently in.

Above the image of the altar was a heading that read "Weeping Blood Array", and Han Li immediately began carefully examining the entire image.

After comparing the Weeping Blood Array to the one outside, Han Li was quickly able to determine that the two were indeed one and the same. On top of that, according to the image, the blood pond in the array was enormous, and the array patterns engraved onto its walls were complex beyond belief.

There were also small passages of annotations around the image of the array, pointing out certain important features of the array and their functions.

The more Han Li saw, the more he came to understand what E Kuai's true intentions were.

In the end, his gaze settled on an annotation on the bottom right corner of the image, and a faint smile suddenly appeared on his face.

Chapter 959: Sudden Change

At this moment, the five city lords were still operating the array outside, and at this point, all five of them had opened a large number of profound acupoints.

Chen Yang already had over 290 profound acupoints glowing over his body, which meant that he had opened close to thirty profound acupoints in this short span of time.

Sun Tu and the others were in a similar situation, and all of them were naturally ecstatic to see this.

All of the bystanders were looking on with envious expressions, but they knew that they were far below the five city lords in terms of both power and status, so they didn't dare to raise any complaints.

At this point, the array was operating far faster than before, and the pentagram arrays beneath the five city lords had expanded to several times their original size, releasing far thicker pillars of crimson light.

The surrounding crimson light barrier had also become far thicker than before, and the countless runes on its surface were giving off a faint buzzing sound.

The stone statues beneath the five city lords were also displaying significant changes. They had turned from their original black color into a shade of dark red, and rays of crimson light were shooting out of their bodies, presenting a peculiar sight to behold.

The four subsidiary city lords were all observing these changes with uncertain looks in their eyes, and Sun Tu and Chen Yang exchanged a glance with each other, only to see their own unease mirrored in one another's eyes.

Thankfully, there was still no restrictive power emanating from the crimson light barrier, and that instilled them with a great deal of reassurance.

At this point, the blood level in the pond had dropped significantly, revealing sets of even more massive remains, and it seemed that the bottom was about to be revealed.

All of a sudden, the blood in the pond began to churn violently, forming a vortex that was several dozen feet in size.

Immediately thereafter, a large ball of crimson light appeared deep within the vortex, giving off formidable energy fluctuations.

These energy fluctuations were a combination of starpower and bloodline power, much like the power harbored within Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds.

Furthermore, these energy fluctuations were so tremendous that even the four subsidiary city lords couldn't help but be astonished.

"Is that the holy remains?" Sun Tu asked with an elated expression.

The other Profound City cultivators were unable to see the ball of crimson light within the crater, but they could all sense the formidable energy fluctuations surging through the air as well.

"Fellow daoists, the holy remains have already been revealed! Let's make one final effort!" E Kuai rallied with an ecstatic look on his face, and the five city lords immediately redoubled their efforts, chanting their incantation and making hand seals with far more urgency than before.

As a result, the blood in the pond began to churn even more violently, and it began rising up into the air before gushing into the five statues as five pillars of blood.

The blood level in the pond was rapidly lowering, and in just mere moments, all of the blood in the pond had vanished into the five statues.

The scale-like patterns on the surfaces of the five statues began flashing erratically, following which the statues turned from dark red to a shade of bright red.

At the same time, the true form of the ball of crimson light was also revealed, and it was a door of crimson light, within which was what appeared to be another world.

The powerful energy fluctuations were coming from inside the door of light, and there were no holy remains to be seen at all.

Furthermore, with no more blood in the way, the energy fluctuation emanating from the door of light had become even more formidable.

"What's the meaning of this, City Lord E? Where are the holy remains?" Sun Tu asked with a dark expression, and the other three city lords turned to E Kuai as well.

However, E Kuai paid no heed to the four of them as he remained seated atop his stone statue with his eyes closed, continuing to make hand seals while chanting an incantation on his own.

All of a sudden, a burst of radiant crimson light erupted out of the statue beneath him, illuminating his entire body crimson.

Immediately thereafter, seven or eight thick tendrils of crimson light shot out of the statue, then fused into E Kuai's body after flailing around momentarily.

E Kuai's body trembled violently for a moment before falling still again, and he opened his eyes to reveal that they had turned bright red.

Not only that, but his body had swelled up significantly like a balloon, and a series of red patterns had appeared over his skin, giving him the appearance of a hellish demon.

The four city lords' expressions changed drastically upon seeing this, and in particular, Qin Yuan had immediately sprung to his feet, but before he had a chance to get away, a burst of crimson light suddenly erupted out of his lower abdomen.

The burst of crimson light then swelled to form a crimson cloud that encompassed half of Qin Yuan's body.

Countless runes could be seen within the crimson cloud, resonating with the statue beneath him, and he seemed to have been completely immobilized.

Almost at the exact same moment, bursts of crimson light also erupted out of the bodies of the other three city lords, forming crimson clouds that immobilized them as well.

All of the other Profound City cultivators immediately stepped forward with alarmed looks on their faces upon seeing this, but all of a sudden, Shao Ying, Zhu Ziyuan, and Zhu Ziqing appeared in their path.

"The five city lords are currently operating the array, so it would be best for all of you to stay back," Shao Ying said as a tremendous aura erupted out of his body, striking everyone with a sense of asphyxiation.

Stunned looks appeared on their faces as they reflexively stopped in their tracks.

Out of everyone present, Mistress Liu Hua was the only one who remained calm and composed, seemingly completely unsurprised by this turn of events.

Inside the array, E Kuai cast his gaze toward the other four city lords, and at this moment, all of the warmth that had previously been in his eyes was completely absent.

The hearts of the other city lords immediately sank upon seeing this.

Clinging onto one final shred of hope, Fu Jian forced a smile onto his own face as he asked, "What are you doing, City Lord E?"

"The holy remains still haven't emerged, so I can't allow the four of you to leave. It was apparent to me that the four of you were getting cold feet, so I had no choice but to employ some measures to make you stay," E Kuai replied with a faint smile.

"Drop the act, E Kuai! You clearly planned all of this from the very beginning!" Sun Tu harrumphed coldly. "How did you manage to do this? We've all been so careful up to this point..."

"It was the Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds!" Chen Yang exclaimed as a look of realization appeared in his eyes, and the eyes of the other three city lords instantly changed slightly upon hearing this.

"Well done, Fellow Daoist Chen! You're as sharp as ever. I knew that none of you would be able to resist the Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds that I planted," E Kuai confirmed with a smile.

"City Lord Sun, City Lord Fu, didn't you two say that you didn't find any Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds?" Qin Yuan asked as he turned to Sun Tu and Fu Jian, and their expressions instantly stiffened slightly upon hearing this.

It was clear that they had been lying, and that they had also obtained Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds, but had chosen to keep that a secret for some reason.

"So that's why there were so many Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds in that area! You've been plotting against us from the very beginning! What are your intentions?" Chen Yang asked.

"You'll all find out soon enough," E Kuai chuckled as he made a string of hand seals, and countless crimson patterns abruptly appeared in the surrounding array, instantly making the array several times more complex than before.

Countless patterns appeared on the crimson light barrier as well, giving it a far more substantial form.

At the same time, radiant crimson light also erupted out of the statues beneath the four city lords before surging into their bodies.

The four city lords struggled with all their might, but they were completely immobilized by the crimson clouds around them, and they could only look on helplessly as the crimson light invaded their bodies.

A series of squiggly crimson patterns appeared over their skin, and these patterns were writhing and moving as if they were living creatures. All four of them began to tremble as agonized looks appeared on their faces, much to the alarm of all of their subordinates.

"City Lord Sun!" Fang Chan yelled in an urgent voice as he sprang forward through the air, followed closely by Duan Tong, Xuanyuan Xing, and Lü Gang.

In contrast, Shi Chuankong backed away from the scene, following Han Li's instructions to remain a detached observer.

A cold sneer appeared on Shao Ying's face as he swept a hand through the air, unleashing five bursts of sharp power that resembled five divine swords slicing through space, leaving five deep trenches in the ground in their wake.

……

Meanwhile, Han Li was on his way back to joining the main group when his entire body abruptly stiffened, and he fell to the ground without any warning.

A burst of crimson light had erupted out of his lower abdomen, forming a crimson cloud that encompassed his entire body.

After sweeping his spiritual sense through his own body, Han Li immediately identified the source of this crimson cloud.

Those Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds have been tampered with!

At this moment, a pair of glowing, crimson clouds had appeared within his abdomen, releasing countless tiny crimson runes that were giving off formidable restrictive forces, rendering him completely immobile.

Chapter 960: Internal Conflict

Even though Han Li had suddenly been immobilized, he remained calm and collected as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might to fight against the restrictions in his body.

However, the restrictions were situated deep within his dantian, and they were completely resistant to his efforts to counteract them.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as several translucent chains flew out of his glabella before vanishing into his own dantian.

The restrictions in his dantian had immobilized his body, but they had no effect on his spiritual sense.

After burrowing into his dantian, the spiritual sense chains wrapped themselves around the two crimson cloud restrictions before tearing at them with all their might, and the restrictions immediately began to tremble slightly.

Han Li was quite relieved to see that his spiritual sense chains were effective on these restrictions, and he took a deep breath as he redoubled his efforts, and a series of translucent threads shot out of his glabella before intertwining together to form a small, translucent sword.

The sword was only around an inch in length, but the spiritual sense fluctuations that it was giving off were far more formidable than those of the spiritual sense chains, and it was none other than Han Li's Spiritual Sense Sword.

The Spiritual Sense Sword vanished into his dantian in a flash, then swelled to around twice its original size, giving off such formidable sword intent that that the surfaces of the two crimson cloud restrictions immediately began rippling incessantly.

The Spiritual Sense Sword then flew straight into one of the crimson clouds, and the latter was instantly sliced into two before exploding into countless specks of crimson light without being able to put up any resistance.

The residual specks of crimson light were then quickly cleared away by the bloodline power in Han Li's body.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and the Spiritual Sense Sword swung around at his behest to strike the other crimson cloud, quickly eradicating it as well.

With the two crimson clouds gone, Han Li instantly regained his mobility, and a contemplative look appeared on his face as he returned to his feet.

It was clear that these restrictions had come from the two Sulfurous Flame Blood Clouds that he had devoured, and with that in mind, a thought suddenly occurred to Han Li, following which he immediately continued to hurry back to the main group.

……

Meanwhile, the subordinates of the four subsidiary city lords were still locked in a fierce battle against Shao Ying and the Zhu siblings.

Even though Fang Chan and the others had a numbers advantage, they were clearly on hte back foot, and it didn't take long before they began suffering injuries.

Shi Chuankong was looking on with an urgent expression, but he continued to refrain from entering the fray.

Inside the array, more and more crimson lines were appearing over the bodies of the four subsidiary city lords, and Fu Jian was howling in agony as he pleaded, "Please spare me, City Lord E! I've always been your most loyal servant!"

"I know you're loyal, and that's why I gave you this opportunity. You should be honored to sacrifice yourself for the greater good of Profound City," E Kuai replied with a faint smile, and there wasn't even a hint of sympathy in his eyes.

The crimson light pouring out of the four statues continued to surge into the bodies of the four subsidiary city lords, and it wasn't going to take long before the crimson lines spread over the entirety of their bodies.

"Fine! If this is how you're going to treat us, then there's no need for me to hold back any longer!" Fu Jian roared in a furious voice before opening his mouth to release a streak of white light, which contained a talisman that bore an image of a small dagger with a serrated edge.

A translucent dagger projection shot out of the talisman, then pierced into his lower abdomen in a flash.

A faint thump rang out, and much of the crimson cloud around Fu Jian's upper body instantly dissipated, allowing him to free his arms.

However, the crimson cloud around his lower body remained as dense as ever, rooting him to the stone statue down below.

"So you had a Soul Dagger Talisman up your sleeve this entire time," E Kuai mused, but he didn't seem to be particularly concerned.

After freeing his own arms, Fu Jian immediately swept both hands through the air, and four thin streaks of black light shot out of his sleeves, with two of them hurtling directly toward E Kuai, while the other two were aimed at the statue down below.

At the same time, he opened his mouth once again to release three more streaks of white light, which pierced into the bodies of Sun Tu and the others in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, much of the crimson clouds around them dissipated, and their upper bodies were freed as well.

"Thank you, City Lord Fu. Don't hold back anymore, fellow daoists! We're all going to have to work together if we want to survive!" Chen Yang yelled as he swept both sleeves through the air, and out of his left sleeve flew three short yellow spears, all of which immediately sped toward E Kuai like lightning.

At the same time, a bone saber appeared in his right hand, and he slashed it down upon the statue beneath him with all his might.

Sun Tu and Qin Yuan also retaliated as soon as they were freed, sending a black sword projection and a streak of resplendent crimson light hurtling toward E Kuai.

Simultaneously, they were also attacking the statues beneath themselves.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, but E Kuai remained completely unconcerned.

A mocking sneer appeared on his face as he switched to a different hand seal, and a crimson light barrier instantly emerged over each of the statues beneath the four subsidiary city lords.

The statue beneath E Kuai also began to release radiant crimson light that formed a protective light barrier.

A string of resounding explosions rang out, as lights of different colors flashed within the array, while the nearby ground also trembled violently.

Fang Chan, Shao Ying, and the others hurriedly stopped what the were doing upon hearing the commotion, then backed away from one another before looking into the array.

All of the lights in the array quickly faded away, and it was revealed that E Kuai and the five stone statues remained completely unscathed.

The crimson light barriers around the statues appeared to be rather thin, but they were extremely resilient.

Stunned looks appeared on the faces of the four subsidiary city lords upon seeing this, while E Kuai sneered, "The Weeping Blood Array is not something the likes of you can even hope to destroy. You should save your energy. Maybe you'll be able to survive a little longer then."

Immediately thereafter, the stone statues beneath the four subsidiary city lords up lit upon again, and countless threads of crimson light shot forth before ensnaring them.

Numerous tadpole-like crimson runes were dancing around the threads of light, all of which were giving off a glacial aura.

In the blink of an eye, the four subsidiary city lords had been tied up from head to toe by these threads of crimson light, and the glacial power within the threads of light instantly seeped into their bodies, immobilizing them once again.

A pleased look appeared in E Kuai's eyes upon seeing this, and he returned to what he was doing before.

The light radiating from the five statues grew brighter and brighter, and more and more threads of crimson light emerged, forming four giant crimson cocoons around the subsidiary city lords in the blink of an eye.

A look of despair instantly appeared in the eyes of Fang Chan and the others upon seeing this.

"The fates of your city lords are sealed, so you should all just surrender to spare yourselves of unnecessary suffering," Shao Ying sneered.

A cold look flashed through Fang Chan's eyes as he pounced forward once again, and before long, the battle between the two sides resumed.

Meanwhile, E Kuai sliced his own finger open, then began inscribing runes onto the air before him.

A series of crimson runes that were roughly a foot in size took shape under his fingertip, then drifted away before fusing into different parts of the surrounding array.

More lines began to appear on the Weeping Blood Array, and in the blink of an eye, it had become far more complex than before, once again.

At this point, E Kuai's complexion was looking a little pale, and it seemed that setting up this massive array had been quite a taxing endeavor for him, but his eyes were glowing with elation as he made one final hand seal.

The entire array instantly began to glow brightly at his behest, releasing a thick pillar of crimson light that encompassed the door of light at the bottom of the pond.

A burst of thunderous rumbling began to ring out from within the door of light, following which a burst of viscous crimson light shot out of it.

The burst of crimson light was as viscous as blood, and there were many black impurities within it, but it was giving off tremendous bloodline power, even more so than the blood in the pond from before.

The burst of crimson light seemed to be rather reluctant to conform, but in the end, it was unable to resist the Weeping Blood Array and fused into the latter.

The entire array instantly began to glow even brighter, and instead of dissipating after entering the array, the burst of viscous light flowed through it like a crimson python, making its way over to the crimson cocoon that Fu Jian was in before vanishing into it in a flash.

Radiant light instantly erupted out of the crimson cocoon, while countless crimson runes danced over its surface, and the aura that the cocoon was giving off began to fluctuate violently.

In the next instant, the burst of viscous crimson light emerged from the back of the cocoon before continuing onward.

Much of the black impurities within it had been eradicated, as if it had undergone some type of purification process.

E Kuai was very pleased to see this, and the burst of viscous light roamed over to the crimson cocoon that Sun Tu was in at his behest before vanishing into it.

Before long, the burst of crimson light re-emerged from the back of the cocoon once again, this time with even fewer impurities within it.

After that, it passed through Chen Yang and Qin Yuan's cocoons as well, and after four bouts of purification, all of the black impurities within it had faded away.

E Kuai made a beckoning motion with an elated look on his face, and the purified burst of crimson light quickly made its way over to him before vanishing into his body.

Chapter 961: Battle of Life and Death

After the crimson light entered his body, E Kuai shuddered as a pained look appeared on his face, but it was quickly overshadowed by an expression of elation as he closed his eyes and channeled his cultivation arts to harness the power within the crimson light.

His limbs began to swell up slightly while also glowing with radiant crimson light, and the indistinct profound acupoints on his body were rapidly attaining substantial forms one after another.

This rate of profound acupoint attainment was several times faster than what was achieved by absorbing the blood within the pond.

More and more crimson light continued to surge incessantly out of the door of light before being purified by the four subsidiary city lords, following which it was absorbed by E Kuai.

In what seemed like no more than the blink of an eye, he had already opened over twenty profound acupoints, and his aura was also becoming more and more immense, hanging over everyone like an all-encompassing cloud.

In contrast, the auras of the four subsidiary city lords began to gradually wane.

Meanwhile, a battle was still raging around the array.

Fang Chan was standing behind the statue that Sun Tu was situated on, and there was a ferocious look on his face, giving him the appearance of a fearsome beast.

He let loose one thunderous roar after another, sending powerful soundwaves sweeping toward the statue, only for them to be kept out by the crimson light barrier around the array.

The surface of the light barrier was rippling incessantly in the face of the soundwaves, and before long, the entire light barrier was beginning to look a little unstable.

A hint of surprise flashed through Shao Ying's eyes upon seeing this.

According to E Kuai, none of the cultivators outside of the five city lords aside from Mistress Liu Hua and Shao Ying should've been able to pose any threat to this crimson light barrier, yet it seemed like Fang Chan was doing just that.

Several seconds later, the rippling of the crimson light barrier gradually subsided.

On the other side, the bandages around Duan Tong's right arm had already been unraveled, revealing a series of strange black patterns on his enormous arm.

He let loose a thunderous roar as he sprang up into the air, then threw a punch down at the crimson light barrier.

All of the black patterns on his arm lit up, and his already massive arm bulged even further as close to a hundred profound acupoints appeared over its surface.

The black patterns on his arm grew brighter and brighter, releasing waves of scorching heat as it accumulated more and more power.

Duan Tong came swooping down with a look of single-minded determination and ferocity on his face, sending his fist crashing down upon the statue before him with all his might.

Right at this moment, Zhu Ziyuan sprang up into the air, appearing directly in front of Duan Tong in a flash before thrusting his bone spear through the air.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as the tip of Zhu Yuanzi's spear struck Duan Tong's fist, and formidable shockwaves erupted in all directions in the form of gusts of fierce wind.

Zhu Ziyuan's bone spear was forced back to the point that its tip had almost completely folded over itself, and he gave a cold harrumph as he grabbed tightly onto his spear with both hands.

At the same time, dozens of profound acupoints lit up over his arms in unison, while the star acupoints on the bone spear also began glowing radiantly.

A burst of tremendous starpower erupted out of his body before gushing into the spear along his arms, and the tip of the spear was instantly bolstered, returning to its original form.

Duan Tong was sent flying back by the force of the tip of Zhu Ziyuan's bone spear springing back to its original orientation, and after landing on the ground, he immediately launched himself forward once again without any delay while swinging his fist at Zhu Ziyuan.

A battle immediately commenced between the two, and Zhu Ziqing was just about to go and back up her brother when she spotted Xuanyuan Xing attacking the crimson light barrier from another direction.

Her brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and after a brief hesitation, she chose to engage Xuanyuan Xing in battle instead.

All the while, Shi Chuankong was looking on with tightly furrowed brows, seemingly very hesitant about how to proceed.

Prior to his departure, Han Li had told him to do his best to remain a passive bystander, but it was clear that the Shao Ying's trio had gained the upper hand here. At this rate, it was only a matter of time before Fang Chan and the others were defeated, at which point he would be all on his own and more vulnerable than ever.

Mistress Liu Hua had also remained a passive bystander this entire time, making no effort to damage the array or oppose the subordinates of the four subsidiary city lords. Instead, all he did was remain standing on the spot with a grim expression, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

Meanwhile, the elder from Profound End City by the name of Lü Gang was also attempting to damage the array, but to no effect.

Right at this moment, another thunderous roar rang out as Fang Chan stomped his feet down onto the ground to adopt a horse stance, shattering the stone slabs beneath his feet in the process.

He clenched his fists tightly, and veins bulged on his forehead as he let loose a pained roar.

Immediately thereafter, the muscles on his body began to rapidly bulge, and tufts of coarse black fur appeared over his skin as his body swelled up like a balloon. In the blink of an eye, he had transformed into a half-human, half-boar creature, and his eyes had turned bright red.

At the same time, his aura had also swelled drastically, and no one dared to get close to him.

"I didn't know that you possessed a true spirit bloodline," Shao Ying mused as his eyes narrowed slightly, and even Mistress Liu Hua had turned to look at Fang Chan with a surprised look in his eyes.

Shi Chuankong was also quite surprised to hear this, but it only took him a single glance to determine that this was definitely not some true spirit bloodline. Instead, he was using some type of secret technique to stimulate his own devilish bloodline in order to achieve this transformation.

After completing his transformation, Fang Chan sprang up into the air, then inhaled deeply before letting loose another resounding roar.

The soundwaves coming out of Fang Chan's mouth were more powerful than ever before, and they crashed against the crimson light barrier like gusts of ferocious wind.

The light barrier trembled violently, and a deep indentation appeared on its surface under the force of the tremendous soundwaves, looking as if it really were about to be overwhelmed.

A look of urgency finally appeared on Shao Ying's face upon seeing this, and he abruptly vanished from the spot, then instantly reappeared behind Fang Chan before reaching out to grab at him from behind.

Fang Chan made no effort to defend himself as he continued to roar with all his might, trying to break the crimson light barrier in one fell swoop.

Inside the Weeping Blood Array, E Kuai took a glance in his direction, following which a cold sneer appeared on his face as he casually made a hand seal.

A burst of crimson light instantly surged out of the wings of the stone statue beneath him before fusing into the crimson light barrier, instantly restoring it to its former condition.

A look of despair appeared in Fang Chan's eyes upon seeing this, and before he could do anything else, he was dealt a heavy blow on the back.

White light was radiating from Shao Ying's arm as his fingers pierced into Fang Chan's back like five sharp swords, sending blood splattering in all directions.

Fang Chan plummeted to the ground in a puddle of his own blood before falling completely still, and it was unclear whether he was dead or alive.

A grim look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon seeing this, and right at this moment, E Kuai ordered, "Kill all of these annoying pests! I don't want any more distractions from them."

"Yes, City Lord E," Shao Ying replied in a respectful manner, and he took a glance at Fang Chan, then turned his gaze toward Shi Chuankong and Lü Gang.

After witnessing Fang Chan's failed attempt to breach the crimson light barrier, Lü Gang's heart had already sunk into the pits of despair, and he shuddered at the sight of Shao Ying's hawk-like gaze before rushing back toward the three stone arch bridges that they had come from.

"You're not going anywhere!" Shao Ying sneered as he set off in pursuit.

Over 160 profound acupoints had already lit up over the elder's body, but his speed couldn't even hold a candle to Shao Ying's, and the gap between the two of them was closed before he could even reach the stone bridges.

Right as Shao Ying's fingers were about to pierce into his back, Lü Gang suddenly stopped cold in his tracks, then swiveled around before thrusting a white dagger at Shao Ying.

All of a sudden, he was displaying far superior speed than when he was fleeing toward the stone bridges, so even Shao Ying was caught slightly off guard.

However, instead of taking any evasive measures, Shao Ying merely gave a cold harrumph as a layer of white starlight appeared over his fingers, and grabbed directly at the oncoming dagger with his bare hand.

A sharp clang rang out as the space within the palm of Shao Ying's hand warped slightly, and the dagger was instantly snapped upon entering the warped space.

Taking advantage of this brief window of respite, Lü Gang darted back in retreat, but instead of continuing to flee, he leaped straight over Shao Ying before landing beside Shi Chuankong.

At this moment, the severely wounded Fang Chan was laying at Shi Chuankong's feet, and the latter was in the process of feeding the former a bright red pill.

"Well done, Elder Lü," Shi Chuankong praised as he rose to his feet.

"So you instructed him to lure me away in order to buy you time to save Fang Chan, is that right?" Shao Ying asked in a cold voice.

"City Lord E is clearly intent on killing all of us, so we have no choice but to band together," Shi Chuankong replied.

Chapter 962: Biding Time

"You may have managed to fool me this time, but you're only delaying the inevitable. Even if you combine your powers, it won't amount to anything," Yin Shao sneered with a sinister grin on his face.

He then reached behind himself with both hands, putting on a pair of white bone claws that were riddled with dozens of glowing star acupoints, clearly indicating that it was a star artifact of a very high caliber.

At the same time, one profound acupoint after another lit up over his body, only stopping once the total count had reached 283.

Grim looks appeared on the faces of both Shi Chuankong and Lü Gang upon seeing this. 283 profound acupoints was a number that placed Shao Ying on the same level as the four subsidiary city lords. In fact, he already outstripped the likes of Qin Yuan.

Right at this moment, Fang Chan's immobile body began to stir slightly, and before long, he had struggled to his feet.

Wisps of crimson mist were rising up from the gruesome wound on his back, and the flesh around the wound was rapidly healing at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

At the same time, he rose up several dozen more feet in height, and black scales began to appear over his chest, shoulders, and neck, making him appear no different from a fearsome scaled beast.

"What did you feed him just now?" Shao Ying asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"It's called a Blood Tide Pill, I'm not sure if you would've heard of it before," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

The Blood Tide Pill had been given to him by Shi Pokong, so there was a chance that it was meant to harm him rather than help him, just like that jade pendant, but with Fang Chan on the verge of death, he had no choice but to feed it to him.

For the moment, it seemed like the pill was working as intended. In fact, it was proving to be far more effective than Shi Chuankong anticipated.

"So it's just a pill that temporarily stimulates his bloodline power. I should've known that you wouldn't have anything good up your sleeve," Shao Ying sneered, then abruptly vanished from the spot.

Shi Chuankong was already prepared, and he raised the purple staff in his hands before sweeping it through the air to his side.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as two sets of sharp bone claws raked over its surface, raising several trails of sparks in the process.

Shao Ying flew back in retreat, and upon steadying himself, he cast his gaze toward the staff in Shi Chuankong's hands with a surprised look in his eyes.

Right at this moment, a giant shadow loomed over his head, and Fang Chan came swooping down upon him while swatting a massive hand down at his head.

Shao Ying was just barely able to evade the attack, and the ground that had been beneath his feet just a moment ago was completely pulverized amid a resounding boom, creating a huge crack that extended all the way to the crimson light barrier..

Before he had a chance to steady himself, Lü Gang pounced at him from behind, holding a glowing white dagger that he pierced directly at the back of Shao Ying's head.

Shao Ying harrumphed coldly as he placed one hand behind his own hand to protect himself while making a tugging motion with his other hand. The bone claw on his latter hand immediately began to glow with radiant starlight, releasing a burst of formidable tearing force that caused the space behind him to warp and twist.

Lü Gang was drawn involuntarily toward Shao Ying by this burst of tearing force, and he hurriedly began to backpedal in an alarmed manner, only managing to stop himself in his tracks after his feet had sunk deep into the ground.

However, before he even had a chance to catch his breath, Shao Ying had already swung around to attack him.

Thankfully, Shi Chuankong and Fang Chan had also already arrived on the scene, and the three of them joined forces to oppose Shao Ying.

On the other side, Xuanyuan Xing possessed a slight cultivation base advantage over Zhu Ziqing, but the latter's bone armor and bone spear were all extremely formidable star artifact, thereby bridging the gap between them, so it was unclear who was going to come out on top between the two.

At the same time, Zhu Ziyuan and Duan Tong were also locked in a fierce battle against each other, one that was fraught with peril.

Countless dark purple runes had appeared over Duan Tong's exposed skin, and they were all giving off bursts of scorching heat.

Plumes of black mist began to rise up from his body as the heat became more and more intense, forming a black cloud around him that made it impossible to gauge the number of profound acupoints on his body.

After forcing back Duan Tong with his spear, Zhu Ziyuan darted back to open up some distance between the two of them as a wary look appeared in his eyes.

"Looks like you've made significant strides since the previous Five City Martial Gathering," Zhu Ziyuan mused.

"I was planning to even the score with Gu Qianxun, but you're the one who has to face the result of my last one thousand years of training now!" Duan Tong replied in a cold voice.

Zhu Ziyuan took a glance at his sister out of his peripheral vision to see how she was faring in her battle, and Duan Tong was furious to see this.

"How dare you get distracted when you're facing me!" he roared as he launched himself at Zhu Ziyuan while swinging his right fist through the air.

His right fist was extraordinarily massive to begin with, and now that it was enshrouded in black mist, it resembled a devilish black lion biting down upon Zhu Ziyuan's head.

Zhu Ziyuan turned his attention back to Duan Tong, then swung his spear upward, and a ball of white starlight emerged over the tip of the spear to clash against Duan Tong's right fist.

As the ball of white light clashed against the black mist, it resembled a resplendent sun piercing into a dark cloud, and the black mist churned violently while rapidly evaporating to reveal Duan Tong's fist once again.

However, it was no longer clenched into a fist. Instead, he had grabbed tightly onto the tip of Zhu Ziyuan's spear.

Zhu Ziyuan was holding the shaft of his spear with both hands as he hoisted it upward, and a series of star acupoints lit up over the spear in rapid succession, releasing dazzling white light that spilled through the gaps between Duan Tong's fingers.

Even so, Duan Tong still refused to release the spear, and he allowed himself to be hoisted up into the air by Zhu Ziyuan.

Right at this moment, a vast expanse of crimson light suddenly erupted out the runes on Duan Tong's arm, while plumes of dense mist surged out of the palm of his hand, drifting toward Zhu Ziyuan like a nest of snakes.

Zhu Ziyuan's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he tightened his grip around the shaft of his spear, upon which a burst of tremendous starpower erupted out of its star acupoints in unison to dispel the oncoming plumes of mist.

However, before he had a chance to do anything else, a loud crack suddenly rang out from the tip of his spear.

He hurriedly cast his gaze toward the tip of the spear to discover that it seemed to have already completely decomposed. Not only had it turned a corrupted, black color, it had shattered all the way from its tip to its shaft.

Zhu Ziyuan was just about to dart back in retreat when he suddenly felt his entire body go stiff, and an alarmed look appeared in his eyes.

Crap! This is Paralysis Death Poison!

All of a sudden, he felt as if his legs had been filled with lead, and even the slightest movement had become an extremely arduous feat.

"I've already refined Paralysis Death Poison into my arm, so your fate was sealed from the very beginning!" Duan Tong roared as he threw a punch at Zhu Ziyuan, and his giant right fist came crashing down with tremendous power.

An alarmed look appeared on Zhu Ziqing's face as she saw this unfold from afar, and in her moment of distraction, she was struck by a blow to the shoulder from Xuanyuan Xing. The bone armor on her shoulder was instantly shattered, and she was sent flying like a rucksack.

A furious look appeared in Zhu Ziyuan's eyes upon seeing this, and all of the profound acupoints on his body lit up as he somehow mustered up the strength required to swivel around and evade Duan Tong's fist.

……

In the heat of battle, no one had noticed that all of the yellow clouds in the sky were currently converging toward the hall from all directions, as if they had been herded here by some type of mystical force.

Under the all-encompassing blanket of yellow clouds, the entire area in a radius of dozens of kilometers around the hall had been plunged into complete darkness.

The layer of clouds in the sky was only continuing to grow thicker and denser, and they gradually formed a giant vortex, at the center of which was a black hole that was looking down at the hall below like a giant eye.

Thick arcs of lightning were flashing incessantly within the vortex amid bursts of dull rumbling, and before long, the vortex had swelled to an enormous size.

Furthermore, there was a burst of devastating power accumulating within it, seemingly waiting for an opportunity to erupt.

……

Inside the hall, the four subsidiary city lords in the Weeping Blood Array were slumped over their stone statues, and all of them were trembling uncontrollably, while their complexions had turned deathly pale.

It seemed like all of them had already given up hope, and they weren't even bothering to try and resist anymore.

All of a sudden, Han Li silently appeared on one of the stone arch bridges leading deeper into the darkness, but instead of immediately revealing himself, he carefully concealed his own aura to observe the unfolding scene from afar.

The first thing that he noticed was that something had clearly gone awry in the Weeping Blood Array, and that the four subsidiary city lords were all in terrible condition.

Before he had a chance to analyze the situation, his attention was drawn to Lü Gang, who had just failed to land a sneak attack on Shao Ying, only for the latter to pounce on the opportunity to retaliate and pierce both sets of bone claws into his chest.

Shao Ying then brought his hands apart, and Lü Gang's entire body was torn into two amid a blood-curdling howl.

Before his nascent soul had a chance to escape, it was also torn to shreds by a swipe from Shao Ying's claws.

Fang Chan let loose a thunderous roar upon seeing this, sending powerful soundwaves sweeping toward Shao Ying, but the latter merely darted away to the side to evade the attack before rushing directly at Shi Chuankong.

Chapter 963: More Than Meets the Eye

At this point, Shi Chuankong's entire body was already riddled with wounds, and he appeared to be quite calm and collected on the surface, but internally, he was feeling very concerned.

There was such a huge power gap between the two sides that even in a three-on-one battle, they were still no match for Shao Ying, and now that Lü Gang was dead, the situation had become even more dire.

In the face of the oncoming Shao Ying, Shi Chuankong was forced to take a step back before swinging his purple staff rapidly through the air, unleashing a flurry of staff projections that descended upon Shao Ying like a waternight net.

In response, Shao Ying merely reached out with one hand, and a burst of tremendous starpower erupted out of his bone claws to eradicate most of the staff projections, following which he lashed out with his other set of bone claws at Shi Chuankong's waist, aiming to tear him in half just like he had done with Lü Gang!

Han Li was just about to intervene when Fang Chan came barreling in from the side, but this played right into Shao Ying's hands, and a sinister grin appeared on his face as he stopped cold in his tracks, then darted back in retreat to avoid Fang Chan.

Right as Fang Chan passed him by, a series of profound acupoints lit up over his arm, and he slammed his bone claws viciously into Fang Chan's back.

A dull thump rang out as a burst of devastating power erupted out of his bone claws, pulvering Fang Chan's back and sending him flying through the air.

With Fang Chan's enormous frame, it was very difficult for him to arrest his own momentum, and he crashed straight through the railing on the edge of the altar before plunging into the dark abyss below.

Shi Chuankong wanted to swoop in to save him, but it was already too late.

"Don't worry, you're next," Shao Ying said as he turned to Shi Chuankong with a cold sneer.

Shi Chuankong's brows were tightly furrowed, but his eyes suddenly lit up ever so slightly as he took a glance in the direction of the three stone arch bridges on the other side of the altar, and he grasped tightly onto his purple staff as he prepared to face Shao Ying in battle.

A series of profound acupoints lit up over Shao Ying's legs, and he launched himself forward at an incredible speed.

In the blink of an eye, he had already reached Shi Chuankong, and his two sets of bone claws were glowing radiantly as he pierced them straight at Shi Chuankong's chest.

Shi Chuankong was very quick to react, raising his staff in front of himself to keep the bone claws at bay, following which he abruptly swung the staff around, tipping Shao Ying upside-down in the process.

Immediately thereafter, profound acupoints lit up over his legs as well, and he threw a vicious kick at Shao Ying's chest.

A burst of tremendous starpower erupted out of the profound acupoints on Shao Ying's body, and he flew directly over Shi Chuankong's head while pushing the purple staff forward with his bone claws.

Shi Chuankong's hands were still wrapped tightly around the staff, and he was tipped forward along with it.

Before he was able to regain his balance, Shao Ying was already upon him.

The disparity in speed between the two was enormous, and Shi Chuankong wasn't able to put up any defenses before Shao Ying caught up to him and plunged a hand straight through his chest, pinning him to the ground.

Shi Chuankong immediately threw up a mouthful of blood as he struggled to get up, only for Shao Ying to stomp down onto his head, driving it into the ground.

He then looked down at Shi Chuankong as he sneered, "If it isn't for the fact that you're still useful to City Lord E, you'd already be long dead by now."

A look of despair appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as he slumped to the ground in a defeated manner, but right as Shao Ying began to lift his foot from his head, he abruptly lifted his legs up from the ground before clamping them tightly around Shao Ying's neck.

Shao Ying was caught completely off guard by this abrupt turn of events, and all of a sudden, he spotted a figure flying out of the darkness in the distance at an incredible speed.

The figure reached him in what felt like the blink of an eye, then swung a white scimitar down at his neck.

The figure was naturally none other than Han Li, and Shao Ying struggled with all his might to free himself, but Shi Chuankong was determined not to let him go, even if it meant having to sacrifice his own life.

Right as he was about to be decapitated by Han Li's scimitar, a cold gleam suddenly flashed through his eyes, and the robes on his back abruptly tore open as a pair of razor sharp bone wings sprang out of his back.

There were around a dozen profound acupoints glowing on the pair of bone wings, and their sharp edges were aimed straight at Han Li.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he stopped in his tracks before darting back in retreat.

The bone wings swept through the air before him, leaving a twisted rift in the space in their wake.

At the same time, a burst of starpower erupted out of Shao Ying's shoulders, freeing him from Shi Chuankong's legs.

He then pulled his bone claws out of Shi Chuankong's chest before kicking him away, following which he spread his bone wings and flew up into the air to glower down at Han Li from above.

"I've been waiting for you," he said with a cold sneer.

Han Li took a glance at Shi Chuankong to find that while his injuries were quite severe, they posed no threat to his life for now.

He then turned his gaze back to Shao Ying as he asked, "Are those wings a part of your body or a star artifact?"

Shao Ying harrumphed coldly and gave no reply as he swooped down at Han Li from above while lashing out with his bone claws like the talons of a bird of prey.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he took a step back, then swung his white scimitar diagonally up at Shao Ying.

In the instant that the scimitar was about to pass the bone claws by, the latter suddenly grabbed onto the former, following which Shao Ying lashed out at Han Li with the pair of bone wings on his back.

Han Li remained completely unfazed as he released the hilt of his scimitar, allowing it to be taken by Shao Ying.

Immediately thereafter, he clenched his fist and channeled his Titan Vajra Arts as he threw a punch at Shao Ying's chest.

His fist was extremely fast, even faster than Shao Ying's bone wings, and it struck him on the chest with a resounding boom.

Shao Ying felt as if his heart had stopped beating for a few seconds from the impact of the punch, and he was struck by a sense of asphyxiation before he was sent flying by a burst of tremendous force.

However, at the same time, he was still able to glance his bone wings over Han Li's back, instantly inflicting a wound so deep that even a section of Han Li's vertebrae had been revealed.

However, Han Li didn't even so much as grimace from his injuries as he channeled his Wingform Ascension Arts to pursue Shao Ying without any hesitation.

He was able to catch up to Shao Ying in mid-air before throwing another punch at his chest, but Shao Ying was able to cross his arms in front of his own chest to defend himself.

A resounding thump rang out as Shao Ying crashed heavily into the edge of the altar, causing the entire altar to shudder violently.

A hint of surprise appeared in E Kuai's eyes upon seeing this, clearly not expecting such a formidable display of power from Han Li.

Shao Ying threw up a mouthful of blood as he hurriedly slashed his bone wings through the air, preemptively retaliating against any further attacks from Han Li.

However, to his surprise, Han Li didn't pounce on this opportunity to continue his assault.

Instead, he had already retreated to quite a distance away, and there was a smile on his face as he chanted an incantation with his hands arranged in a strange seal. Only then did Shao Ying notice that a leaf-shaped jade pendant had appeared on his bloodstained chest.

A horrified flook appeared on his face as he identified the Explosive Space Realm Talisman, but it was already too late for him to do anything.

The veins on the surface of the leaf-shaped jade pendant lit up one after another, and the air around Shao Ying compressed violently, immediately following which a radiant white sun appeared out of thin air to illuminate the darkness.

A violent explosion rang out as a ball of blazing white light exploded before rising up as a white cloud.

Devastating shockwaves swept through the air in all directions, destroying half of the entire altar in the process.

The light barrier around the Weeping Blood Array trembled violently, and it looked as if it were about to be overwhelmed by the shockwaves from the explosion.

E Kuai hurriedly made a hand seal upon seeing this, injecting his own power into the array to bolster the light barrier against the explosion.

Only after close to twenty seconds had passed did the shockwaves gradually subside, and one half of the altar had vanished into thin air, while the other half remained largely unscathed thanks to the protection of the Weeping Blood Array.

Several massive holes had been blown into the ceiling of the hall, and the suffocating blanket of yellow clouds up above were visible through them.

Everyone was caught completely off guard by this sudden turn of events, and Zhu Ziyuan had only just forced back Duan Tong when an instinctive sense of foreboding welled up in his heart.

He immediately rushed over to Xuanyuan Xing, then knocked him back with an attack as well before grabbing onto Zhu Ziqing's arm and dragging her over to Mistress Liu Hua's side.

Meanwhile, Xuanyuan Xing rushed back in retreat to join Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

Ultimately, everyone was able to avoid the explosion from the Explosive Space Realm Talisman, but they were all looking at the massive chunk of the altar that had gone missing with lingering fear in their eyes.

At this point, Shao Ying had already been erased out of existence.

Elsewhere on the altar, much of the black mist around Duan Tong's body had already faded away, and the runes on his skin were also glowing nowhere near as bright as before. On top of that, his entire body was looking very emaciated, with the exception of his right arm, which was still as massive as ever.

By refining Paralysis Death Poison into his own arm, he could enhance his own offensive prowess for a period of time at the expense of his own bloodline power, but evidently, this was extremely taxing on him, and he was already close to a spent force.

Once Zhu Ziyuan realized this, he intentionally began employing stalling tactics to make their battle one of attrition, and over time, Duan Tong's powers began to wane. If it weren't for the fact that Zhu Ziyuan had been startled into retreat by Shao Ying's abrupt demise, perhaps Duan Tong would've already been struck down by now.

Zhu Ziqing was carrying many injuries, but none of them were very severe, and at this moment, she was standing beside her brother while observing Han Li with an amazed expression as she said, "You were right, Big Brother, there really is more to him than meets the eye..."

In her eyes, Shao Ying had always been a very snide and sinister man, so she didn't resent Han Li for killing him.

Meanwhile, Zhu Ziyuan was observing Han Li with an apprehensive look in his eyes.

Chapter 964: Entering the Array

"Well done! I must admit that I'm impressed. To think that even Shao Ying was no match for you!" E Kuai chuckled from within the array.

"You're far too kind, City Lord E. I was only able to come out on top thanks to some little tricks," Han Li replied with a smile as he began to make his way toward the statue beneath Chen Yang.

At this point, the four subsidiary city lords were all seated with their heads drooping down in despair, and it seemed like they didn't even have the energy to look up anymore. It was clear that they were about to perish soon.

In contrast, E Kuai's aura had swelled to unprecedented heights, and over a thousand profound acupoints had already opened up on his body. At this rate, it most likely wasn't going to be difficult for him to open all of the profound acupoints on his body.

"Truth be told, I could really use a man of your talents. Right now, I'm willing to give you another chance. If you do as I say, I'll let you off the hook for killing Shao Ying," E Kuai said with a smile.

"How generous of you, City Lord E. What would you like me to do for you?" Han Li asked as he gently poked the crimson light barrier with his finger.

"Get rid of those two eyesores for me, and you and Fellow Daoist Shi Kong can join my Profound City together to serve as my top-ranking elders. Of course, if you don't want to stay in Profound City, then you can go and serve as the city lord of any of the four other subsidiary cities, but only under the condition that you must follow my orders at all times," E Kuai declared.

"Don't believe him, Fellow Daoist Li! He's been deceiving us from the very beginning!" Xuanyuan Xing yelled in an alarmed manner, and Duan Tong also reflexively clenched his fists tightly upon hearing this.

Han Li took a glance at the two of them, then sighed, "It's very thoughtful of you to extend this olive branch to both myself and Fellow Daoist Shi, City Lord E. It's just a pity that I'm not from the Scalptia Spatial Domain. Otherwise, I really wouldn't be able to think of a good reason to turn down such an offer."

"Is that a no then? What a pity. In that case, I'll have to ask you to wait until I'm done here to continue our conversation," E Kuai replied in an indifferent manner.

"There's no need to wait, I'll come into the array to meet you right now, City Lord E," Han Li said with a smile.

E Kuai immediately burst into laughter upon hearing this, as if he had just been told a hilarious joke.

"I'll gladly welcome you into the array, Fellow Daoist Li. Let's see if you have what it takes to make it in here."

Han Li remained completely unfazed as he said, "I'll do my best."

He then made a hand seal while chanting a complex incantation, following which he raised a hand, and all of the profound acupoints on his arm lit up as he swung his hand down at the statue before him in a powerful chopping motion.

A burst of white starlight appeared over his hand, and it was able to exert immense pressure upon the crimson light barrier, creating a deep indentation on its surface.

E Kuai's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he seemed to be rather taken aback.

However, right as Han Li's hand was about to make contact with the statue beneath Chen Yang, the crimson light barrier suddenly brightened significantly, then sprang back to its original form to force back Han Li.

A faint smile appeared on E Kuai's face upon seeing this.

Shi Chuankong and the others had also previously made futile attempts to breach the light barrier, so they weren't surprised to see Han Li fail in the same endeavor.

Han Li wasn't disheartened by this at all, and he took a deep breath, then made his way over to the statue beneath Sun Tu before repeating the same process.

The outcome was identical, and he was only just barely able to touch the statue before he was repelled by a burst of invisible force.

He then moved onto the statue beneath Qin Yuan and did the same thing.

"You're just a human with fewer than three hundred profound acupoints opened, so there's simply no chance for you to break into the Weeping Blood Array through brute force. No matter how many times you try, it'll always end in failure," E Kuai scoffed with a disdainful shake of his head.

He then paid no further heed to Han Li as he closed his eyes and began absorbing the bloodline power within the Weeping Blood Array at an even faster rate than before.

Chen Yang and the others could sense their own bloodline power surging even more rapidly out of their bodies, and they let loose a collective cry of pain, but their voices weren't very loud due to how feeble they were.

Han Li remained completely unfazed as he carried out the same procedure on the statue beneath Fu Jian, then did the same thing with the statue beneath E Kuai.

All of the 263 profound acupoints on his body lit up in unison, and it was as if a bright sun had appeared over the palm of his hand as he chopped down onto the crimson light barrier.

Right as his hand came into contact with the statue before him, a secret rune that had been hidden up to this point appeared below each of the five statues in unison.

Immediately thereafter, a faint buzzing sound rang out, and the entire crimson light barrier shuddered violently as ripples surged over its surface.

E Kuai's eyes immediately sprang open upon sensing this disturbance, and he looked on with an astonished expression as Han Li stepped straight into the Weeping Blood Array, looking as if he had just made his way through a film of water.

Everyone was astonished to see this.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he sprang up to the very top of the light barrier, hovering in mid-air around ten feet above the five stone statues.

"This Weeping Blood Array truly is a miraculous creation! It feels like there's a vast sea of power swirling around me," Han Li praised.

"Impossible! Anyone inside the array without a Weeping Blood Star Diagram will be reduced to a sacrificial object! How are you able to remain unaffected?" E Kuai exclaimed in an incredulous manner.

"Is this what you're referring to, City Lord E?" Han Li asked with a smile as he extended a finger forward before drawing a circle in the air, and a crimson pentagram identical to ones on the five stone statues took shape beneath his feet.

Right at this moment, a dull thump suddenly rang out from down below.

Han Li looked down to discover that Duan Tong had also attempted to step into the array to save Fu Jian, only to be sent flying back by a burst of tremendous force, much to the amusement of Zhu Ziqing.

A spark of hope was reignited in the hearts of the four subsidiary city lords, and all of them raised their heads with great difficulty to look at Han Li with hopeful expressions.

"I've come to meet you in the array, City Lord E. Are you ready?" Han Li asked with a smile.

A serious look then appeared on his face as he began making a string of hand seals while chanting an urgent incantation, and a few moments later, a burst of dull rumbling suddenly rang out from deep within the array.

All five the statues shuddered in unison, following which a string of brand new runes appeared over each of them, and the operation of the entire array slowed down significantly, as if it were going to stop operating altogether.

However, immediately thereafter, the viscous crimson light at the bottom of the pond rose up once again, then passed through the crimson cocoons around the four subsidiary city lords one after another before surging into E Kuai's body.

E Kuai was rather puzzled to see this, but his befuddlement quickly turned to alarm as he discovered that the purified crimson light flowing into his body was flowing out again before surging into Han Li's body.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li's entire body was enveloped in a giant crimson cocoon consisting of countless thin crimson threads, and he had become the final destination for the crimson light within the array.

As this burst of tremendous power surged into his body, his expression instantly became twisted with agony. He felt as if his meridians were being torn apart from the inside, and he was clenching his teeth so tightly against the pain that they were on the verge of shattering.

He had thought that after being filtered and purified by the city lords, this burst of bloodline power wouldn't be so violent anymore, but the reality was that with only fewer then three hundred profound acupoints opened, his body was still too frail to withstand such tremendous power.

Thankfully, Han Li had developed an extraordinary pain tolerance over the course of his cultivation journey, so he was able to retain his lucidity.

Inside the crimson cocoon, over a thousand specks of white light appeared over his body, but of course, most of them were blurry and insubstantial.

"Impossible! How have you seized control of the Weeping Blood Array? Who are you?" E Kuai exclaimed in an incredulous manner.

Han Li paid no heed to him as he let loose a long roar and channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, funneling the bloodline power surging into his body toward profound acupoints that he was still yet to open.

In the span of no more than twenty seconds, three profound acupoints had opened in rapid succession on his chest, while everyone else looked on in astonishment.

"How could this be, Big Brother? Could it be that this human has some ties with the Great Ruins?" Zhu Ziqing asked.

Shi Chuankong was also looking on with mixed emotions, completely stunned by the fact that Han Li seemed to have gained the upper hand over E Kuai in the Blood Weeping Array.

A cold look appeared in E Kuai's eyes upon seeing this, and he suddenly made a hand seal before tapping a finger against his own glabella.

A strange crimson rune instantly appeared on his glabella, and the crimson light emanating from him instantly brightened to intercept the bloodline power that was flowing out of his body.

As a result, the influx of bloodline power into Han Li's body slowed down, and he turned to E Kuai with a smile as he said, "You are only drawing upon the power of the Weeping Blood Array through illegitimate means, so there's no way you can hope to contend with me."

Chapter 965: Taking Over the Array

"My eyes have truly been opened today! If we were outside the array, I would be able to crush you with a single finger, yet here you are, displaying more insolence than you would ever dare to if we were elsewhere! Let me see what you have up your sleeve to back up that big mouth of yours!" E Kuai sneered.

Immediately thereafter, he made another hand seal before tapping his own glabella several more times in succession, and several more identical runes appeared on his forehead, following which the bloodline power that was seeping out of his body began to return again.

Han Li paid no heed to E Kuai as he began making a string of hand seals of his own, and a burst of white light rose up from his crimson cocoon. Several cracks then appeared over the cocoon's surface, and it bloomed into a nine-tiered crimson lotus flower.

Han Li sat down with his legs crossed, and the crimson lotus flower beneath him began to radiate dazzling crimson light while releasing a burst of tremendous suction force.

The bloodline power that was returning to E Kuai's body instantly began to surge out of him rapidly once again, forming a mighty dragon that hurtled rapidly toward Han Li before plunging headfirst into the nine-tiered crimson lotus flower.

Han Li's eyes immediately widened as veins began to bulge on his forehead. The accelerated influx of power was exacerbating his pain by severalfold, and he felt as if there were countless sharp daggers piercing into his body.

A string of loud booms rang out as several more profound acupoints lit up over his body, and at this point, E Kuai finally came to realize the dire situation that he was in.

Not only was the bloodline power in the array beginning to funnel through his body toward Han Li, even the bloodline power that had accumulated in his body was beginning to seep out.

A furious look appeared on E Kuai's face as he switched to a different hand seal, and a pair of gashes split open on the palms of his hands, bleeding profusely to stain his hands bright red.

He pressed his bloodstained hands firmly into the pentagram beneath himself while chanting an urgent incantation, and the pentagram instantly began to glow brightly while releasing powerful suction force, intercepting the bloodline power that was surging into Han Li's body.

"City Lord E, I must admit that you are the most powerful bodily refinement cultivator I've ever met, but do you still not understand the situation that you're in? I'm more familiar with this array than you are, so you can't beat me while we're in here!" Han Li sneered as he switched to a different hand seal yet again, and the suction force released by the nine-tiered lotus flower instantly increased in potency by severalfold.

A dull thump rang out as the crimson light emanating from the pentagram beneath E Kuai abruptly fizzled out.

He was powerless to contend against Han Li any longer, and he could only look on helplessly as the power in the Weeping Blood Array flowed toward Han Li.

The insubstantial specks of white light on E Kuai's body faded one after another, and before long, all that remained were the one thousand or so profound acupoints that he had already opened.

At the same time, the bloodline power that he thought he had already absorbed began to spill out of his body as well.

At this rate, it wouldn't be long before he was reduced to the same state as the four subsidiary city lords.

A decisive look finally appeared on E Kuai's face as he made a hand seal before slamming a palm down upon the head of the statue beneath him, but Han Li suddenly pointed a finger in his direction as he said, "Don't be in such a hurry to leave, City Lord E. I still need you to stay in the array for a little longer."

A vast expanse of crimson light erupted out of the pentagram beneath E Kuai, following which a seven-petaled crimson lotus flower emerged, then closed itself around him like the mouth of a giant beast.

E Kuai immediately clenched a hand into a tight fist before throwing an almighty punch at the pentagram down below.

Dense clusters of profound acupoints lit up over his arm, releasing a layer of white starlight that was giving off tremendous energy fluctuations.

A resounding boom rang out as E Kuai's fist struck the crimson lotus flower, and the entire statue shuddered violently, but was somehow able to hold itself intact.

A burst of formidable shockwaves erupted in all directions, crashing into the inner wall of the crimson light barrier, causing the entire array to tremble violently, while everyone outside the array looked on with astonished expressions.

Suspended in mid-air, Han Li was also struggling to maintain his balance in the face of these powerful shockwave, and he hurriedly made a string of hand seals to try and stabilize the array, but right at this moment, E Kuai slammed his bloodstained palms down onto the stone statue beneath himself once again.

Two bursts of white light erupted out of the wings on the stone statue's back before erupting outward to forcibly create an opening on the crimson light barrier that was just large enough for a person to fit through.

The opening appeared very unstable, and it began closing as soon as it was opened, but E Kuai had already flown out through it in a flash.

On top of that, as he flew out of the array, he reached out with both hands, and two bone chains shot out of his sleeves, instantly piercing into the crimson cocoons around Sun Tu and Chen Yang.

The two of them were completely powerless to resist as the bone chains pierced through their shoulder blades before wrenching them out of their cocoons toward the opening on the crimson light barrier.

With the three city lords exiting the array, the crimson light was only able to flow through Fu Jian and Qin Yuan before surging into Han Li's body.

Having only undergone two rounds of purification, the bloodline power in the crimson light was far more violent than before, and in the instant that it surged into Han Li's body, he felt as if he were about to be torn apart at the seams.

Han Li hurriedly made a hand seal in an attempt to suppress the raging bloodline power in his body, while E Kuai dragged Chen Yang Sun Tu out of the Weeping Blood Array before tossing them aside like a pair of dirty rags.

Shi Chuankong and the others were all looking on with wary expressions, and none of them dared to approach the three city lords.

"Let's see how much longer you can last with only two people filtering the bloodline power of the array for you! Once you self-detonate, you'll become part of the array, and I'll absorb all of your power as well, so I actually have to thank you for your sacrifice!" E Kuai sneered as he glowered at Han Li from outside the array.

At this moment, Han Li's ears were ringing so violently that he couldn't hear E Kuai at all.

He was channeling the starpower in his own body with all his might, and he was able to stabilize the array again with much difficulty, but with only two city lords acting as filters, the bloodline power within the array was far too violent for him to safely withstand.

A string of dull thumps rang out over Han Li's chest and abdomen as around a dozen more profound acupoints opened up, and what was rather strange about this latest batch of opened profound acupoints was that they were all tinged with hints of crimson light.

At the same time, his body began to swell up like a balloon, and he was in such excruciating pain that anyone with inferior mental fortitude and spiritual sense would've already fallen unconscious in his place.

However, he knew that it was only going to be several more seconds before his body exploded, and in what he perceived to be his own final moments, he wondered if it would be possible for his nascent soul to survive and seek refuge in the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Everyone around the array was watching Han Li intently with mixed emotions, and Zhu Ziqing turned away slightly, seemingly not wanting to watch him self-detonate.

"This is the price that you pay for your insolence!" E Kuai chortled with glee, but to everyone's surprise, Han Li's inflated body suddenly began to slowly contract, and it quickly returned to normal.

Han Li threw his hand over his own head as he let loose an agonized roar, but a hint of clarity had returned to his eyes.

Unbeknownst to everyone else, there was currently a small, green vial in his stomach that was absorbing the violent power surging into his body like an insatiable abyss, and it seemed that there was no limit to its capacity.

As for the agonized look on Han Li's face, that was nothing more than an act that he was putting on to fool everyone.

The vast majority of the power surging into his body was absorbed by the Heaven Controlling Vial, while only a tiny amount was being absorbed by him.

"How is this possible? He definitely shouldn't be able to last this long!" E Kuai roared with a bewildered expression.

Shi Chuankong was already plotting his own escape, and he was also stunned by this sudden turn of events.

"What's going, Big Brother?" Zhu Ziqing asked.

However, Zhu Ziyuan was just as perplexed as she was, and his brows were slightly furrowed as he turned his gaze to E Kuai.

All of a sudden, E Kuai vanished from the spot, only to reappear behind the stone statue beneath Qin Yuan an instant later.

"Let me see if you can keep this up after I get rid of these two as well!" E Kuai sneered.

Chapter 966: Attracting Lightning

A string of cracks and pops rang out from E Kuai's joints as he spoke, and his height was increased by several feet as he reached out with one hand, emulating what Han Li had done earlier as he forced the palm of his hand into the crimson light barrier until he made contact wti the statue inside.

In the instant that he made contact with the statue, he curled his fingers inward forcefully, piercing straight through the crimson light barrier to press his hand against the statue.

Immediately thereafter, he began chanting an urgent incantation, and the statue shuddered as the crimson light emanating from it dimmed significantly.

A dull thump rang out as the crimson cocoon around Qin Yuan imploded, and E Kuai made a hand seal with one hand while making a grabbing motion with the hand that had reached into the array, and a giant crimson hand projection appeared before making a grab for Qin Yuan.

Han Li was just about to intervene when a sense of foreboding suddenly welled up in his heart, and he immediately looked up at the sky.

At the same time, E Kuai also looked up, clearly having sensed the same thing.

At this moment, there were no longer any yellow clouds to be seen through the holes in the ceiling. Instead, all that could be seen was a vast expanse of dazzling silver light that was cascading down like a waterfall.

It was as if liquefied silver lightning were raining down from the heavens, gushing into the hall from above.

An earth-shattering thunderclap rang out, and all of the lightning converged to form an incredibly thick pillar of lightning that came crashing down upon E Kuai's head with unerring accuracy.

Thick arcs of lightning were constantly springing out of the pillar of lightning, and what sounded like draconic roars were ringing out incessantly from within.

Han Li hurriedly drifted over a hundred feet away upon seeing this, while a look of bewilderment flashed through E Kuai's eyes, following which he grabbed onto Qin Yuan and hurled him up at the oncoming pillar of lightning without any hesitation.

A resounding boom rang out, and Qin Yuan's body and nascent soul were completely decimated within the silver lightning before he even had a chance to cry out.

Silver lightning erupted in all directions, illuminating the entire hall, and everyone reflexively took a step back while shielding their own eyes from the dazzling radiance.

Chen Yang had been laying on the ground this entire time, and what everyone had failed to notice was that he had pulled a palm-sized black mirror out of the front of his robe, then traced a bloodstained finger over its surface briefly before verbally communicating something into it.

Immediately thereafter, a ring of white light appeared around E Kuai, and all of the dissipated lightning abruptly converged once again, reforming a pillar of lightning that came crashing down upon him once again.

A grim look appeared on E Kuai's face as he hurriedly darted back over a hundred feet in retreat.

However, right as the pillar of lightning was about to strike the ground where E Kuai had just been standing, it abruptly swerved around and began pursuing him once again.

E Kuai's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he evaded the pillar of lightning once again, only for it to continue pursuing him as if he had a target on his back.

Right at this moment, E Kuai spotted the black mirror that Chen Yang was trying to conceal under his body, and a furious look appeared on his face as he sprang up into the air to evade the pillar of lightning while reaching out into the front of his own robe to pull out a mirror that was completely identical to Chen Yang's, except it was a different color.

"So you've been plotting against me since over a century ago! You can have this back," E Kuai harrumphed coldly as he hurled the mirror at Chen Yang, and it fell to the ground with a loud crack before rolling over to his side.

A streak of white light erupted out of the surface of the mirror, and the streak of light clung to E Kuai's body like glue, following him wherever he went.

"The Yin Yang Lightning Attraction Mirror has already absorbed too much of your aura, so you won't be able to get away," Chen Yang sneered.

E Kuai became even more furious upon hearing this, but he had no time to lash out at Chen Yang as the pillar of lightning was racing after him at an incredible speed.

No one knew where these pillars of lightning had come from, but it had to have been extremely formidable, considering how wary E Kuai was of it.

After evading the pillar of lightning several more times, its speed and power still hadn't waned in the slightest, and a decisive look appeared in E Kuai's eyes upon seeing this.

He drifted onto the altar, taking no further evasive measures as all of the over a thouasnd profound acupoints on his body began to glow radiantly.

A layer of scorching, white starlight enshrouded his entire body, and he lowered his own center of gravity before throwing a punch at the oncoming pillar of lightning.

A resounding boom rang out as the pillar of lightning transformed into a ball of lightning that devoured E Kuai whole.

Arcs of silver lightning sprang incessantly through the air, causing the nearby space to ripple violently, creating countless tiny spatial rifts in the process.

The crimson light barrier was on the verge of being torn apart, but it was able to remain intact thanks to the bloodline power that it was able to draw upon from the array.

Han Li was astonished as he looked up at the sky once again. The sea of yellow clouds had reappeared up above, and at the center was a massive black hole.

Han Li immediately began to bolster the crimson light barrier around the Weeping Blood Array with all his might while also preparing himself to flee at any moment.

Close to twenty seconds later, the ball of lightning finally dissipated to reveal E Kuai, who was still standing, and all of his profound acupoints continued to glow radiantly.

However, his right arm, which had made direct contact with the ball of lightning, had been completely charred black.

A plume of white smoke billowed out of E Kuai's mouth as he exhaled, and all of a sudden, his entire right arm crumbled away into ashes.

However, a burst of white light then appeared over his right shoulder, and a new arm began to rapidly take shape, completely regenerating in the span of no more than several seconds.

At this moment, E Kuai's face was bright red, as was his entire body, and countless veins were bulging beneath his skin, presenting an unsettling sight to behold.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this.

That's the Hazy Helmet Technique!

In the next instant, the unnatural red coloration of E Kuai's skin faded away, and his complexion instantly turned as pale as a sheet.

Not only that, but small spurts of blood began to spray out of all of his profound acupoints, while blood also came gushing involuntarily out of his mouth.

Even though he had managed to withstand the pillar of lightning using the Hazy Helmet Technique, it was so formidable that it had still managed to injure all of his profound acupoints.

"City Lord E!"

Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing flew over to his side with concerned looks on their faces.

E Kuai paid no heed to them as he looked up into the sky, right as seven figures decended from one of the holes in the ceiling, and they were led by none other than Sha Xin.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist E," Sha Xin giggled in a seductive manner, and the woman in purple was standing beside her.

The other five figures to round out the seven were Zhuo Fa, Wu Yun, the brawny man with the braid on his head, and two bald men clad in suits of black armor.

E Kuai didn't seem surprised to see them at all, but all of the other Profound City cultivators were astonished by the sudden arrival of the Puppet City cultivators.

Han Li was also rather taken aback to see the Puppet City cultivators, and his gaze lingered momentarily on the woman in purple before he looked away again. At the same time, he was still putting on an agonized expression when in reality, the vast majority of the bloodline power surging into his body was still being absorbed by the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Upon catching sight of Han Li, the woman in purple suddenly shuddered slightly, and it seemed that she was about to say something, but right at this moment, several golden runes suddenly appeared on her glabella beneath the black veil over her face, and her interest in Han Li abruptly faded away.

No one else had noticed this, but Han Li had been secretly observing her this entire time, so this fleeting reaction from her didn't manage to escape his notice.

Right at this moment, two figures rushed over to join the Puppet City cultivators, namely Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing.

A layer of bright crimson light had appeared over Chen Yang's face, and he seemed to have taken some type of pill that had restored some of his strength.

"Well done, Fellow Daoist Chen. You've made a truly stellar contribution in this elaborate plot of ours," Zhuo Fa praised with an excited look on his face.

"It was only thanks to City Lord Sha's unmatched wisdom that this plan was able to work. After taking over as the city lord of Green Goat City, I offered up this Yin Lightning Mirror to E Kuai, and the yin lightning power contained within it has a strong bodily refinement effect. Just as City Lord Sha predicted, E Kuai would be sure to carry the mirror with him at all times, and that almost led to his downfall!" Chen Yang replied with a smile.

"Fellow Daoist Xuanyuan, you also did a fantastic job of serving as a spy in Profound City for so many years," Zhuo Fa said.

"It's my honor to be able to make a contribution to City Lord Sha," Xuanyuan Xing replied in a respectful manner.

"So all of you have been working together from the very beginning. What brilliant foresight!" E Kuai sneered in a cold voice.

Chapter 967: Vendettas

"Likewise, City Lord E. You've also been plotting against all of us from the very beginning, and I've only done what I did out of self-preservation," Chen Yang repiled.

"Let me remind you of this, Sha Xin: only by working together will we have any chance of securing the holy remains. Without me, even if you find the holy tomb, you definitely won't be able to obtain the holy remains," E Kuai said as he turned to Sha Xin.

"Do you really think I don't know what happened all those years ago? My main objective for approaching you for this collaboration was to have you killed in these Great Ruins!" Sha Xin sneered.

E Kuai harrumphed coldly and didn't say anything further.

"Why has E Kuai come out of the array? Isn't he supposed to be inside the Weeping Blood Array right now?" Sha Xin asked as she turned to Chen Yang with slightly furrowed brows.

"Some unexpected mishaps have taken place, and I was unable to report them to you due to the restrictions around the hall," Chen Yang replied with a wry smile.

A look of realization appeared in E Kuai's eyes upon hearing this.

If he had been inside the array as the pillar of lightning had descended, then he would've undoubtedly been delayed, and there was a chance that he would've been killed on the spot.

It was all thanks to Han Li that he had emerged from the array, and with that in mind, his resentment toward Han Li abated significantly.

"You may have been fortunate enough to have survived, but you're already severely injured, so just accept your fate," Sha Xin sneered with cold killing intent in her eyes as she swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a fist-sized golden ball.

A series of cracks appeared on the ball's surface, and radiant golden light erupted out from within.

The ball then rapidly transformed into a giant golden bird puppet that was over a hundred feet tall, resembling a two-headed golden eagle. Its wingspan was also in excess of a hundred feet, and its entire body was covered in golden feathers that were etched with intricate designs.

The golden bird puppet had a very regal and majestic appearance, but at the same time, it was clearly also extremely dangerous.

E Kuai's expression changed drastically at the sight of the golden bird puppet, and he immediately launched himself at Sha Xin.

Despite the severe injuries that he had sustained, he was still astonishingly fast, recching Sha Xin in the blink of an eye.

A white longsword had appeared in his grasp, and it was radiating dazzling white light as its sharp tip pierced directly at Sha Xin's chest.

However, right at this moment, a golden wing abruptly appeared between Sha Xin and the sword.

The white sword struck the golden wing with a resounding clang, and the wing was able to stop the sword in its tracks with ease.

At the same time, another golden wing came swinging down at E Kuai's head like a giant golden saber, moving at an astonishing speed.

Even before the wing had fully descended, the gale-force winds that it was sweeping up had already sliced a series of deep trenches into the nearby ground.

E Kuai hurriedly dodged to the side, and at the same time, another white longsword appeared in his other hand as he slashed both swords through the air, unleashing a pair of formidable sword projections that struck the oncoming golden wing.

A violent eruption of golden and white light ensued, and powerful shockwaves swept through the air in all directions, scraping off a thick layer of the ground.

The entire building trembled and rumbled violently, while all of the Profound City and Puppet City cultivators hurriedly darted back in retreat.

The Weeping Blood Array was also struck by the shockwaves sweeping over the altar, and Han Li hurriedly channeled the power of the array in secret to bolster the crimson light barrier.

The white sword projections were shattered, but the golden wing was also stopped in its tracks.

E Kuai threw up another mouthful of blood as he flew back in retreat, and at the same time, he stomped a foot violently down onto the ground, launching himself up at one of the holes on the ceiling.

He was moving as fast as lightning, and it reached the ceiling in the blink of an eye, yet right as he was about to fly out of the hole, a golden shadow abruptly flew through the air.

Its speed far exceeded even E Kuai's, and it appeared directly in his path, blocking him from the hole in the ceiling.

E Kuai immediately drew to a halt upon seeing this.

At this moment, Sha Xin was standing on the bird puppet's back, and barely visible translucent threads could be seen extending out of his fingertips, connecting them to various parts of the puppet's body.

"Speed is the Gold-Winged Falcon's forte, so you're not going to be able to get away today, City Lord E. Just accept your fate," Sha Xin sneered.

All of a sudden, the Gold-Winged Falcon flapped its wings forcefully, releasing countless golden feathers that screeched through the air as they rained down upon E Kuai.

Each feather transformed into a streak of radiant golden light that hurtled through the air like miniature, golden shooting stars, and E Kuai seemed to be very apprehensive of these feathers as he swung his swords rapidly through the air.

Countless white sword projections were unleashed to oppose the golden feathers, but the sword projections were instantly decimated, while the golden feathers were only slowed down slightly as they continued to rain down from above.

A grim look appeared on E Kuai's face as all of his profound acupoints glowed radiantly, and he began spinning like a top, forming a white vortex of starlight around himself.

All of the nearby starpower converged toward him in a frenzy, and rays of white starlight were also shining down from the holes in the ceiling before fusing into the vortex.

As a result, the vortex instantly swelled to several times its original size, releasing fearsome tearing force that caused the nearby space to ripple and warp.

As soon as the golden feathers flew into the white vortex, they immediately veered off their original trajectories, being involuntarily swept up by the vortex.

Meanwhile, E Kuai lashed out with his swords to send the oncoming golden feathers flying one after another.

However, these golden feathers were imbued with tremendous power, and with each one that E Kuai repelled, he would involuntarily shudder and be knocked back slightly.

A string of resounding clangs rang out as all of the golden feathers came raining down in a ferocious barrage, slamming E Kuai into the ground to create a huge crater.

Most of the golden feathers that were repelled pierced into the ground, while the rest were redirected at the nearby walls, and in the face of these golden feathers, all of the surrounding structures may as well have been carved out of tofu.

The entire hall was trembling violently from the shockwaves sweeping through the air, and it seemed like it could collapse at any moment.

All of the Profound City and Puppet City cultivators had already fled even further away, and all of them were looking on in astonishment.

In the face of the two city lords, everyone else was made to resemble ants, and they couldn't play any role in the battle at all.

The Weeping Blood Array was also struck by a pair of golden feathers, but thankfully, it was still able to continue operating.

Meanwhile, Han Li was looking on with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

Even after sustaining such severe injuries, E Kuai was still displaying incredible power, so by opposing E Kuai, Han Li had put himself in a situation of extreme peril. If the Puppet City cultivators hadn't suddenly showed up, he would've been in a truly dire situation.

Right at this moment, E Kuai sprang out of the crater in the ground, and the starlight emanating from his body had already completely faded.

He threw up another mouthful of blood, and it seemed like he was truly a spent force.

The Gold-Winged Falcon appeared directly above E Kuai in a flash, and Sha Xin looked down at him with a cold expression as she said, "You're not getting away. Today is the day that I avenge our master!"

The Gold-Winged Falcon flapped its wings once again, unleashing another flurry of golden feathers.

Despite the terrible condition that he was in, E Kuai displayed no intention of giving up, and he was just about to defend himself when eight bursts of silver light suddenly shot forth from the side.

Each streak of light contained a silver ball, and they appeared above E Kuai in the blink of an eye.

The eight silver balls then exploded to release countless silver runes, which formed an array of silver light in the blink of an eye.

The array encompassed an area with a radius of several hundred feet, and it was impossible to see E Kuai within the array.

Countless golden feathers shot into the silver array, causing it to tremble violently, but it was able to remain intact.

Sha Xin's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and she cast her gaze toward the direction that the streaks of silver light had come from, but there was no one there.

She gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and the Gold-Winged Falcon swooped down at her behest before releasing another torrential barrage of golden feathers upon the silver array.

At the same time, a burst of radiant golden light appeared over its talons as it descended with unstoppable might.

A pair of giant golden talon projections appeared in mid-air, then clawed down upon the silver array before forcefully tearing it to shreds.

At the same time, two figures sprang out of the ruined silver array, and they were none other than E Kuai and Mistress Liu Hua.

At this moment, E Kuai's complexion was looking slightly better, seemingly having administered some self-treatment while in the silver array.

Instead of fleeing toward the holes in the ceiling of the hall, the two of them rushed toward one of the walls in the hall, which was riddled with cracks after being struck by around a dozen golden feathers.

Chapter 968: Don't Disturb Me

"You're not getting away!" Sha Xin yelled, and the Gold-Winged Falcon immediately set off in pursuit of E Kuai and Mistress Liu Hua at an astonishing speed, reaching them in the blink of an eye before grabbing down with its massive talons.

Right at this moment, Mistress Liu Hua suddenly swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of black light that hurtled directly toward the oncoming Gold-Winged Falcon like lightning.

The black light was formed by countless tiny black particles, and it was giving off very peculiar energy fluctuations.

Sha Xin seemed to have identified what the streak of black light was right away, and an alarmed look appeared on her face as she exclaimed, "Where did you obtain this Extreme Origin Magnetic Light from?!"

At the same time, the Gold-Winged Falcon swerved to the left at her behest to try and evade the streak of black light, but it was already too late, and the streak of black light struck the Gold-Winged Falcon in the abdomen.

A loud thump rang out as the burst of black light exploded into a series of glowing black ripples that rapidly spread outward in all directions.

The Gold-Winged Falcon's movements instantly became extremely stiff, and high-pitched grating sounds could be heard ringing out from within it, as if its internal mechanisms were being severely impeded.

E Kuai and Mistress Liu Hua pounced on this opportunity to dart away to the side to evade the Gold-Winged Falcon, which continued to fly forward in an uncontrolled fashion before crashing heavily down onto the ground, smashing open a massive crater.

Sha Xin was able to dismount the Gold-Winged Falcon in time, and she was also smashed into the crater along with it.

E Kuai and Mistress Liu Hua continued onward without pause, and right as E Kuai was passing by a certain sheltered spot, he abruptly rushed into it for a moment, and a pained cry rang out before immediately cutting off again.

As E Kuai re-emerged from that sheltered spot, he was carrying a person with him, and Han Li was surprised to identify that it was none other than Shi Chuankong.

His eyes were tightly shut, but his aura still remained, so it seemed that he had only been knocked unconscious.

This came as quite a relief to Han Li, but at the same time, he was rather perplexed. E Kuai had sustained very severe injuries, and he was still in a very perilous situation, so why was it that he had taken the time to capture Shi Chuankong instead of focusing wholeheartedly on fleeing the scene?

E Kuai continued to rush away like lightning, appearing in front of the wall that was riddled with cracks in the blink of an eye.

Radiant white starlight erupted out of his fist as he threw an almighty punch into the wall, and the entire building shuddered violently as a huge hole was smashed into the wall, allowing the light outside to shine into the hall.

Right at this moment, Sha Xin flew out of the crater in the distance, and an urgent look appeared on her face as she rushed after E Kuai and Mistress Liu Hua, displaying some very impressive speed of her own.

At the same time, she swept both sleeves through the air to release a pair of silver balls, each of which split open to transform into a giant silver bird in the blink of an eye, and the two silver bird puppets flapped their wings urgently as they flew after E Kuai and the Mistress Liu Hua.

Silver light was flashing over the bodies of the bird puppets, and countless sharp silver spikes shot forth through the air, raining down upon the targets that they were pursuing.

Even though Sha Xin had reacted very quickly, too much distance had already been opened up between her and E Kuai's duo, and the two of them rushed out of the hole in the wall before the bird puppets and the torrential barrage of silver spikes could reach them.

The silver spikes rained down onto the wall, instantly punching it full of countless holes.

The two silver bird puppets were quite similar in appearance to the Gold-Winged Falcon, but they seemed to be far inferior in power.

However, they weren't much slower than the Gold-Winged Falcon, and they were unable to arrest their own momentum as they crashed heavily into the hole in the wall.

Two resounding booms rang out as the entire building shuddered violently once again, and the hole in the wall was expanded significantly, but still not to the degree that it could allow the two puppets to pass through.

The two silver puppets were stuck in the hole, and they were struggling with all their might, presenting a rather comical sight to behold.

Sha Xin rushed over to the wall with a furious expression, and she made a rapid string of hand seals, upon which the two puppets rapidly shrank back down into a pair of silver balls that flew into her grasp.

"Xiao Zi, Kun Yu, come with me. Zhuo Fa, I'm going after E Kuai, so I'll leave everything here to you. You can have control of the Gold-Winged Falcon for now as well. Kill all of the Profound City scoundrels here!" Sha Xin ordered as she turned to Zhuo Fa.

At this moment, Fu Jian was still trapped in his crimson cocoon, and his aura was becoming more and more feeble, clearly indicating that he wasn't far away from death.

Out of the other three subsidiary city lords, Qin Yuan was dead, and Chen Yang had defected to Puppet City, so the remaining Profound City forces consisted only of Han Li, Sun Tu, Duan Tong, Zhu Ziyuan, and Zhu Ziqing.

Duan Tong, Zhu Ziyuan, and Zhu Ziqing's expressions changed drastically upon hearing this, and they wanted to flee, but they didn't dare to for fear of incurring Sha Xin's wrath.

At this moment, black light was flashing over Sun Tu's body, seemingly having unleashed some type of secret technique, and he rose to his feet with a grim expression.

"You can count on me, City Lord Sha!" Zhuo Fa assured as he cupped his fist in a salute, while the woman in purple and the brawny man by the name of Kun Yu prepared to set off with Sha Xin.

Han Li's gaze was focused intently on the woman that had been referred to as Xiao Zi by Sha Xin. Right as the trio was about to depart, Sha Xin seemed to have suddenly detected Han Li's gaze, and she turned to look at him.

Han Li hurriedly looked away upon seeing this, continuing to act as if he were in excruciating pain.

A hint of befuddlement flashed through Sha Xin's eyes, but she didn't delay any longer here and flew out of the hole in the wall, followed closely by Xiao Zi and Kun Yu.

Meanwhile, Zhuo Fa made a hand gesture, and Wu Yun, the two bald men, Chen Yang, and Xuanyuan Xing immediately converged to surround Sun Tu and the others.

Grim looks appeared on the faces of the four Profound City cultivators, and they immediately formed a circle with their backs facing each other.

Inside the Weeping Blood Array, Han Li was watching the purple-robed woman's departing figure with a conflicted look on his face.

However, he was able to quickly compose himself before continuing to absorb the tremendous bloodline power in the array.

At this point, both Sha Xin and E Kuai had already left, so he no longer had to keep up his act, and he began channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might.

Bright crimson light erupted out of his body as one profound acupoint was opened after another amid a string of dull thumps.

The entire Weeping Blood Array was also suddenly glowing far brighter than before, and the crimson light inside was swirling rapidly to form a vortex.

The attention of the Puppet City cultivators was instantly drawn to Han Li, and Sun Tu and Duan Tong pounced on this opportunity to rush out of the encirclement.

At the same time, Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing also rushed away in another direction.

Zhuo Fa cursed himself for his own complacency as he immediately set off in pursuit of Sun Tu and Duan Tong with one of the bald men, and at the same time, he yelled, "Wu Yun, you and Hei Er go chase after the other two. Chen Yang, Xuanyuan Xing, I'll leave the two people in the array to you."

Wu Yun and the other bald man gave an affirmative response before rushing after Zhu Ziyuan and his sister, while Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing made their way over to the Weeping Blood Array.

Right at this moment, a cold harrumph suddenly rang out beside their ears, and they felt as if a pair of red-hot daggers had been driven into their skulls.

They were just about to cry out in pain when a series of translucent chains shot out of the array, then vanished into their heads in a flash.

The two of them were instantly completely immobilized and rooted to the spot.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, so Zhuo Fa and the others weren't aware that anything was amiss. From their perspective, it simply looked like Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing were observing the Weeping Blood Array.

"Given our past history, I won't kill you, but don't disturb me," Han Li said in a cold voice, then continued to channel his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might.

After fleeing out of the encirclement, Sun Tu and Duan Tong immediately rushed toward the hole in the wall that had been smashed open by E Kuai.

However, both of them were carrying injuries that hampered their speed, so they were intercepted halfway by Zhuo Fa and the bald man.

Two resounding booms rang out as a giant white wolf and a giant silver panther came crashing down from above, standing directly in their path.

Each puppet was over a hundred feet tall, and they were casting enormous shadows over Sun Tu and Duan Tong.

Zhuo Fan and the bald man were each standing atop the head of one of the giant beast puppets, and Sun Tu and Duan Tong stopped in their tracks as looks of despair began to surface in their eyes.

"I have no personal qualms against you, but City Lord Sha has ordered me to take your lives, so I have no choice but to oblige," Zhuo Fa said, and the wolf puppet opened its cavernous mouth a this behest before biting down viciously upon Sun Tu and Duan Tong.

Chapter 969: One-Sided Battle

Sun Tu and Duan Tong hurriedly sprang back in retreat upon seeing this, but to their surprise, despite the wolf puppet's enormous stature, it was extremely fast and agile.

Before Duan Tong had a chance to react, a millstone-sized front paw had already appeared before him in the blink of an eye, sweeping toward him with tremendous power.

Duan Tong's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he could only retaliate against the wolf puppet's formidable paw with his thick right arm.

A gruesome crack rang out as Duan Tong's arm was instantly snapped in several places upon impact, and he was sent flying like a cannonball before crashing heavily onto the ground with blood gushing out of his mouth.

The wolf puppet shuddered as it took a step back, but it was immediately able to steady itself before opening its mouth to release a burst of white light.

The white light contained countless white flying needles that were screeching through the air, and they rained down upon Duan Tong in the blink of an eye.

The needles were imbued with tremendous power, punching countless holes into Duan Tong's body and the ground around him, granting him a swift and painless death.

A fearful look appeared on Sun Tu's face upon seeing this, and he immediately turned to flee.

However, right at this moment, the bald man descended upon him atop his silver panther puppet, which was swinging its two massive front paws through the air in unison.

Having just witnessed how easily the giant wolf puppet had overwhelmed Duan Tong, Sun Tu didn't dare to directly withstand the puppet's attack, and he frantically dodged to the side, only just barely evading the puppet's sweeping paws.

Right at this moment, a sharp screeching sound rang out, and the giant wolf puppet released another torrential barrage of white needles that rained down upon Sun Tu.

Sun Tu let loose a low roar as a thin, black bone sword appeared in his hand amid a flash of black light, and he slashed his sword at the oncoming barrage of flying needles.

A burst of black light erupted out of the sword, then transformed into a projection of a black feline creature that opened its mouth to release a black whirlwind, which swept up all of the flying needles.

In the blink of an eye, all of the flying needles vanished without a trace, while the feline projection also faded away, but the black light emanating from the sword had dimmed significantly, indicating that it had just expended a great deal of its power.

However, Sun Tu then flipped a hand over to produce a white crystal, while he pressed into a slot on the hilt of the sword, and the crystal instantly vanished, while the black light radiating from the sword was restored to its former brightness.

A hint of surprise flashed through Zhuo Fa's eyes upon seeing this, but he continued to keep up the pressure, and the giant wolf puppet pounced on Sun Tu in the blink of an eye, displaying far superior speed to the silver panther puppet.

Sun Tu remained calm and composed as he once again evaded the puppet's sweeping front paws, but after failing to strike Sun Tu with its initial attack, the wolf puppet immediately pushed off against the ground with its hindlegs to send itself crashing toward Sun Tu like a small mountain.

Yet again, Sun Tu was just barely able to evade the attack.

Thus, a game of cat and mouse ensued, with the giant wolf puppet throwing itself at Sun Tu over and over again, while Sun Tu evaded all of its formidable attacks.

Even though he was severely injured, Sun Tu was still a city lord, so he was far more powerful than Duan Tong and the others, and the giant wolf puppet was struggling to pin him down.

The puppet was displaying exceptional speed and agility, far superior to what one would expect to see in a living creature of its stature, but it hadn't unleashed any more barrages of flying needles, and it was unclear if this was because it had already used up all of its flying needles.

Even so, the giant wolf was picking up more and more speed as the battle wore on, and it was gradually beginning to catch up to Sun Tu.

Meanwhile, the bald man observed the battle from afar atop his silver panther puppet, making no attempt to help Zhuo Fa.

Zhuo Fa's Lone Wind Wolf was a puppet of an extremely high caliber, and it would have no problems dealing with an injured city lord. On top of that, the bald man knew that he would only serve as a hindrance to Zhuo Fa, and that was why he was remaining on the sidelines.

The giant wolf puppet continued to grow faster and faster, and right at this moment, it swept its front paw through the air once again.

This time, the attack was too fast for Sun Tu to evade, yet right as he was about to be struck, he let loose a loud roar as he slashed his black sword through the air once again, releasing the same black feline projection, which bit down onto the front paw of the giant wolf puppet, and the paw abruptly vanished into thin air, while the black feline projection returned to the sword.

However, the giant wolf puppet then performed a barrel roll before lashing out with its other front paw with perfect timing, as if Zhuo Fa had already anticipated that the feline projection would appear. In the same instant that the feline projection vanished into the black sword, the giant wolf puppet's front paw struck Sun Tu on the chest, inflicting several long and deep gashes.

Sun Tu was sent flying back through the air with blood spraying out of his mouth, and he slammed heavily into the ground with a loud thump.

Before he had a chance to get up, a short halberd shot forth through the air like lightning, piercing straight through his dantian to pin him to the ground.

Sun Tu struggled and writhed for a moment longer before falling completely still.

"Your puppet manipulation abilities have improved even further, Palace Master Zhuo. At this point, no one in our city aside from City Lord Sha is a match for you," the bald man praised as he approached Zhuo Fa atop his silver panther puppet.

"You're far too kind, Brother Hei Da. In terms of puppet manipulation, Palace Master Wu Yun and Palace Master Kun Yu aren't inferior to me, and Celestial Maiden Xiao Zi possesses such exceptional aptitude that even City Lord Sha has nothing but praise for her. Compared with them, I still have a lot of room for improvement," Zhuo Fa replied, then jumped down from his puppet before landing beside Sun To to recover his halberd.

His gaze then fell upon Sun Tu's black bone sword, and his eyes lit up slightly as he stowed the sword away.

After that, he rummaged through Sun Tu's robes to fish out a few more items before jumping back onto his white wolf puppet.

Hei Da raised no objections to this. Zhuo Fa was the one who had killed Sun Tu, so he was naturally entitled to all the spoils.

The two of them then turned their attention to Wu Yun and Hei Er, who were currently locked in a fierce battle against Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing.

Both Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing were carrying some injuries that hampered their combat prowess, and as result, Wu Yun and Hei Er had already gained the upper hand. At this rate, it was only a matter of time before they emerged victorious.

Meanwhile, Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing were still standing in front of the Weeping Blood Array, making no attempt to enter it.

Zhuo Fa's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he rushed over to the two of them atop his giant wolf puppet before asking in a cold voice, "What are you still waiting for, Fellow Daoist Chen Yang?"

Hei Da also arrived on the scene behind Zhuo Fa, and he suddenly interjected, "Hold on, something's not quite right here."

Only then did Zhuo Fa notice the dazed looks on Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing's face, and he drifted down from his puppet before giving Chen Yang a nudge as he asked, "What's going on here?"

However, Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing remained completely still and unresponsive.

"It looks to me like restrictions have been placed on their souls," Hei Da remarked.

"That does appear to be the case, but who could've done this? Does it have something to do with this array?" Zhuo Fa mused as he cast his gaze toward Han Li and Fu Jian inside the array.

At this point, the crimson cocoons around them had already become so thick that it was impossible to see the two of them from outside the array.

"In any case, we can't allow this array to keep operating any longer," Zhuo Fa said as a cold gleam flashed through his eyes, and he leaped back onto his giant wolf puppet.

A burst of radiant white light emerged over the puppet's body at his behest, all of which converged toward its only remaining front paw.

Immediately thereafter, the puppet sprang up into the air before swiping its front paw at the Weeping Blood Array, unleashing five crescent-shaped claw projections that were each several hundred feet in length.

The claw projections were giving off an extremely formidable aura, and Zhu Ziyuan and the others all turned to see what was happening from afar.

The five claw projections descended upon the crimson light barrier in the blink of an eye, and right at this moment, countless crimson runes suddenly appeared over the light barrier.

As a result, the light barrier was significantly bolstered, and an earth-shattering boom rang out as blinding red and white light erupted in all directions, causing the entire hall to tremble violently.

The tremors quickly subsided, while the white and red light also faded away to reveal the crimson light barrier, which remained completely unscathed.

Zhuo Fa's expression immediately darkened slightly upon seeing this.

"It looks like the two people in the array must be responsible for what happened to Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing. Palace Master Zhuo, let's combine our powers to break this light barrier together!" Hei Da urged.

Chapter 970: Holding the Fort

Hei Da raised both hands up into the air as he spoke, and a series of flashing silver patterns appeared over the body of the silver panther puppet.

"This light barrier is too resilient for our puppets to break through on their own," Zhuo Fa said as he raised a hand to stop Hei Da.

"What do we do then?" Hei Da asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"Don't worry, our puppets may not be able to break this restriction, but we have another trump card up our sleeves. This must be why City Lord Sha left the Gold-Winged Falcon puppet behind for us," Zhuo Fa said as he turned to the Gold-Winged Falcon.

Right at this moment, a cold harrumph suddenly rang out beside his ears, and he let loose an involuntary cry of pain as he reflexively threw his hands over his own head.

At the same time, several translucent chains shot out of the array, reaching Zhuo Fa in the blink of an eye, yet right as they were about to vanish into his head, dozens of near-transparent thin threads abruptly shot out of his glabella before wrapping themselves around the oncoming translucent chains.

The translucent chains were instantly stopped cold in their tracks, but the chains were far thicker and more powerful than the translucent threads, so they were able to continue inching forward through the resistance.

However, this brief window of respite was all that was required for Zhuo Fa to recover from the effects of Han Li's Spirit Stun Thorn, and he leaped up from his giant wolf puppet before rushing away into the distance as he sneered, "Looks like you must not have much experience in facing us Puppet City cultivators in battle. Otherwise, you'd know that a spiritual attack of this caliber wouldn't pose any threat to us."

Hei Da also immediately retreated into the distance with Zhuo Fa, while Han Li made a hand seal from within the Weeping Blood Array, and his spiritual sense chains struggled free from the translucent threads before flying back to him.

After that, Han Li took a deep breath and continued to focus on channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

During this brief period of time, he had opened close to thirty more profound acupoints.

Zhuo Fa flew onto the Gold-Winged Falcon in the blink of an eye, and a series of translucent threads shot out of his fingertips before vanishing into the puppet's body.

Meanwhile, Hei Da was standing in front of the Gold-Winged Falcon, observing the Weeping Blood Array from afar with a wary look on his face.

Some of the black light was still lingering on the surface of the Gold-Winged Falcon's body, but it had stopped proliferating.

A burst of radiant golden light appeared over the Gold-Winged Falcon's body at Zhuo Fa's behest, and the golden light began to retaliate against the black light.

As a result, the black light began to dissipate, but at a very slow rate.

A hint of impatience flashed through Zhou Fa's eyes as he pulled out the black bone sword that he had just taken from Sun Tu before slashing it through the air.

The feline projection reappeared, but it was looking far fainter than before, and it also seemed to be quite lazy and reluctant to move.

Zhuo Fa harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, and several translucent threads shot out of the palm of his hand before vanishing into the hilt of the sword, and only then did the feline projection spring into action, opening its mouth to devour the black light on the Gold-Winged Falcon's body.

With the feline projection working in conjunction with the golden light radiating from the Gold-Winged Falcon's body, the black light was quickly eradicated, and the Gold-Winged Falcon immediately spread its wings and flew up into the air, then darted around in the hall at an astonishing speed, easily leaving dozens of afterimages in its wake.

With each flap of its wings, gusts of ferocious wind were released, slicing deep gashes into the ground and the walls of the hall, forcing Wu Yun, Zhu Yuanzi, and the others to take evasive measures.

A fearful look appeared in Zhu Ziyuan's eyes as he looked up at the blurry golden shadow that was darting through the air.

This was Zhuo Fa's first time controlling this puppet, so he was rather unfamiliar with it, and as a result, the Gold-Winged Falcon's flight was slightly unstable.

However, it didn't take long at all for Zhuo Fa to adjust, and an excited look appeared in his eyes as he praised, "As expected of the fastest puppet in all of Puppet City!"

He then cast his gaze toward the Weeping Blood Array as a cold gleam flashed through his eyes.

All of a sudden, the Gold-Winged Falcon let loose a sharp screech at his behest, and it flew at the array like a bolt of golden lightning.

As it drew close to the array, the Gold-Winged Falcon suddenly folded its wings against its own body, making it resemble a giant golden spike that was hurtling through the air with unstoppable might.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which a Spiritual Sense Sword flew out of his glabella.

It was very taxing on his spiritual sense to keep Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing's souls imprisoned, so this Spiritual Sense Sword was far less formidable than what he was normally capable of unleashing.

The sword was aimed at Zhuo Fa instead of the Gold-Winged Falcon, and it appeared in front of him in the blink of an eye before racing toward his glabella.

Zhuo Fa's expression changed drastically upon sensing the aura of the Spiritual Sense Sword, and he hurriedly leaped to the side to take evasive measures.

However, the Spiritual Sense Sword abruptly changed directions as well, sweeping toward the translucent threads extending out of Zhuo Fa's fingertips.

"Did you think I would fail to anticipate such an obvious ploy?" Zhuo Fa sneered with a mocking look in his eyes, and the translucent threads attached to his fingertips suddenly took on a form resembling intangible mist.

The Spiritual Sense Sword continued onward without pause, sweeping through the translucent mist, causing it to implode and dissipate into specks of translucent light.

Much of the Spiritual Sense Sword's power seemed to have been expended in the process, and it dimmed significantly as if flew back into the Weeping Blood Array.

An astonished look appeared on Zhuo Fa's face as he lost control of the Gold-Winged Falcon, and its wings spread open on their own, causing it to fly directly upward.

As a result, it was the puppet's abdomen that crashed into the crimson light barrier instead of its beak.

The crimson light barrier caved in drastically, then rebounded forcefully to send the Gold-Winged Falcon flying up toward the ceiling.

Zhuo Fa frantically made a string of hand seals upon seeing this, and more translucent threads shot out of his fingertips before vanishing into the Gold-Winged Falcon's body in a flash.

After the Gold-Winged Falcon fell back under Zhuo Fa's control, it flapped its wings rapidly, stopping itself right before it struck the ceiling of the hall.

Zhuo Fa heaved a long sigh of relief, then cast his gaze toward the Weeping Blood Array, and the Gold-Winged Falcon immediately pounced down upon the array once again at his behest.

However, this time, instead of attacking with its beak, the Gold-Winged Falcon kept its distance and flapped its wings vigorously, sending countless golden feathers raining down upon the crimson light barrier.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

At this moment, there weren't many resources that he could draw upon while inside the array. If Zhuo Fa were near the array, then he would be able to retaliate, but if Zhuo Fa kept his distance and attacked from afar, then there was nothing that Han Li could do.

In the end, Han Li had no choice but to bolster the crimson light barrier even further in an attempt to keep out the golden feathers.

A string of resounding booms rang out, and the crimson light barrier trembled violently while being rapidly whittled down.

At the same time, Hei Da also began unleashing long-range attacks with his silver panther puppet to assist Zhuo Fa.

The crimson light barrier was whittled down further and further, and it didn't take long before it was finally shattered, upon which the torrential barrage of golden feathers rained down onto the array.

These golden feathers were astonishingly powerful, decimating most of the array with ease.

What remained of the array shuddered violently as a series of giant bulges appeared on its surface before exploding violently, and the entire array was completely destroyed, sending formidable crimson shockwaves erupting in all directions.

Even though Zhuo Fa and Hei Da were situated quite far away, they were still swept up by the crimson shockwaves, forcing them into retreat along with their puppets.

Zhuo Fa frantically made a string of hand seals to try and stabilize the Gold-Winged Falcon, but before he was able to do so, a radiant, white figure suddenly shot out of the crimson shockwaves up ahead before throwing an almighty punch at Zhuo Fa.

The fist was imbued with tremendous power, leaving a clear white mark in the space in its wake.

Zhuo Fa's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly darted back in retreat, abandoning the Gold-Winged Falcon in the process.

At the same time, a thick pillar of white light erupted out of the sole of each of his feet, enhancing his speed even further, and only then was he just barely able to dodge the oncoming punch.

The figure harrumphed coldly as he stomped down onto the Gold-Winged Falcon's back, and a dull thud rang out as the Gold-Winged Falcon was sent plummeting to the ground like an asteroid.

By using the Gold-Winged Falcon as a launching pad, the white figure was able to achieve extraordinary acceleration, reaching Zhuo Fa in the blink of an eye.

A panicked look appeared on Zhuo Fa's face as eight streaks of black light shot out of his spinal column, resembling a full set of spider legs.

Each leg was around twenty to thirty feet in length, with sharp black tips that were giving off a menacing gleam, and the eight legs pierced rapidly at the white figure in unison.

Chapter 971: Extraordinary Aptitude

Even though the eight spider legs were extremely fast, the white figure was even faster, and in the blink of an eye, he was able to grab onto all eight spider legs with his hands before snapping them with ease.

The white figure then hurled the eight snapped spider legs back at Zhuo Fa, sending them piercing into his chest.

As a result, Zhuo Fa was sent flying back through the air, and he twisted around in mid-air before a long, white chain shot out of his sleeve, then pierced into the ceiling with a loud crack.

He tugged forcefully onto the chain with one hand, launching himself into one of the holes on the ceiling, and this entire sequence of movements was performed in a very agile fashion, as if he hadn't sustained any injuries at all.

The white figure seemed to be rather taken aback by this, but instead of chasing after Zhuo Fa, then began to descend rapidly out of the sky.

The crimson shockwaves down below had only just subsided, and Hei Da immediately began fleeing toward the hole in the wall atop his silver panther puppet with a horrified look on his face.

However, right at this moment, the white figure abruptly appeared on the silver panther puppet's head in a wraith-like manner.

"Why are you in such a hurry, Fellow Daoist Hei Da?" the figure asked, and a burst of tremendous power erupted out of their body, instantly shattering the silver panther puppet's head.

Hei Da's first instinct was to flee, but it then occurred to him that there was no way he would be fast enough to escape from the white figure, so he stopped in his tracks again.

"You're a smart man, Fellow Daoist Hei Da. If you had dared to attempt an escape just now, you would've ended up just like this puppet," the white figure said as they stomped onto what little remained of the silver panther puppet's head, and its enormous body was instantly sent crashing into the ground.

Hei Da shuddered as a fearful look flashed through his eyes, and he remained completely still on the spot, not daring to make any false moves.

All of a sudden, a hole was blasted into the wall in the distance, and Wu Yun and Hei Er rushed out of the hole as quickly as they could.

The white figure had come from within the Weeping Blood Array, so he was clearly one of the two Profound City cultivators inside. With that in mind, the two of them immediately abandoned Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing to flee for their lives.

Zhu Ziqing was just about to turn and flee as well, only to be stopped by Zhu Ziyuan, and the two of them spoke briefly through voice transmission before making their way toward the white figure together.

Zhu Ziyuan's body was riddled with wounds, but he was still standing as straight as ever, and he cupped his fist in a grateful salute toward the white figure as he said, "Thank you for saving us, Fellow Daoist Li."

Zhu Ziqing also quickly followed suit.

The white light around the figure quickly faded to reveal none other than Han Li.

"Those two left on their own, so you have nothing to thank me for," Han Li replied in an indifferent manner.

He harbored no animosity toward the Zhu siblings. However, now that he had become sworn enemies with E Kuai, he naturally didn't consider the two of them to be his allies, either.

"In any case, you saved our lives, and for that, I owe you a favor, Fellow Daoist Li. I'll be sure to repay you in the future, but for now, we'll be taking our leave," Zhu Ziyuan said, then began making his way toward the nearest hole in the wall.

Zhu Ziqing took a glance at Han Li, and it seemed like she wanted to say something, but ultimately remained silent as she followed along after Zhu Ziyuan.

The two of them quickly leaped out of the hole in the wall and vanished out of sight.

"Fellow Daoist Li, may I ask why you've instructed me to stay behind?" Hei Da asked with an uneasy expression.

"Don't be afraid, I only asked you to stay as I have a few questions for you. If your answers prove to be satisfactory, then I'll spare your life. Come with me," Han Li replied, then turned and made his way into the distance.

Hei Da was very relieved to hear this, and he immediately followed along.

The two of them quickly arrived beside the Gold-Winged Falcon, and after examining the puppet for a moment, Han Li turned to Hei Da as he asked, "If I'm not mistaken, the cultivators of your Puppet City are using spiritual sense threads to manipulate these puppets, right?"

"That's correct," Hei Da replied.

"It must require very powerful spiritual sense to accomplish this, so all of you Puppet City cultivators must be using some spiritual sense enhancement secret technique, right? What is the name of this secret technique?" Han Li asked.

"It's a secret technique bestowed upon us by City Lord Sha, and it's called the Puppet Heart Technique," Hei Da replied.

"Give me the secret technique," Han Li ordered in a cold voice.

A hesitant look appeared on Hei Da's face upon hearing this.

"Is there a problem?" Han Li asked as a hint of killing intent flashed through his eyes.

"Not at all! Here's the secret technique," Hei Da hurriedly replied in a fearful manner as he pulled out a jade slip before offering it up to Han Li.

Han Li's expression eased slightly as he accepted the jade slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

The jade slip contained a spiritual sense enhancement secret technique that was no less profound than the Spirit Refinement Technique, and it consisted of five levels.

Aside from the secret technique itself, the jade slip also contained instructions on how to manifest one's spiritual sense into threads suitable for puppet manipulation.

Han Li was very interested in the art of puppetry to begin with, so he immediately began to study the contents of the jade slip closely.

A short while later, he stowed the jade slip away before raising his hands, and thick translucent threads shot out of his fingertips before vanishing into the Gold-Winged Falcon's body.

A burst of golden light instantly appeared over the Gold-Winged Falcon as it rose up into the air, much to Hei Da's astonishment.

The art of puppet manipulation was extremely difficult to master, and even with sufficient spiritual sense, it would normally take at least a century of diligent practice to master the art, yet Han Li had accomplished this in what seemed like the blink of an eye!

Han Li sprang onto the Gold-Winged Falcon's back, and it immediately began flying around inside the hall at his behest.

However, as a complete novice in puppet manipulation, his control over the Gold-Winged Falcon was far inferior to that of Zhuo Fa, and it was flying in a very unstable manner.

Han Li only flew around atop the Gold-Winged Falcon briefly before jumping back down onto the ground.

The art of puppet manipulation was extremely difficult to master, and he was only able to just barely get the hang of it thanks to his tremendous spiritual sense. Furthermore, he had no intention of using puppets in battle, and he was only familiarizing himself with the art of puppet manipulation in order to better prepare himself for potential future battles against Puppet City cultivators.

"I saw earlier that these puppets can be shrunk down into balls. How is that done?" Han Li asked.

Having already given Han Li the Puppet Heart Technique, Hei Da didn't have any qualms about revealing further information, and he replied, "That's accomplished using a secret technique invented by City Lord Sha that combines puppetry techniques with a spatial secret technique."

With that, Hei Da gave Han Li a detailed explanation of how the secret technique worked.

It was a rather complex secret technique, but now that Han Li had already achieved elementary mastery over puppet manipulation, he was able to quickly master this secret technique as well, and before long, the Gold-Winged Falcon had shrunk down into a ball that was sitting on the palm of his hand.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, and Hei Da was very relieved to see that Han Li was in a good mood.

"Do you have any other questions for me, Fellow Daoist Li? I'll be sure to tell you everything I know," Hei Da said in a sycophantic manner.

"What are Puppet City's objectives for entering the Great Ruins?" Han Li asked.

"According to City Lord Sha, we have two objectives, one of which is to kill E Kuai, while the other is to obtain the holy remains. As for whether there are any other hidden objectives, that's beyond me," Hei Da replied.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then said in a serious manner, "I have one final question for you. If you can answer it well, then I'll let you leave."

"Please go ahead, Fellow Daoist Li," Hei Da hurriedly prompted.

"That woman in the purple robe that's been accompanying City Lord Sha this entire time, her name is Xiao Zi, right? What do you know about her? When did she first come to Puppet City?" Han Li asked.

"Xiao Zi has always been by City Lord Sha's side, and she never seems to communicate with anyone outside of City Lord Sha, so I'm afraid I don't know much about her at all. All I know is that she possesses exceptional talent in the art of puppet manipulation, so City Lord Sha holds her in very high regard.

“As for when did she first come to Puppet City, I only recently came out of a period of seclusion that lasted several centuries, and by the time I came out, she was already in our Puppet City. Apparently, she first arrived in our city over a century ago," Hei Da replied.

Han Li was silent for a long while upon hearing this, following which he raised his head and said, "Alright, you can go now."

Hei Da was ecstatic to hear this, and he cupped his fist in a parting salute before rushing out of the hall.

Han Li remained standing on the spot for a moment, then heaved a faint sigh before stowing away Zhuo Fa's white wolf puppet as well.

After that, he strode over to the pentagonal pond.

Even though the Weeping Blood Array had been completely destroyed, the pond remained largely unscathed.

At this point, the door of crimson light at the bottom of the pond had already vanished, but Fu Jian was laying on the bottom of the pond in a completely still manner.

Han Li jumped down into the pond before examining Fu Jian's condition with his spiritual sense.

At this point, it would be an understatement to describe Fu Jian's condition as dire. His bones, muscles, and organs were all on the verge of failure, and even his nascent soul was close to dissipating.

What little remained of his aura was rapidly fading, and it wasn't going to take long before it vanished altogether.

Han Li naturally harbored no positive feelings toward Fu Jian, but even so, he couldn't help but feel a hint of sorrow at the terrible fate that had befallen Fu Jian.

After taking a moment to compose himself, Han Li cast his gaze toward the spot where the door of crimson light had been just a moment ago, only to find that there wasn't even the slightest trace of it left behind.

Chapter 972: Private Conflict

Han Li swept his gaze over the surrounding area with a contemplative look on his face.

Even though he had found a diagram of the Weeping Blood Array in the back of the hall, he still had no idea why the array was here and where the bloodline power surging out of the crimson gate of light had come from.

It seemed that E Kuai still knew a bit more than he did.

The fact that both E Kuai and Sha Xin had left this place without any hesitation indicated that the holy remains definitely weren't here.

In that case, he had no choice but to follow them deeper into the Scalptia Spatial Domain, both to pursue Violet Spirit and to find a way to leave this place.

With that in mind, a decisive look appeared on his face, and dense clusters of profound acupoints lit up over his body, amounting to a total of 475.

Even with Zhuo Fa's interference, Han Li was still able to master the first three levels of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts before the Weeping Blood Array collapsed.

On top of that, the Heaven Controlling Vial had absorbed the majority of the array's power, so he could draw upon it to continue breaking more profound acupoints in the future.

Even though he was still currently no match for E Kuai and Sha Xin, he was confident that he could crush any of the other cultivators from the two cities.

Furthermore, with his speed and movement techniques, he was somewhat confident in his ability to escape from E Kuai and Sha Xin should a conflict arise.

Han Li quickly concealed his profound acupoints again before turning his gaze to the other side of the blood pond, where Chen Yang and Xuanyuan Xing were still rooted to the spot.

Several translucent chains flew out of their heads at Han Li's behest, instantly restoring their mobility.

The two of them looked around to discover that the hall was even more severely ravaged than before, and on top of that, there was no one else here aside from Han Li.

An awkward look appeared on Chen Yang's face as he stuttered, "Fellow Daoist Li, you... I..."

"The Puppet City cultivators have already left. If you want to go after them, then go ahead," Han Li said in an indifferent manner, then flew out of one of the holes in the walls.

Upon arriving outside the hall, Han Li swept his gaze over his surroundings with slightly furrowed brows.

His spiritual sense was next to useless in the Great Ruins, so he could only carefully examine the residual energy fluctuations in the air to try and determine where Sha Xin and the others had gone.

However, too much time had passed, and the residual energy fluctuations in the air had become far too scattered. Hence, he could only decide on a rough direction to set off in.

At this moment, he felt as if his own body were filled with inexhaustible power that he was still rather unaccustomed to, and he would often find himself overbalancing slightly from exerting too much force while racing along the ground.

As he sped over the horizon, he encountered many sets of ruins, but he was too fixated on his goal of pursuing that woman by the name of Xiao Zi to examine any of those places.

Three days later.

Han Li arrived in a large, abandoned garden with a series of fake mountains of different shapes and sizes littered throughout.

As he was passing through the garden, he suddenly heard the sound of a battle ringing out up ahead to his left, alongside a rather familiar voice.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he suppressed his own starpower fluctuations before continuing onward in a cautious manner.

After emerging from the garden and traveling for close to another ten kilometers, he arrived at an enormous basin that was hundreds of thousands of feet in diameter.

From there, he hid behind a semi-collapsed stone wall before looking into the basin.

A woman clad in a suit of bone armor was wielding a bone whip in one hand and a bone spear in the other, clashing against a saber-wielding man in a suit of black armor.

It really is her...

The woman was none other than Gu Qianxun, and she was currently locked in battle against Shi Zhanfeng, who had put on a suit of purple devilish armor that was able to withstand all of Gu Qianxun's attacks.

At the same time, he was wielding a white bone saber, with which he was exerting tremendous pressure upon Gu Qianxun.

Gu Qianxun already had three profusely bleeding holes pierced into her lower abdomen, and at this rate, it was only going to be a matter of time before she was defeated.

Han Li also noticed that there was a female body lying lifelessly on the ground not far away from them. It was the petite woman who had been accompanying Shi Zhanfeng earlier, and there was a large hole in her chest.

A loud clang rang out as Gu Qianxun's whip wrapped itself around Shi Zhanfeng's saber, following which its sharp tip pierced directly at his face like a springing viper.

Shi Zhanfeng sprang back in retreat while tugging on his saber, and the bone whip wrapped around it was instantly stretched taut.

At the same time, all of the star acupoints on the saber began to glow radiantly, releasing a burst of tremendous starpower that instantly snapped the bone whip into pieces.

Gu Qianxun was also struck by this formidable wave of starpower, exacerbating the injuries in her lower abdomen even further, and she involuntarily stumbled back a step.

Before she had a chance to steady herself, Shi Zhanfeng's saber was already swinging down upon her with tremendous power, and she had no choice but to raise her bone spear to defend herself.

The ground beneath her feet was instantly shattered from the force of the clash, and her legs sank down into the ground up to her knees as she threw up a mouthful of blood while trembling uncontrollably.

Shi Zhanfeng flicked her spear away with his saber, then rested the blade of the saber against her neck as he interrogated with a threatening expression, "Who instructed you to attack me?"

Gu Qianxun took a glance at the body of the petite woman on the ground with a wistful look in her eyes.

If that woman hadn't shielded Shi Zhanfeng from a lethal blow at the cost of her own life, there was a chance that Shi Zhanfeng could already be dead by now.

"If you're going to kill me, then go ahead," Gu Qianxun said in a composed manner.

"The Myriad Opportunity Palace is still waiting for me, so I have no time to waste with you here. If you insist on falling by my blade, then I'll grant you that wish!" Shi Zhanfeng sneered as he raised his saber to decapitate her.

Right at this moment, a ball of fire shot forth through the air, striking Shi Zhanfeng's saber with such incredible power that he was sent stumbling away to the side.

Shi Zhanfeng took a glance at his own saber to discover that a red-hot, molten rock was currently slowly sliding down the blade of the saber.

He hurriedly turned around to find a tall figure in the distance, casually approaching the scene while tossing a few walnut-sized rocks up and down in his hands.

A stunned look appeared on Shi Zhanfeng's face as he identified Han Li, and mixed emotions surfaced in Gu Qianxun's eyes as well.

"Long time no see, Your Highness," Han Li said with a faint smile.

Shi Zhanfeng's eyes narrowed slightly as he sized up Han Li from afar. For some reason, he couldn't help but feel as if there were something different about him.

"Are you going to get involved in our private conflict, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Zhanfeng asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I don't know what bad blood exists between you two, but I have some things to discuss with her, so I'll have to ask you to leave, Your Highness," Han Li said as he stopped in his tracks.

"You can have a chat with her after we've settled our differences!" Shi Zhanfeng sneered as he swung his saber at the back of Gu Qianxun's head with incredible speed.

A burst of radiant starlight erupted out of the palm of Han Li's hand, instantly burning the rocks that he was holding into a red-hot state, and with a flick of his wrist, four semi-molten rocks were sent flying out of his grasp, reaching Shi Zhanfeng in the blink of an eye, with two of them aimed at his saber and the other two aimed at his heart and his dantian.

Shi Zhanfeng hurriedly withdrew his saber to defend himself, and the two rocks aimed at his saber missed their target, while the rocks aimed at his body were kept out by the saber.

The saber shuddered violently as the flat of its blade crashed into his chest, sending him flying back close to a thousand feet, and his legs were like a pair of plows, leaving a pair of deep trenches in the ground.

After steadying himself, Shi Zhanfeng looked down at the pair of cracks that had appeared on the blade of his saber with tightly furrowed brows, then quickly composed himself again as he smiled and said, "Looks like you've found more fated opportunities in these Great Ruins, Fellow Daoist Li. If you insist on saving her, then you can have her."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the white saber in his hand snapped into three pieces.

Despite this, he remained composed as he tossed the hilt of the saber aside, then bade farewell to Han Li before departing, quickly vanishing into the distance.

Han Li made no attempt to stop him as he strode over to Gu Qianxun.

Chapter 973: Pursuit

Gu Qianxun watched as Han Li drew closer and closer, and it was unclear what she was thinking.

"You can let go of the thing that's in your hand. Surely there's no need to use that on me," Han Li said.

Gu Qianxun relaxed a little upon hearing this, and he stowed away the white jade pendant that she was holding, then sat down before pulling her own legs out of the ground.

"Why did you help me when I already turned on you earlier?" Gu Qianxun asked after devouring a beast core.

"I met Mistress Liu Hua earlier, and he removed the Black Tribulation Centipede in my body, so I'm helping you as a form of repayment to him," Han Li explained.

"You met him? How is he?" Gu Qianxun hurriedly asked.

"He's doing well. He should currently be with E Kuai right now, traveling to where the holy remains are," Han Li replied, and a look of relief appeared on Gu Qianxun's face upon hearing this.

"Who exactly are you?" Han Li suddenly asked.

"I'm sure you've already figured it out at this point, haven't you? I'm a pawn left in the Scalptia Spatial Domain by His Highness, Shi Pokong. If it wasn't for his protection, I would've already perished by Du Qingyang's hands alongside my mother, and it's all thanks to him that I was able to survive and exact my revenge. Hence, I was obligated to follow his orders to eliminate Shi Zhanfeng and Shi Chuankong," Gu Qianxun replied.

Gu Qianxun's reply confirmed the suspicions that Han Li had harbored ever since their previous encounter, and he nodded calmly in response.

A wry smile appeared on Gu Qianxun's face as she sighed, "If possible, I really don't want to be your enemy."

"You can go after Shi Zhanfeng as you please. In fact, I can even help you kill him if you need, but if you go after Shi Chuankong again, then I'll have no choice but to strike you down," Han Li warned.

Mixed emotions flashed through Gu Qianxun's eyes upon hearing this, and she offered no response.

"Shi Zhanfeng should be far away by now, so you shouldn't be in any more danger. This is where we part ways," Han Li said, then turned and departed without any hesitation.

Gu Qianxun remained seated in silence for a long while before rising to her feet.

She was still looking a little unsteady on her feet as she strode over to her bone spear before picking it up, then took a deep breath before setting off in the same direction that Han Li had just departed in.

At this moment, Han Li was racing along with slightly furrowed brows, and there were many thoughts running through his mind.

He had thought that this trip into the Scalptia Spatial Domain would only be a brief one, and that he would be able to quickly return after finding Violet Spirit, but he had inadvertently become caught up in the conflict between Profound City and Puppet City.

That was already quite a pain in the backside, and now that it had become clear that Shi Zhanfeng and Shi Pokong also had some involvement in this place, the circumstances had only become more complicated.

Compared with Shi Zhanfeng, Han Li was more wary of Shi Pokong. The fact that Gu Qianxun was a pawn of his clearly indicated that he had already been exerting his influence upon the Scalptia Spatial Domain for a very long time.

The only reason that they could be interested in a place as barren and desolate as the Scalptia Spatial Domain had to be the holy remains in the Great Ruins.

With that in mind, Han Li couldn't help but wonder if that was also why Shi Chuankong had willingly accompanied him into the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

At the same time, he was thinking about Daoist Xie.

Upon entering the Scalptia Spatial Domain, he discovered that his connection with Daoist Xie had become far weaker than before. It wasn't that their spiritual connection had been severed. Instead, Daoist Xie suddenly felt a lot more unfamiliar to him.

Thinking back to the contents of the jade slip that Daoist Xie had given him, Han Li couldn't help but be curious about Daoist Xie's objectives.

In fact, he was even beginning to suspect that this former owner of Daoist Xie's was none other than that set of holy remains, or perhaps the former owner of the Great Ruins. Otherwise, how was it possible that the jade slip contained information known to no one else?

Even the route that he was currently taking was one that had been mentioned in the jade slip.

After traveling for several hundred kilometers, Han Li began to spot more and more signs of recent battles, presumably left behind by E Kuai and Sha Xin.

Occasionally, he would stop to take a look, only to quickly set off again.

......

Close to a month flew by in a flash.

On this day, Han Li arrived on a large white stone plaza.

There were four nine-story pagodas situated on the four corners of the plaza, and at the center of the plaza was a majestic palace that was far more massive than any other building he had previously seen in the Great Ruins.

Furthermore, in contrast with all of the ruins that he had encountered, this building was extremely well-preserved, and there were no signs of the ravages of time at all, as if the palace had been newly constructed not long ago.

Looking at the palace from afar, Han Li could see that its giant gates were wide open, and hanging above the entrance was a golden plaque that read: "Myriad Opportunity Hall".

Han Li immediately recalled hearing this name mentioned by Shi Zhanfeng earlier.

He suppressed his own aura fluctuations as he sped over to the palace, and while approaching the building, he noticed that there were many star runes engraved onto the ground, forming an extremely complex array several thousand feet away from the palace.

Upon reaching the staircase at the foot of the palace, Han Li discovered another separate array.

As he reached the entrance of the palace, Han Li discovered many char marks all over the gates, and all of the restrictions on them had been completely destroyed.

Instead of immediately entering the palace, peered into the building from outside to discover that the interior was in a state of complete disarray.

All of the furniture inside had been tipped over or smashed into bits, clearly indicating that a fierce battle had taken place here not long ago.

Han Li listened carefully for a while, but the palace remained completely silent, and that was slightly reassuring to him as he stepped inside.

The palace was completely empty with the exception of some furniture and puppet fragments, and E Kuai and the others were nowhere to be seen.

After conducting a thorough examination, Han Li discovered that these puppets were very similar to the ones that he had encountered elsewhere in the Great Ruins, indicating that they were puppets stationed here to defend this palace rather than puppets under the control of Puppet City.

Right at this moment, he suddenly spotted a black stone chair, which was standing upright and completely unscathed amid all of the wreckage.

He strode over to the chair, and after conducting a brief examination, a faint smile appeared on his face.

He grabbed onto the back of the chair with both hands, then twisted it to the side, and a grating noise rang out as a pitch-black passageway that led underground appeared beside the chair.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li jumped down into the passageway, then followed the stone staircase inside downward.

After walking several thousand feet through the darkness, he reached the bottom of the staircase, arriving at an opening.

Han Li slowed down to ensure that he was walking as quietly as possible, but as he drew close to the opening, he abruptly channeled his Wingform Ascension Arts and flew inside in a flash.

From there, he immediately swung around to inspect his surroundings, and he was relieved to see that there was no ambush waiting for him.

He quickly ducked behind a large rock, then carefully cast his gaze forward.

Up ahead was a giant lake of blood that was tens of thousands of feet in size, and the blood inside was constantly rippling slightly.

The surface of the lake was enshrouded under a layer of crimson light, and Han Li could see a crystal coffin floating on the surface of the lake at its very center.

The coffin was tapered from top to bottom, and it was over a hundred feet in size. It was transparent and flawless, and there was an extremely complex array engraved upon it.

Upon close examination, Han Li discovered that the core of the array was a pentagram design, but there were at least five other arrays branching out from it, all of which were interconnected in an extremely profound fashion.

Inside the coffin was a skeleton that was over a hundred feet tall, and all of its bones were as translucent as jade.

There were some sharp horns on the skeleton's skull, and there were also long tusks protruding out of its mouth. Furthermore, the entire skeleton was covered in a layer of scale-like patterns.

Right at this moment, Han Li detected Daoist Xie's aura, but it was extremely faint, and he was unable to ascertain Daoist Xie's exact location.

He closed his eyes to carefully examine the aura with his spiritual sense, but just a few seconds later, his eyes sprang open again as a bewildered look appeared on his face.

To his surprise, he discovered that his spiritual connection with Daoist Xie was gradually becoming weaker and weaker.

Right at this moment, an angry voice rang out from the other side of the lake of blood.

"Are you still not ready to repent, you traitor?"

Han Li hurriedly turned his gaze in that direction to discover Sha Xin and the Puppet City cultivators locked in a confrontation against E Kuai.

Mistress Liu Hua was standing behind E Kuai, while Shi Chuankong was laying at E Kuai's feet, and it was unclear whether he was unconscious or bound by some type of restriction.

Chapter 974: Identity of the Devilish Lord

"You're a fool, Sha Xin! Let me ask you this: what have you and I been waiting all these countless years for?" E Kuai asked.

Sha Xin gave no reply as she glowered intently at E Kuai with a look of righteous fury on her face.

"The two of us have been trapped in the Scalptia Spatial Domain for so many years, and our two cities have been in conflict with each other for just as long. Why did you come to me to propose a collaboration? Is it not for the same objective as mine? Why lie to yourself by bringing up those events from the distant past that no one even cares about?" E Kuai sneered.

"Don't compare me with you!" Sha Xin spat in a disdainful manner.

"Right now, the Devilish Lord's remains are right in front of us. If you and I split it evenly, then both of us will be sure to make massive strides in our cultivation, and leaving the Scalptia Spatial Domain will become a simple task! Once we reach the Devil Realm or the Immortal Realm, we'll be free to go wherever we please!" E Kuai yelled in a rousing voice.

Han Li took another glance at the crystal coffin floating above the center of the lake of blood upon hearing this.

At this point, he was all but certain that the set of remains in the coffin were the holy remains that they were referring to, but he couldn't help but wonder who this "Devilish Lord" was.

With that in mind, he couldn't help but think of Daoist Xie again. It seemed that Daoist Xie had many inexplicable connections to the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so was it possible that this Devilish Lord was none other than Daoist Xie's former owner?

"Are you here, Daoist Xie?"

Han Li called out to Daoist Xie through their spiritual connection, but received no response.

Right at this moment, Sha Xin's voice rang out again.

"You think I approached you for a collaboration because I share the same objective as you? If that's the case, then you couldn't be more wrong! I can tell you now that I've already found a way to revive our master!" Sha Xin scoffed.

"You must be dreaming! All that remains of the Devilish Lord is this body of his, and there's no way it can be resurrected! Otherwise, why do you think these Great Ruins have remained stagnant for all these years? It would be great if the Devilish Lord was still alive. That way, I wouldn't have been trapped here for so long! I advise you not to strive in futility toward something that's completely out of reach," E Kuai sneered.

"Ungrateful scum! It was all because of your betrayal that the Devilish Monarch was able to intervene in that crucial juncture of our master's ascension to become a Dao Ancestor! Otherwise, our master would've definitely been successful!" Sha Xin yelled in a furious voice.

"You don't know anything," E Kuai harrumphed coldly. "Even if the Devilish Monarch hadn't intervened, he wouldn't have succeeded anyway."

"Who are you to say something like that? If it wasn't for our master, you'd already be long dead by now, yet here you are, referring to him as Devilish Lord instead of master," Sha Xin scoffed in a furious voice.

"He only took me under his wing because he saw my aptitude and wanted to nurture me into a henchman. Both of us were merely pawns at his disposal, yet for some reason, you seem to enjoy that role. All those years ago, I chose the path of bodily refinement, while you chose the path of puppetry, and it all seems like fate now. You are destined to serve as the Devilish Lord's puppet for your entire life, even after he's been dead for so many years," E Kuai harrumphed coldly.

"Regardless of what you say, I'm not letting you get your hands on our master's remains just for your own selfish objectives. Once I resurrect him, I'll leave it to him to punish you as he sees fit," Sha Xin said as she suppressed her own fury.

E Kuai took a glance at Shi Chuankong, then sneered, "How are you going to open the coffin when you don't even have access to the bloodline of the devilish imperial family? I have a prince on my hands here. If you're willing to work with me, then both of us will be able to benefit. Otherwise, neither of us is getting anything!"

Before Sha Xin had a chance to reply, a tall figure in a veiled bamboo hat emerged from behind her, then declared, "The bloodline of our imperial family may be rare, but Chuankong isn't the only one who possesses it. In fact, my bloodline is a little purer than his."

The figure removed the veiled hat as they spoke, revealing a set of striking features that was headlined by a head of silver hair and a pair of purple pupils.

It was none other than Shi Zhanfeng!

E Kuai's expression darkened significantly upon seeing this, and he spat through gritted teeth, "I've done everything in my power to make you see the light, but you're still stubbornly clinging onto your little fantasy, so I suppose I have no choice but to beat some sense into you!"

He stomped a foot down onto the ground as he spoke, and the entire underground space shuddered violently, while the surface of the lake of blood rippled and quivered.

E Kuai immediately vanished from the spot, then reappeared behind Shi Zhanfeng an instant later before reaching out to make a grab for his head.

Shi Zhanfeng was able to react to the act, but it was still too fast for him to evade.

Right as the tips of E Kuai's fingers were about to pierce into his skull, a white bone spear suddenly shot forth from the side, striking E Kuai's wrist with a loud clang.

Out of the corner of his eye, Shi Zhanfeng could see that Kun Yu was holding onto the spear with both hands, attempting to shield him from E Kuai's attack.

The spear was bent over so far that it was almost doubled over, but it was only able to force E Kuai's hand slightly off its original trajectory. As a result, his swiping fingers failed to strike Shi Zhanfeng's head, but they still left several gashes in his face.

Taking advantage of this opportunity, Shi Zhanfeng ducked down slightly before pouncing forward while drawing a white bone sword, and the star acupoints on the sword were glowing radiantly as he thrust it directly at E Kuai's lower abdomen.

Right at this moment, the bone spear was snapped into two under E Kuai's hand, and at the same time, he raised a leg to block Shi Zhanfeng's sword with his kneecap.

Dense clusters of profound acupoints lit up over his leg, releasing a layer of starlight that protected his leg from the tip of the bone sword, following which he gave a cold harrumph before abruptly kicking out with his leg.

A ball of white light instantly erupted from the tip of his foot, hurtling directly toward Shi Zhanfeng's face.

Shi Zhanfeng immediately sprang back in retreat, opening up close to a thousand feet of distance between himself and E Kuai in the blink of an eye.

However, E Kuai's speed was far superior to his, and before he even had a chance to steady himself, E Kuai had caught up to him once again.

It was clear that E Kuai was desperate to eliminate Shi Zhanfeng, the muscles on his right arm bulged as layers of white starlight surged forth, culminating in a burst of explosive power that erupted out of his fist.

In the face of E Kuai's almighty punch, Shi Zhanfeng was struck by a sense of asphyxiation, and he felt as if even the space around him had become slightly warped, making it very difficult for him to move.

Han Li was rather astonished as he witnessed this from afar. E Kuai had sustained extremely severe injuries not long ago, yet it seemed like he had made a full recovery.

Even in his current form, with 475 profound acupoints opened, Han Li had no confidence in withstanding this attack in Shi Zhanfeng's place.

All of a sudden, a string of resounding booms rang out, and twelve radiant metal balls abruptly appeared around E Kuai.

Immediately thereafter, the twelve metal balls transformed into twelve armored puppets, each of which was holding a white bone chain with a curved blade on the end.

The twelve bone chains were sent hurtling toward E Kuai from all directions, criss-crossing over one another like a cobweb.

E Kuai immediately redirected his own fist upward upon seeing this, and a vast expanse of white starlight erupted out of his fist before splitting up into countless bursts of light that crashed toward the net formed by the white bone chains.

Right at this moment, all of the star acupoints on the net of bone chains abruptly transformed into a series of miniature vortexes that released tremendous suction force.

All of the starlight that had erupted out of E Kuai's fist was sucked into the star acupoints, thereby completely nullifying his attack.

Before he had a chance to do anything else, the net of bone chains had already fully descended upon him.

Immediately thereafter, the twelve armored puppets moved in a synchronized fashion to instantly adopt a certain formation, and a burst of silver lightning instantly flashed over the net of bone chains, forming a ball of silver lightning that trapped E Kuai inside.

It was only then that Han Li noticed that the woman referred to as Xiao Zi by Sha Xin was currently seated on the ground with her legs crossed, and there was a black stone array plate in front of her, upon which were placed twelve white stones.

Controlling twelve puppets at once and arranging them into a set formation in such a uniform and synchronized fashion was a very difficult task, so it came as quite a surprise to Han Li that it was Xiao Zi who had accomplished this feat, as opposed to Sha Xin.

Kun Yu was standing not far away as her guardian, having pulled out another bone spear to replace his snapped one.

Right at this moment, E Kuai's disdainful voice rang out from within the ball of silver lightning.

"You think such a crude array will be enough to trap me?"

Immediately thereafter, the profound acupoints on his body began to glow radiantly as he threw a punch at the ball of lightning and net of bone chains around him.

However, the starlight that erupted out of his fist was once again devoured by the star acupoints on all of the bone chains, and at the same time, bursts of silver lightning converged to strike E Kuai from all directions, raising large flurries of sparks upon contact.

The array of bone chains remained unscathed, but some tiny, barely visible cracks had appeared on the bodies of the twelve puppets, and Xiao Zi also shuddered violently, and it was clear that keeping E Kuai contained was a very demanding task.

"The array naturally won't be able to trap you forever, but all I need is for it to buy me some time," Sha Xin said in an expressionless manner, then beckoned toward Shi Zhanfeng, and the two of them sprang up into the air, quickly reaching the center of the lake.

Chapter 975: An Act

The two of them landed on the surface of the lake beside the crystal coffin, and faint ripples were spreading over the surface of the lake beneath their feet.

A series of mixed emotions flashed through Sha Xin's eyes as she gazed upon the set of remains inside the crystal coffin, and she took a deep breath, then said, "Please lend me your blood essence, Fellow Daoist Shi. Rest assured, I'll be sure to follow through on the promise that I made to you."

Shi Zhanfeng nodded in response, then swiped his sword over the palm of his own hand to create a gash, out of which blood that was tinged with faint hints of golden light began to flow.

Sha Xin immediately pulled a Star Wave Pen out of a pocket in her sleeve, and after dipping the tip of the pen into Shi Zhanfeng's blood essence, she began to make a series of inscriptions onto the surface of the crystal coffin.

The lines of blood essence flowing out of the pen quickly came together to form a crimson array that encompassed the entire coffin, fusing as one with the existing complex pentagram diagram on the coffin.

The coffin began to glow with radiant red light while also trembling violently, causing the entire lake to ripple and churn.

A layer of blood rose up from the lake like a living creature, encompassing the entire coffin to form a giant crimson cocoon.

A resounding boom rang out as E Kuai unleashed another almighty attack against his restraints, and the array around him was able to withstand his attack once again, but the cracks on the bodies of the armored puppets also increased further in size and number as a result.

A faint crack rang out, and a crack appeared on each of the twelve stones on the array plate in front of Xiao Zi as well.

At the same time, her body shuddered violently, and her complexion had turned deathly pale beneath the veil of her bamboo hat.

A concerned look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he didn't know how to proceed.

If he were to intervene now, there was a very good chance that he could be targeted by both E Kuai and Sha Xin. On top of that, if he were to rush in recklessly, there was also a chance that he would only hinder Xiao Zi rather than help her.

At this point, he was mostly convinced that this Xiao Zi was indeed Violet Spirit, but this was clearly not the right time and place for a reunion.

Right at his moment, a dull thump suddenly rang out from the crystal coffin, and the cocoon of blood around it flowed back into the lake to reveal the holy remains.

Strangely enough, the crystal coffin had completely disappeared, leaving behind only a crimson crystalline slab that was floating on the lake of blood with the holy remains laying on top.

The unveiling of the holy remains wasn't accompanied by any astonishing phenomena, as one would perhaps expect. In fact, it wasn't even giving off any formidable energy fluctuations ,and it appeared no different from an ordinary body.

However, Han Li could see that the crystalline slab beneath the body was riddled with extremely profound runes, most of which he had never seen before. Thankfully, the small portion of runes that he was able to identify were enough to tell him that the purpose of the crystalline slab was to suppress the body's bloodline power.

An urgent look appeared in E Kuai's eyes as he stared intently at the holy remains through the ball of lightning around him, and he began lashing out at the surrounding array once again.

Meanwhile, Sha Xin made a hand seal while chanting an incantation, then gently laid a hand over her own lower abdomen.

A burst of radiant white light instantly appeared over her lower abdomen, and a string of mechanical clicks rang out from what appeared to be her flesh, following which her fair skin spread outward like a blooming lotus flower.

She's modified herself into a puppet!

Han Li was very surprised to see this.

After her lower abdomen split open, a burst of dazzling crimson light erupted out of the opening, and everyone around the lake of blood with the exceptions of Sha Xin and E Kuai were stunned to see that there was a beating heart contained within a crystal ball inside the crimson light.

Not only was the disembodied heart beating vigorously, Han Li could hear the sound of its beating all the way from the other side of the lake.

At the same time, the heart was releasing tremendous life energy, and after the heart was revealed, the opening in Sha Xin's lower abdomen slowly closed again.

However, her aura had become noticeably more feeble, while her complexion had also turned very pale, and it was as if she had suddenly been sapped of half her strength.

"So you've been keeping that heart inside your body this entire time, yet you haven't dared to take anything from it! No wonder your cultivation base has only been regressing over the years. What a complete and utter fool you are!" E Kuai chortled with mirth.

Sha Xin paid no heed to him as she quickly devoured a beast core, then cradled the crystal ball with both hands as white light began to radiate from her palms, commencing the process required to free the heart from its seal.

Right at this moment, a muffled groan suddenly escaped her lips as the tip of a sword came protruding out of her chest, piercing straight through her heart in the process.

Half of her body instantly became drenched in her own blood, which Shi Zhanfeng twisted the hilt of his sword viciously, upon which a tearing sound rang out from within Sha Xin's chest.

Sha Xin threw up a mouthful of blood, then swung around to swing a hand at Shi Zhanfeng's head.

However, Shi Zhanfeng had already released his bone sword, and all of the profound acupoints lit up over his body, elevating his speed to an extraordinary level as he slid past Sha Xin before driving a bone dagger into her lower abdomen.

At the same time, he abruptly sprang up and grabbed the crystal ball out of Sha Xin's hand, then retreated to the other side of the lake of blood in the blink of an eye.

At the same time, a resounding boom rang out, and a vast expanse of silver lightning erupted in all directions, causing the entire underground space to tremble violently.

Interspersed throughout the silver lightning were countless shattered bone fragments that pierced a myriad of holes into the surrounding mountain faces and the ceiling above.

Han Li hurriedly ducked down right before one of the bone fragments sliced off the top of the large rock that he was hiding behind.

The array of bone chains had finally been broken by E Kuai, and the twelve armored puppets exploded amid an eruption of white light.

The twelve white stones also exploded, while the black array plate was shattered into pieces. As a result, Xiao Zi was struck by immense backlash that sent her flying back through the air while blood came gushing out of her mouth.

After freeing himself from the array, E Kuai took a glance at Sha Xin, then turned to Shi Zhanfeng with a smile as he said, "Congratulations on obtaining the heart that you so desire, Your Highness."

"It was all thanks to you, City Lord E," Shi Zhanfeng replied with a smile.

"So the two of you have been working together all along," Sha Xin spat through gritted teeth as she pulled out the bone sword that had pierced through her heart.

"What do you think, City Lord Sha? His Highness and I put on quite a convincing act, did we not?" E Kuai asked with a smile, and Sha Xin offered no response.

Earlier, Sha Xin had chosen not to intervene when E Kuai was trying to kill Shi Zhanfeng precisely because she was trying to see if Shi Zhanfeng was truly on her side or not, but in the end, she had still been fooled.

She reached into the front of her own robe to pull out a black stone vial that was around an inch in height, following which she pulled out the stopper before tipping out what appeared to be some golden sand onto the palm of her own hand.

She spread the golden sand over the hole in her chest, and the sand instantly entered her body like a colony of living creatures to mend her wounds.

"Now that you've lost the heart, there's no way for you to resurrect the Devilish Lord. I'm willing to give you one more chance to share the holy remains with me. What do you say?" E Kuai asked.

Instead of answering his question, Sha Xin pulled out a longan-sized metal ball as she instructed in a determined voice, "Xiao Zi, retrieve the heart at all costs."

"Looks like you're determined to go down fighting. In that case, I'll grant you the heroic death that you desire," E Kuai harrumphed coldly as he sprang toward the holy remains at the center of the lake.

In response, Sha Xin tossed the metal ball up into the air, and it transformed into a giant Arhat puppet that was over a hundred feet tall. The puppet was wearing a kasaya that was forged from metal, and it had eight arms, all of which were bulging with muscles that looked as if they contained immense explosive power.

A burst of red light appeared in the puppet's eyes, and it thrust all eight of its palms forward at once to release a burst of tremendous force.

A disdainful sneer appeared on E Kuai's face as he threw a punch in retaliation, and over a thousand profound acupoints lit up over his body as he unleashed a wave of fist projections.

The fist projections clashed against the eight arms of the Arhat puppet to produce a string of resounding clangs, and formidable shockwaves were sent sweeping through the air in all directions, causing the entire underground space to quake and rumble violently.

On the other side, Xiao Zi had sat down with her legs crossed once again, and a pair of strange-looking puppets had appeared before her. One of them was a humanoid puppet that had four metallic wings on its back, while the other resembled a prowling feline, but had the head of a young woman.

The two puppets immediately sprang at Shi Zhanfeng from different directions at her behest.